♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
♪ I got a feeling that it's
gonna be a wonderful day ♪
♪ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ♪
♪ And he's shining a salute
to the American race ♪
♪ Oh, boy
it's swell to say ♪
♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
-Firing pin!
-Hammer!
-Breech bolt!
-Come on. Easy game.
Name the gun part!
-Breech bolt!
-Muzzle!
Point for Steve!
Good one, Son.
-Breech bolt!
-Steve already
guessed it, Klaus.
Yeah, what are you?
An idiot?
Say that in mein bowl!
I dare you!
Wow, Hayley! Some dye job.
The carpet match the curtains?
-What did you do to your hair?
-I dyed it at
a Green Party rally.
You missed family game night
for that? Go wash it out!
You look like
a slutty wad of money.
-No way!
-Yes way!
-Stan!
-She started it!
It's my hair.
I'm keeping it.
What the hell
is wrong with that girl?
Do I have to smell like B.O.
and hump a redwood just
to get through to her?
Stan, I'm sure
this green-hair thing
is a phase.
I bet by tomorrow
she'll already be over it.
Something tells me
you're right.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- Sandman's a-calling.
Shh, shh, shh.
That's right. That's right.
Bigfoot's baking sugar cookies
and Santa wants to take you
to the Oscars.
-How's everyone's French toast?
-Smelly and ungrateful!
But this American toast
is delicious!
Well, Sleeping Beauty's
finally up.
Whoa! Nice dome.
You're almost as ugly as Roger.
I'm not ugly!
Am I?
-How dare you!
-How dare I? How dare I?
I'm sorry. I was at
the shooting range this morning,
and I left in my earplugs.
-Did you say, "How dare I?"
-Mom!
-Oh, Stan, how could you?
-How could I? How could I?
Sorry. Backup pair.
It's okay, honey.
You don't look like
a giant penis.
-How am I supposed to go
to school with no hair?
-Already got you covered.
-Wigs?
-Not just any wigs.
These are styled after
the most revered Republican
first ladies of our time.
The Barbara Bush,
the Nancy Reagan,
the Maria Shriver--
stay tuned.
Those are terrible!
Most girls your age
have to go through chemo
to get a wig this nice.
Do me a favor.
Stay out of my life!
How do I look now, Steve?
Pretty enough for you?
Huh? Ah, forget it!
Hey, turn down that rap music!
It's a bad influence!
-I swear, yo, shorty be
leaning on my last nerve!
-Well, what do you expect?
You shaved her head
in her sleep.
And putting her hand
in that bowl of warm water?
That was just overkill.
I wanted to see if it works.
It totally does.
Oh, finally.
-Mom, is my wig straight?
-Perfect.
What is that?
Horsehair?
Jeff's here. Later.
-Who's Jeff?
-My boyfriend. Don't wait up.
Boyfriend?
How can she be old enough
to have a boyfriend?
She still wets her bed.
Stan, you're so stressed.
You want me to make you
happy with my mouth?
Yeah, I guess so.
Well, that helps a little.
Stan, maybe you'd feel better
if we met this boy.
Why don't we have him
over for dinner so you
can get to know him?
That's brilliant, Francine!
Now rephrase it so it sounds
like my idea.
Man, that dance
is gonna be a rager!
Yeah. It's too bad
we can't get dates.
What? Fellas,
girls want to get down
just as bad as we do.
Here, here. Watch.
Hey, foxy. Ohh!
You got something
to say, Barry?
Easy, Steve.
We're just not studs.
We are the geeks who don't
get the choice babes
until we're making major cash
in our mid-to-late 30s.
No. No, no.
You know what?
Not only am I going
to that dance,
but I'll bet each of you
20 bucks I also get boob.
-Bring back the bra
to prove it?
-I'll do you one better!
I'll wear it back!
No. Actually,
I'll just bring it.
My surfboard nails me
in the head, and I go down
like a bag of rocks.
And just then, my life
flashes before my eyes,
and I'm bored.
He's bored!
Oh, you took us the other way
with it, Jeff. Thank you.
Hey, I just hope one day
I, too, have a daughter
who's as smart
and wonderful as Hayley.
Oh! Isn't he sweet, Stan?
He sure is. Next time
I'm out of Jolly Ranchers,
I'm just gonna suck on Jeff.
Jeff, you were so good
at dinner.
Babe, we're good together.
Which is why I was thinking
you should move in with me.
Whoa!
It's only been three weeks.
Besides, I don't think my dad
would be too happy with that.
Babe, your dad digs me.
I can tell. He wants us
to be together.
Great. Now it's officially
a sausage fest.
See you tomorrow, fellows.
Hey, Sanchez, try to get to
work on time for a change.
Hey. No fair.
Hey, don't make me
come up there. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, you'd better fly.
Huh. Ah, what
a bunch of clowns.
There. Now you can talk,
and we took care
of that mustache.
Dad, are you insane?
You can't just
abduct me like that!
Hey! Don't you use
that word in this house.
I "liberated" you.
And maybe next time
you'll think twice before
dating the wrong guy.
There's nothing wrong
with Jeff.
Too bad.
I forbid you to see him.
-What?
-Stan, I'm not sure we should--
-Francine, wait in the car.
-What?
Hayley, this is for
your own good. Jeff was
much too relaxed at dinner.
He had the laid-back
attitude of a stone man.
-Do you mean a stoner?
-Go wait in the car
with your mother.
You can't do this. I'm 18.
While you're under my roof,
you'll live by my rules.
Dude, this is your house!
And you're alive!
Well, guess what, Dad?
I don't have to listen
to your rules anymore.
-I'm moving in with Jeff.
-What?
-Right on, babe.
-Hayley, don't go!
You get back here,
Hayley! No?
-Well, I didn't want to have
to use this, but... rhubarb!
-Rhubarb?
Mm. That's her trigger word.
I had her brainwashed at five.
She's supposed to
kill Walter Mondale,
but I guess it didn't take.
-Come on.
Let's go to your place.
-This is my place.
-What? You live in your van?
-No. We live in our van.
My mom had me right
where you're sitting.
Jeff, how could you not tell me
you live in your van?
Babe, we did it.
We took the plunge.
Come celebrate on the patio.
Can we just get out of here?
I got to get away
from my parents.
This van is our pen,
and the road is our parchment,
and together
we'll drive a poem
across America.
Yep. This is the spot.
We are right where
we need to be.
Uh! I got to use the can.
Oh, Stan, I can't believe
our little girl moved out.
Oh, Francine,
you are gonna love this.
Jeff-- Y-You know Jeff--
Jeff lives in his van.
And the piece of junk
just broke down right outside.
She's not going anywhere.
-Stan, are-are you sure
she's safe--
-Hey, Hayley!
At least the last time
you ran away, you made it
all the way to the stop sign!
Aw, that's funny.
I'm funny.
Don't egg her on!
She'll never want to come back.
Francine,
she hates it in there.
By morning,
she'll be back in bed
wearing her footsie pajamas
and sucking on her
Lion King blankie.
-But she got rid
of those things years ago.
-Not in here she didn't.
Oh, Stan, our little girl
is back!
Hey, I didn't order
"rude" service.
-Roger, why aren't you
in the attic?
-Oh, it's so cold and drafty,
which is great for a Michelob,
but I got to sleep up there.
Oh, yeah. That's good.
That's not too bright.
That's fine.
Stan, she's still out there.
What is she squatting over?
Oh, Hayley, that's not how
you make coffee.
-Is Roger moving
into Hayley's room?
-No, he is not.
Fine. I'll go up
to the frigid attic.
I'm supposed to
bring pneumonia back
to my home planet anyway.
Stan, I want my baby girl home.
Just go down there
and apologize.
No! No apologies.
George W. taught me that.
I just have to remind her
how great life is
in the Smith home.
Babe, keep tonight open.
Marco and Skye are having
a wine and cheese thing
in their Tercel.
Oh, hi, Hayley. I got you
a clown and a petting zoo.
Sure you don't want to
move back in?
Maybe the clown
will ride the pig.
Man, we're having fun!
-How much longer
do I have you for?
-Two hours.
Go read to my wife.
Uhh!
How's the bra hunt coming?
Making progress.
A girl just groped me
with her foot.
What the heck?
Since when does Frankle
reel in the babes?
Oh, he's got
the sympathy factor
working for him.
His little brother got his arm
stuck in a ski lift,
tore it right off.
-Boy, that sucks!
-Not for Frankle.
Sure, girls. I'll judge
your kissing contest.
-Good news, Francine.
-Hayley's back?
-Even better. Say hello
to your new daughter!
-What?
-Isn't she beautiful?
-Is that a Chinese baby?
Sure is.
Japanese to be specific.
Stan, I don't want
a new daughter.
Don't you get it?
I want my Hayley!
One of us pooped.
Hayley, what happened?
You used to be so easy.
-Eat your peas, Hayley.
-Why?
So you can be strong enough
to fight off President Clinton's
sexual advances.
Oh, there he is right outside.
Hey, Stan. Did you hear?
Sanders just killed
his first dictator.
Well, first he was
a U.S. ally, then a dictator.
-Yeah, a dictator.
I mean, it's good. I'm happy.
-Hey, we got to celebrate!
-Lunch and drinks Friday
at the place with the buffet?
-Great!
So, Stan, did Hayley
move back in?
No. And Francine
is just devastated.
I mean, if she's this upset now,
what's she gonna be like
when Hayley dies?
Have you talked to Hayley?
You know, to let her know how
much you want her home?
Absolutely not!
I could never grovel
to my own daughter.
But I think I know
someone who could.
- Paper or plastic?
- Burlap.
I, too, share your annoying
concern for the environment.
-Dad?
-No! No, I am former
Communist named Petrov.
Like you, I embrace insane
left-wing philosophies
-which are best discussed
in comfort of parents' home.
-Dad, leave me alone.
All right, I've had enough
of this. You're coming home
with me right now or else.
-Or else what?
-That'll be 38.40.
-Hey!
-Or else you can't use this.
Your mother and I gave you
this card, and I can damn well
take it back.
-Fine. I don't need your money.
-Good! 'Cause I'm completely
cutting you off!
Petrov, go restock
that stuff.
Can't Susan do it? I on break
in, like, two minutes.
-Thanks for tutoring me.
-No worries.
Hey, did you hear about
Frankle's brother
losing his arm?
Yeah. Poor Frankle.
I just wanted to hug him
and never let go.
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember when my sister
had her accident.
Oh, did I not mention my sister
who was horrifically burned
over 98% of her body?
-That's terrible!
-Only her taint survived.
Okay, it's on! You pull this off
and I'll convince my parents
to let you sleep in here.
Don't worry.
I've been studying all day.
I even watched Meg Ryan's
latest movie where she plays
that burn victim.
-She never played a burn victim.
-Oh, Meg, honey.
Kim, meet my sister Hayley.
Time for your burn cream.
I hope I don't cry
like last time.
-What-- What happened?
-Oh, I was dating a pool guy.
And he thought it'd
be kinky if we gave each
other chlorine massages.
I went first.
Ooh! Mm, that's cooling.
-How awful!
-I know! I'm hideous!
-You are so not hideous.
-Oh, don't tease me!
No, really.
It's your eyes and the unique
shape of your head.
I think you're beautiful.
Oh, oh. And Steve's
been a super little brother.
Freezing my Snickers,
sticking me in the shade
outside.
-Steve, that is so sweet.
-I know.
-Want to go to the dance?
-I'd love to.
Great!
Well, see you, Hayley.
I am beautiful!
Mm! Uh! Oh!
Saw my tushy.
Impressive, Miss Smith.
A lesbian of color couldn't
have done a better job.
-I'd give it an "A,"
if you had paid your tuition.
-What?
But I'm paid up
for the semester. Dad.
There are no free rides here
at Groff Community College.
-You have three days
to pay your tuition.
-A whole semester's tuition?
How am I supposed to
come up with 85 bucks
in three days?
Welcome to House of Hoagies.
Can I get you a sandwich...
with nothing on it?
-Hey, waitress, bring me a beer.
-I just brought you one.
Yeah. This one's
to drown my crabs.
Don't worry, doll.
It gets easier.
I'm fine.
At least I'm not being exploited
like these poor strippers.
-Exploited? Sweetie,
these girls are being empowered.
-Yeah, right.
Think about it.
All they do is
show their breasts
and men hand over hundreds
of their hard-earned dollars.
Who's really
being exploited here?
Plus, to quote Camille Paglia,
these ladies are
sexual conquerors
controlling the channel
between nature and culture.
Take it off, bitch!
Camille Paglia, huh?
Hey, Stan, everything
work out with Hayley?
No. I had to cut her off
like a diseased hand.
And like any diseased hand,
sooner or later
she'll come flopping back.
-They always do.
-Yep, I got her
right where I want her.
All right, gentlemen.
Let's welcome to the stage,
Dusty!
Yeah!
Oh, my God!
What is she doing?
Pretending to ride a horse.
If you want to see
a real horse, you got to
go to the track.
Come on. We're all leaving.
The girls here are "vugly."
We can't leave.
We just got here.
- Oh, no!
- Somebody pulled the alarm!
You know what that means.
Dusty, you're on fire!
And that's a double dance
for you! Ha!
Yeah!
-Ow!
-How could you
let Hayley do this?
-Do what?
-Don't play dumb.
You know she's stripping!
Showing people her Ho Hos,
her Ding Dongs, her Susie-Q's,
her-- her, uh, uh...
Wh-What are those called?
Those-- The little pink
with coconut?
-Th-They're really good. Uh--
-Her Snowballs?
-You bastard!
-I didn't know
she was stripping!
-Don't lie to me, stone man.
-For real.
She said she was out
torching SUV's.
-I'd never be cool
with stripping.
-Really?
Yeah! I mean,
I've dated three strippers,
and two of them turned up dead.
And the cops always go
to the boyfriend with the van.
That's profiling, man.
And that's wrong.
Well, that's the price you pay
for the sweet pleasure
of van ownership. Let's go!
Kim! Wow, you look great!
B-But the dance isn't
for two hours.
Yeah.
But I got to be up early
for church camp.
So I thought we'd
fool around beforehand.
Thank you, Jesus.
Oh, wait.
Can I say hi to your
charred sister first?
I was also thinking
some mascara, you know,
to draw focus to my eyes.
You know what else?
Some blush would really
bring out your cheekbones.
I love that idea!
Paint me! Paint me!
Oh, yeah.
Who's your daddy?
-I am!
-Dad!
Blow up many
four-runners today?
Or did you four-get?
-Jeff, I'll, uh,
do the talking.
-Let me go!
-Hey, she's not going anywhere!
-Yeah? Who's gonna stop me?
I see. Well, I don't
want any trouble.
I'll just be on
my merry little way--
Hey, Bo Peep.
I know where you can
find your sheep. In hell!
Hayley,
are you in there?
I brought some fresh laundry
and rinsed out your tinkle can.
Hello?
Hayley's working
at a booby bar?
And she traded shifts
with Tina?
What does Tina have to do
that's so important?
Oh, wait.
This isn't about Tina.
This isn't about Tina!
It's never
been about Tina.
Kim, we are running out
of time if we're going to,
you know, get busy.
Here I come!
Oh, you look gorgeous!
-Doesn't she look
gorgeous, Steve?
-Stunning.
Can I talk to you, Sis?
Would you cut it out?
I should be touching
her na-nas right now!
All you had to do
was sit there and be ugly.
- I am not ugly!
- Steve!
Th-That's not what I said.
Tell-Tell her, Hayley.
Or maybe you don't want to
stay in this room anymore.
Kimmy! He wants to
lock me in the attic
like I'm some kind
of disgusting monster!
-Well, you are!
-Shut up!
You shut up!
I never want to
see you again, Steve!
Roger, I thought
we had a deal.
Rouge can make a fellow
do crazy things, Steve.
-Sorry I ruined your plan.
-Sorry I called you ugly.
Well, I guess I'll go
let the guys know
I'm a loser after all.
Steve, wait.
Kimmy loaned this to me.
Roger, you are beautiful.
Way to go, Mr. S.
You're so hot!
Oh, I remember now.
I was gonna be
a civil engineer.
What are you gonna do?
Tickle me to death?
Ooh!
-You're coming home right now!
-I don't have to listen to you!
Stop!
Just stop right there!
We've tried doing things
your way, and it's only
made things worse.
-But she's making
so many mistakes.
-You sound just like my father.
He never supported
my choices.
My dad didn't support me either.
That's why I started stripping.
-Me too.
-Same here.
Yeah.
Plus my uncle touched me.
I never meant to
drive Hayley away.
Stan, we need to
listen to these ho-bags.
Hayley's gonna make mistakes,
but they're hers to make.
And as parents,
the most important thing
we can do is be supportive.
Supportive?
Yes.
Ooh, yeah!
Shake it, baby!
You will not break it!
It took me nine months
to make it!
-Give me some more singles.
-You used to look like that.
-What are you guys doing?
-Being supportive.
Look, I've been treating you
like a little girl. And, well,
you're a grown woman.
You made that abundantly clear
halfway through that Jay-Z song.
-Oh, come back home, honey.
-What do you say?
-Give your old man
a second chance.
-I'll think about it.
You have some
pretty terrific parents.
I guess that means
you're done here, and you'll
be going back home, huh?
Yeah. Then again,
the girls are really nice,
and the money's awesome.
No, I think I'll stay.
Hit it, Ron!
-Oh, man! That's gross!
-Yeah. That's the one place
you want them to have hair.
-Oh, I got a good one!
-"Quivix?" That's not a word.
-It is on my planet.
-Is it a proper noun?
-Damn!
-I'm going out with Jeff.
-Hey, be home by 11:00.
-Dad!
-Okay. Just be safe.
-Thanks, Daddy.
All right, you have visual?
All right, stay three car
lengths behind her and check in
with me every half hour.
Yes, I know!
She's got a great ass!
Stay on it!
Have a great night!