♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
♪ I got a feeling that it's
gonna be a wonderful day ♪
♪ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ♪
♪ And he's shining a salute
to the American race ♪
♪ Oh, boy
it's swell to say ♪
♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
Shoot him! Shoot him!
Big Bird, just share it
with Cookie Monster.
Don't trust him!
He just pretends to eat cookies,
but he never swallows anything.
Good morning.
Francine,
your negligee is see-through.
Unfortunately, you are not.
Oh, Stan, doesn't
today have some special
significance for you?
Today? Wait!
- Is today the 14th?
- Yes. Yes, it is.
Good God!
How could I forget a date
so dear to my heart?
It's the big C.I.A.
fishing trip.
You're gonna do
the laundry anyway, right?
Hmm! No time to poop.
I'll just do it
on the way down the stairs.
You're gonna
vacuum anyway, right?
See you, Mom.
I'm going to the mall
to try and figure out
how the piano store
stays in business.
Hold up, Steve.
I'm going with.
Whoa, Roger.
You know you can't
leave the house.
- Everyone else gets to.
- Well, everyone else
isn't an alien, now are they?
Whoa! Somebody had a big piece
of grouchy pie this morning.
I just can't believe
Stan forgot our anniversary.
- I would never forget
our anniversary.
- We have an anniversary?
October 25, the day you forgot
to put on underpants.
Let's celebrate early.
Quick! Straddle mein bowl.
Hayley, do Mommy a favor
and put on something
less revealing.
There is nothing inappropriate
about this outfit.
Not if you're gonna spend
the weekend tinkling
on Bob Guccione.
Oh, God, Mom.
Were you ever cool?
Oh, yeah, Hayley?
Well, I pity the fool
who thinks I'm uncool.
Get it? I was making
a Dr. "T" reference.
Hey, Hayley, guess
where I'm taking you
this weekend.
♪ Burning man ♪
It's this awesome celebration
where they burn
this huge wooden man.
It's all about life, love
and the power of community.
No, it's all about
a bunch of naked morons
drinking and doing
lots of drugs.
- What are we, 12?
- Wait. Before you decide--
This is a microcosm
of the power
that is Burning Man.
Imagine this,
but 70 feet tall.
Ah, nothing like
the great outdoors.
Who's ready to do
some fishing?
Yeah, yeah!
Let's go fish! Yeah.
This is Cast Master One.
Bring in air support.
Look,
it's Ariel.
- Hey, Jackson, you ever do it
with a dead mermaid?
- Mermaid? No.
Oh, my God.
Lindsay Coolidge.
Could she be any sexier?
Gross! She'd never
do that, Toshi.
Besides, where are we
gonna get a dozen
Ping-Pong balls?
Hey, Steve,
she's coming this way.
Ask her out--
unless you're afraid.
You forget yourself, Snot.
Steve Smith is never afraid.
I'm Steve Smith.
Would you like
to go out with me?
- I'd love to.
- Really?
On one condition.
You gotta find a date
for my friend Jewel.
- No problem.
- Here she comes now.
Hey, Jewel,
Steve here is gonna
set you up on a date.
Jewel, I'd like you
to meet my friends.
Godzilla!
I can't believe
that Dummkopf didn't
remember your anniversary.
And after what happened
last year--
Oh, that was classic.
♪ Bad boys, bad boys
whatcha gonna do ♪
That jerk forgot
our anniversary!
- Keep her away from me!
- Aah!
Okay, okay. I'm cool.
Ach, ja! This is
my favorite part.
Here it comes,
here it comes,
here it comes!
He could never forget
a beating like that.
I'm sure he's just waiting
for the perfect time
to surprise me.
After all,
our anniversary
isn't over till midnight.
This midnight fishing
is great.
Sounds to me like someone
doesn't want to go home.
Yeah, I'm, uh, laying low.
Today is the anniversary
of a huge fight
me and Francine
got into last year.
- Yeah? What about?
- Oh, I forgot our anniversary.
I'm never
gonna do that again.
I-- Uh--
Ahh!
There it is.
Oh, good. You're up.
I, uh, have a special
anniversary surprise
for you.
Your favorite song,
sung by America's
sweetheart,
Whitney Houston.
Come on, daddy.
I-- I need my fix.
Remember the deal, Whitney.
First you sing, then you get
your precious cocaine.
How dare you!
Do you think
I would--
♪ No matter what
they take from me ♪
♪ They can't take away
my dignity ♪
Happy anniversary, sweetheart.
Come on, Whitney.
Go get it.
What a performer.
Well, let's turn in.
You know what?
If you don't get
why this day
is so important to me,
I guess you never will.
Sweetie, I made a mistake.
Can't you take a page
from that bitch Hillary Clinton
and just let it go?
No! This is the most
inconsiderate thing
you've ever done.
I am never
going to forget this.
I was afraid
you were gonna say that--
which is why
I got you this card.
Open it.
I promise it'll
make everything better.
There's nothing
that could-- Oh.
Thank God for top-secret
C.I.A. technology.
Just lose the last 20 hours
of her memory.
- That ought to get me
out of the doghouse.
- Francine?
- Francine, can you hear me?
- Don't kick me out.
The bouncer said I could,
like, totally meet
Def Leppard.
- Def Leppard?
- Francine, what year is it?
Duh. 1985.
Hey, anybody got some gum?
I wanna get the taste
of roadie out of my mouth.
- Why the hell does my wife
think it's 1985?
- Huh.
Instead of erasing
the last 20 hours,
I must have erased
the last 20 years.
Oh, I guess this
is the dial for hours,
and this is the dial
for years. Yeah. Yeah.
The last 20 years
of your wife's memory
have been erased.
Well, go ahead
and undo it.
Reverse brain erasing?
Now that's just
science fiction.
Kind of like
the female orgasm.
Oh, that's great.
You gotta do stand-up.
You gotta. You're great.
You know, you're not
the first person
who's told me that.
I bet I'm not.
Anyway, Stan,
the procedure
is irreversible.
- You're kidding.
- 'Fraid not.
But if you do
figure something out,
let us know,
and we'll name
the discovery
after you--
like they did
for Johnny Flyswatter
or Doug Reach-Around.
You permanently erased
Mom's memory?
Well, that's just
what the experts
at the lab say,
but there's no way
she could ever
forget me.
I mean, who could forget this?
Or this?
Or these?
Go on, kids,
give 'em a squeeze.
- It's not weird. I'm your dad.
- She's coming to.
One look at me,
and her memories of our love
will come flooding back.
Narc! Narc!
What? What?
Oh, God, is there
a bee on me?
Oh! Does it look Africanized?
Hey, baby.
Mom.
You idiot.
Why would you do that?
I thought it was
like the hiccups.
Okay, this is gonna be
harder than I thought.
Maybe we should
watch the video.
Has your loved one's memory
been irretrievably lost?
Hi. I'm forgettable actor
Bill Pullman.
You might not remember me
from such movies
as While You Were Sleeping
and Twister.
Wait. Was I in Twister?
No. No, that was Bill Paxton.
See? Memory can be
pretty tricky,
so that's why if you tell
your loved one
what's happened to them,
their brain will implode.
Good luck.
I'm Bill Pullman.
Oh, oh!
I was also in Independence D--
Jeff Daniels is right.
We have to maintain
the illusion that
your mother is still 18,
or it's going to get
very messy in there.
- So what do we do?
- Well, when she was 18,
she lived in West Langley,
so we need to get her
back into her old apartment.
Hayley, you can
keep an eye on her
by being her roommate.
What? I don't want to live
with Mom. Besides, I'm sure
someone lives there.
Good day, ma'am.
I'm a friend of your child.
He or she has asked me
to take you
- to a wonderful retirement home.
- How lovely.
- Right in here, ma'am.
- Oh, you're such a nice young--
Hello?
Am I supposed to vote now?
Please, Pete?
Lindsay won't go out with me
unless I find a date
for her friend.
She's not that bad-looking--
and besides, you're blind.
Come on. You went
to the Winter Ball
with that guy.
Yes, it was a guy.
Hello?
It's like there's not
a human being alive that
would go out with that girl.
Hello.
Who are you?
Uh, Hayley,
your new roommate.
- Oh, right.
I must have blacked out.
- Wait a second. You party?
Totally.
I need a shower.
Great Grizzly Adams.
Who fired the gardener?
Unbelievable.
How did she ever hook up
with a stiff like Dad?
I'll tell you how
she hooked up
with a stiff like me.
It was 20 years ago.
I didn't normally
pick up transients,
but for her,
I made an exception.
Her T-shirt said "Bad Girl,"
and her eyes said,
"Read the T-shirt."
My God, she was beautiful.
She was cold to me,
but I was hot for her--
which explained
the moderate temperature
in the car.
And then, fate scampered
across the road.
It was on a slow train
to Death City,
so I asked the conductor
if he could skip
the next few stops to make up--
-Oh, I shot it in the eye.
She said it was
the most compassionate act
she'd ever witnessed--
and I got to kill something.
It was a magical moment.
Well, there you go.
If you want Francine back,
just recreate that moment.
Roger, you're a genius!
That's how I'll bring
back her memory.
You just gave me
my Reach-Around.
Hey, old lady, party!
Wow.
This is Upstanding Conservative
to Dirty Liberal.
Drop point ahead.
Can you check the back tire?
The car is riding
kind of low.
What the hell?
You crazy bitch!
I love you!
You got me.
Game on.
- Need a ride?
- Thanks, pops.
Hey, are you, like, a narc?
I feel like I've seen you
somewhere before.
- Nope, first time
we've met, Francine.
- What?
- Nothing. Stick of
your favorite gum?
- What?
Nothing.
Look out!
Oh, sweet masked bandit
of nature,
let me put you
out of your misery.
Actually, I don't think
you hit it.
No, he's suffering--
pure agony.
Oh, my God!
Stop!
What, are you crazy?
Crazy with compassion.
Come on. Watch me
blow its head off.
Die! Die!
So that you may know peace.
Truck!
Stop the car,
you psychopath!
Oh, God!
Raccoon!
No, I'm never coming home.
Because you're
smothering me, Linda.
I was wrong.
I'll be home by 9:00.
Because I promised Derek
I'd meet him for a drink.
That's why 9:00!
And let the love
come flowing back.
Stay away from me!
♪ I'm all right ♪
♪ Nobody worry about me ♪
This is great.
By the way,
great call on this
Rasta disguise, Steve.
I'm "ganja" wear it
all the time.
Hey, Steve,
is this your friend?
Yeah. Lindsay,
this is Roger.
- Nice to meet you.
- Charmed.
- And this is Jewel.
- Your date.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
I'm out. I'm out.
Ew! Ew!
Hey, we had a deal.
Steve, she's so ugly.
So ugly.
Too bad.
I snuck you out
so you could be my wingman.
Now you can make nice
with Jewel,
- or you can go home
and rot in the attic.
- Uh, Steve,
"Jamaican" me crazy.
Sorry. I've had that one
loaded up all night.
Ahh. This picture
was taken on our honeymoon.
It's the only photo of Francine
where you can't see Vaj.
Ah, Vaj--
the little island boy
who served as our tour guide.
I see from her wristband
that you were at a Sandals
all-inclusive resort.
Hmm! Fancy.
Wait a minute.
I know just the thing
to trigger her memory.
Hayley, I thought
we were going to--
♪ Burning Man ♪
Sorry, but my mom decided
to throw a rager.
Besides, Jeff,
I never said I was going.
Party foul! Consume!
I had this boyfriend.
He was in an avalanche.
He survived three days
on melted snow,
and his grandfather
found him
because he had a dream
about the exact spot
where he was trapped.
Wow!
You had a boyfriend?
Oh, you have--
You have a little thing.
Oh, Roger, stop it.
- I don't have a hard time
looking at you.
- At me?
I can see past
your hydrocephalic head
and into your beautiful mind.
You're like Russell Crowe,
and I'm Jennifer Connelly.
Yeah. Yeah, you're
Jennifer Connelly.
Uncomfortable.
Get a room, you two.
Maybe we should lead
by example.
Or we could just
go back to your place
and make out.
Yeah, okay,
I understand.
Well, I had
a fun time anyway.
See you at school.
Huh?
Okay!
- Hayley, where's your mother?
- Last time I saw her,
she was in the kitchen,
- serving up body shots.
- What a hostess.
- She's not here.
- There's a note in frosting
on the fridge.
"Hayley-- Me and Jeff
went to Burning Man
together.
Rock on,
Francine."
My mother stole
my boyfriend!
Your boyfriend
stole my wife!
Let's get back at them
by dating each other.
Wait a minute.
Daddy didn't think that through.
The sandman's starting
to goose me.
Here. Have some coffee.
- Klaus!
- When you come home und pack,
I heard you and Hayley
talking about this Burning Man,
so I says to mein self,
"Road trip!"
Stan, by the way,
I could not hold mein pee-pee.
Honestly,
I only
went out with you
to get Jewel a date,
- but you're a lot less
of a dork than I thought.
- Stick around.
I think you'll find
I'm a lot less
of everything.
You can do
whatever you want to me.
Oh, so I can crate you
and hide you in that warehouse
at the end of Raiders?
So funny.
Kiss me, funny boy.
I know, I know.
Bad for the ozone.
Yeah, Burning Man
is great this year.
Ow! Ow!
Dad, we've been searching
all night.
Let's just start fresh
in the morning.
Francine? Francine?
I'm not just
saying this
to be clever--
I really feel
like a fish
out of water here.
What's the deal
with the flower?
On our wedding day,
I placed this yellow flower
in your mom's white bouquet.
It symbolized
her sunshine brightening
my otherwise cloudy world.
Dad, I've never seen
this side of you.
It's so sweet.
Well, if you tell anybody
I'll kill you.
Ah. I'm serious.
I will kill you.
I will reach into your chest,
pull out your beating heart,
and eat it--
all of it, every last bit.
Well, sweet dreams, angel.
I-I-It's not you.
It's the timing,
you know?
I just got out
of a bad relationship.
You're lying.
I'm a loser.
Don't be like that.
You're not a loser.
Think how pretty you make
people look by contrast.
That's a gift.
Gotcha!
Oh, my God!
You're an alien!
Lindsay! Lindsay!
Roger is an ali--
- Roger!
- She was all over me,
and my wig fell off,
and we'd be in big trouble.
Did you see
where they went?
- Who?
- The black guys who did this.
Aah! Mr. Smith!
- Where's my wife?
- She ditched me
as soon as we got here.
I just ran away with her
to get a rise out of Hayley.
- Please don't kill me!
Let me get this straight.
You ran away with my
memory-erased mother
to a pagan festival
- just to get my attention?
- Did it work?
Did it ever!
Mmm!
You know, we're
about to go on tour
to Bangkok and Amsterdam,
and this hot piece
of mama's comin' with us.
I am ripped off my ass!
Francine!
- You again?
- Look what I have.
Remember. Please remember.
How long till it kicks in?
Oh, Francine, for God's sake,
we're married.
You love me.
Look, you're a stiff.
I could never fall in love
with a suit like you.
A suit like me?
Well then,
I'll get rid of the suit.
Huh? Huh?
Look at me.
Nothing stiff here.
Hey, it's never gonna
happen with us.
Never!
Because hang-gliding
makes me feel alive,
Linda, okay?
Francine!
Don't worry. I'm leaving.
I just wanted you to be safe.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me,
and I took it for granted.
I'm just happy that--
Uh, that I got the privilege
to be with you
for the time that I did.
Okay, my shoes are full.
I better go now.
I love you, Francine.
It's a little late,
but happy anniversary.
Remember.
- Stan?
- Francine?
Stan, it was so weird.
And I was alone
and confused.
And there was this raccoon,
and I knew who I was again.
Oh, Francine, thank God.
- I love you.
- I love you too, Stan.
That was gross.
I still love you.
Thanks for looking after me.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be.
You were fun.
In fact, you were cool.
Oh. Hey, funny story.
A little bit longer,
and their last 24 hours
will be completely forgotten.
- Oh, thank God.
- You are not
off the hook, mister.
I am deeply
disappointed in you.
- Dad, I was with this one.
- Oh. Well, outstanding.
Bye! Have a beautiful time.