Stop!
Get them!
THANKS!
Five billion with
nonsequential serial numbers.
It's a shower of money!
Ya-hoo!
Whoa! Yow, that's hot stuff.
Come on. Bury me in it.
What's wrong, Lupin?
- Dump it.
- What?
This is counterfeit.
Excellent quality too.
All this?
No way. We heisted this
from the vault of the national casino.
- Goat bills.
- Goat bills?
You mean
the legendary counterfeits?
So they've made their way
into the national casinos now.
Jigen! I've decided
what our next job will be.
Why don't we have a little
pre-victory celebration?
Darn it! Darn it! Darn it!
I want to go with you
Searching for happiness
No matter how hard the road
or how the night may grow cold
I just want to wander on with you
Who else is there to comfort and hold
This lonely traveler
when their heart grows cold?
Who else but you can make
All my dreams come true?
Like a raging fire
My love for you burns
All I want is for you
to know how I feel
Make me your prisoner
and never let go
The Duchy of Cagliostro.
Never heard of it.
Population: 3500.
The world's smallest member
state of the United Nations.
And this is the source
of the Goat bills, huh?
It's a famous legend
in the underworld.
This is the black hole of
the counterfeiting world.
Black hole?
No one who's gone in looking
around here has ever come back.
Oh, sounds scary.
I'm so scared I need a nap.
Hey!
Jeez!
This spare's totally bald.
Peaceful, isn't it?
- What the—
- Get in!
- Which are we helping?
-The girl!
Typical.
- Get the tires.
- Gotcha.
Damn!
That's no ordinary car.
Yow! Well, this is
sure getting exciting.
Going up!
Got 'em!
This time I won't use
an ordinary bullet.
All right!
She's fainted.
- It's coming apart.
- Take the wheel.
- No, let me go!
- Hey, don't. It's dangerous!
Down! Look down!
Yeah, that's better.
Just stay like that.
Hello?
Forgive me.
Hey, Lupin.
- Jeez, what happened to you?
- Where's my bride?
Damn it!
Who are those guys and
why are they after that girl?
- It's a ring, isn't it?
- Funny, I could swear I've-
What's wrong?
When you saw that ring, you suddenly
got a weird look in your eyes.
Hey, Lupin.
What do we want at this old castle?
The same crest
that was on the ring. Lupin?
Abandoned,
but not that long ago, either.
Fire, huh?
- Who's there?
- Just some passers-by.
- Tourists?
- You could say that.
I was under the impression that
this was the grand duke's palace, but—
It still is, and it's no place for
strangers to be wandering around in.
This is the grand duke's palace?
It's just a burnt-out shell.
There was a fire seven years ago.
The duke and his wife
were lost in it.
Since then, the palace
has been left to go to ruin.
That's strange. The grand duke
was like your king, right?
Does that mean
you don't have a king now?
There's a regent. They say
there's nothing to be concerned about.
- Now hurry up and leave.
- Right.
Hey, Lupin!
She's grown.
- Something wrong?
- Quit playing dumb.
Pulling that "I'm a cool,
suffering loner" act, right?
- Now talk!
- No. No!
- Gonna talk?
-I talk!
The castle of
Count Cagliostro, the regent.
Look over there.
No, down a little more.
Past the aqueduct.
That boat from before!
The bride's in that castle.
There's the floodgate over there.
It hasn't changed at all.
You've broken
into that castle before?
That was more than 10 years ago.
I was looking for the secret
of the Goat bills.
I was still a young punk,
just starting out.
And? What happened?
I got my butt royally kicked!
Had to run away with
my tail between my legs.
I didn't think
they used autogyros anymore.
It's the count.
C'mon. Let's find a room
for the night.
Hey!
- You were careless, Jodo.
- I beg your pardon, My Lord.
It happened while they were
fitting the bridal gown.
She escaped when the men
left her alone in the room.
She's in the north tower now?
Yes, My Lord.
She's been heavily sedated.
- Foreigners?
- Yes, Lord.
Two men.
They helped her to escape.
Find them
and take care of them.
The ring's gone.
Summon Jodo!
This inscription's in Capran,
a dead language.
Capran?
"When light and shadow are joined
once more, it shall be restored."
AD 1517.
The date's in Roman numerals.
So that ring's 400 years old.
- Sorry for the wait.
- Looks great!
What is it
that you are looking at?
Oh, nothing.
Just this old ring I found.
I was wondering
if it was worth anything.
Oh, it's pretty!
That's Lady Clarisse's crest.
Clarisse?
Look, that girl.
See that photo?
It was taken when she was a child.
She just came back
from the convent yesterday.
- I'll bet she's really beautiful now.
- Convent?
Don't you know about it?
I thought you both were here to see
Lady Clarisse marry the count.
Oh, I see. No wonder why
there are so many tourists here.
Still, I feel sorry for Lady Clarisse.
The count's known for
being a real playboy.
Oh, really? Just like me.
Say, are you busy tonight?
One of the count's men.
His eyes lit up
when he saw that ring.
Just having the bride isn't enough.
They want the ring too, right?
Oh, no, you don't!
You knew that girl this afternoon was
the grand duke's daughter, didn't you?
Oh, didn't I mention that?
"When light and shadow are joined
once more, it shall be restored," huh?
Do you think it's a treasure
that'll be restored?
Oh-ho!
The gang's all here!
Why, you—
My Magnum has no effect!
These guys are professional killers.
Move it!
They had me worried for a while.
They actually launched
a full-scale attack on us.
There's more to this case
than meets the eye.
Things are really gettin'
interesting now.
This batch isn't very well made.
The quality's just
getting worse, isn't it?
Forgive me, sir.
But it's unavoidable if we continue
to mass-produce them like we are.
Redo them. However,
we can't miss our delivery date.
- Yes, sir.
- Who's there?
Jodo, My Lord.
For the first time ever, I've failed you.
The rats escaped the trap.
Jodo, what's that paper
you have on your back?
What the—
When did he—
Lupin!
It's Lupin's calling card.
- Read it.
- Yes, My Lord, But—
Just do it.
Yes, Lord.
"To the lecherous and greedy count.
I shall take your bride.
The day I will come is near."
Signed, Lupin the Third.
It's good news, Jodo.
Why don't we wait for this man
Lupin to come to us?
Hi, there.
You sure came quick.
What's the job?
Goemon's arrived.
So has someone else.
Take a look.
What?
That's a Japanese police car.
- It's Zenigata.
- What?
Everybody out!
Form up!
And now the players
are all in place.
Ow, hot! Hot!
Forgive me
for interrupting your meal.
I am Zenigata of Interpol.
We've received a report that you've
gotten one of Lupin's calling cards.
You no doubt mean the grandson
of that common thief, Arsene Lupin.
Is Interpol in the habit of interrupting
peoples' breakfasts for such matters?
Your Excellency,
you shouldn't make light of Lupin.
If he says he's coming,
then he's definitely coming.
Your wedding is in five days.
Until then, please allow
my men to guard this castle.
We have police in this country too.
Although we have the refinement
to refer to them as the "royal guard."
You summoned me, My Lord?
Gustav, cooperate
with our Japanese guest.
- You may leave.
- Yes, sir!
Your Excellency,
I have one more question.
Will you please tell me why
Lupin would be after your bride?
Who knows?
Isn't finding that out your job?
If you'll excuse me.
Is it wise to have that man
inside the castle, My Lord?
It doesn't matter. I have many
friends in Interpol as well.
They'll be leaving soon.
Good ol' Zenigata.
The archetypical Japanese man.
Totally devoted to his work.
What's that over there?
Don't go any further.
- What?
- Observe.
If you don't wish to die,
don't wander around.
Tell your men that too.
Inspector. I'm picking up
anti-personnel radar here too.
I've got a bad feeling
about this castle.
There are too many security systems
here for a normal man to have.
A woman?
Oh, no!
Don't say you're bailing on us.
Yeah, a girl's involved,
but that's not the whole story.
You're saying that ring has
something to do with it?
We'll find that out when we grab the
girl from that dirty old man, the count.
Anyway, my Magnum
may not have worked on them...
but between your sword
and this anti-tank rifle—
Hey, there, Lupin.
- You figured out a way in yet?
- Nope.
That place is incredible.
A nest of lasers and radar.
I see.
We may even need a tank.
That's why you called in
Zenigata, right?
What? Is that true, Lupin?
Exactly!
You've got good intuition.
Use poison to fight poison, eh?
This is Cagliostro Castle.
This is where we are.
This Roman aqueduct here
is still in use.
It's the only way in.
The aqueduct brings water from
this lake into the castle.
I get it. And there won't be
any lasers in the water, right?
Goemon. Stay on watch here.
Careful. There's a hole.
The first obstacle, huh?
Let's go.
Lupin!
Whew! This must be the
machinery room for the clock.
I wonder if that SOB
actually made it.
What's that windmill for?
Gustav said they use it
to bring water up into the castle.
- And where does the water come out?
- A fountain on the upper cannon deck.
- Come on!
- Yes, sir!
Inspector!
We just received orders from
Paris HQ, "Pull out at once."
What? That's ridiculous!
I'll see about that.
What? But we got a warning
that Lupin was coming, so—
The count?
I'm a cop, not a court jester!
I don't care if he likes us here or not—
Hello? Hello?
Oh, for the love of—
I'll talk to the count about this.
Show me to the count.
I need to see the count at once.
Didn't you hear me?
Let me through!
Stop it.
Only trusted people are
allowed past this point.
What? Are you saying
Interpol officers can't be trusted?
I believe you've received
orders to pull out.
I must ask you to leave.
How did you know about that?
We won't need any of you Orientals
to help us with Lupin. Now go.
Oh, really? I see.
We're pulling out for now.
Was I just here?
- What?
- You idiot! That was Lupin!
He disguised himself as me
so he could sneak in here!
Couldn't a muscle-bound idiot
like you see through that getup?
Why, that— Follow me!
Don't let Lupin get away!
Hold it!
Lupin?
Cut it out! It's Lupin!
Save the Inspector!
Charge!
Wow, that's wild.
Cut it out! He's Lupin!
Darn it!
Lupin!
Looks like we caught someone.
That fool. He should have left
as soon as he could.
- The guards are gone.
- Gustav!
What's he doing,
leaving his post?
- You stay here.
- Yes, sir!
Sorry, Old Man.
You fool!
Stop this uproar at once!
Don't you understand?
Lupin did this to sneak in.
Why, that—
Let go. Let go of me!
So that devil Lupin
made it in after all.
I have no excuse, My Lord.
Tell the inspector's men that
he went home ahead of them.
It's not unheard of for people
to vanish while traveling, is it?
Don't move.
- Good evening, Fujiko.
- Lupin!
There's nothing lovelier than a woman
who's absorbed in her work.
So you made it in this far.
That's all you say after a year apart?
You wound me, my dear.
And after I looked all over for you.
Lupin, you're looking
for the bride, aren't you?
Oh, you know about that?
I'll tell you where she is, but do you
promise to not interfere with my job?
I won't!
I'd never dream of it.
I wonder about that.
She's being held
at the top of the north tower.
Although it's impossible to get into.
Lupin?
Damn, they've really got her
locked up in a hell of a place.
- Who's there?
- A thief.
A thief?
Good evening, Miss Bride.
You! You're the man who—
You forgot something.
You came here just for this?
But if the count finds you,
you'll be killed.
No matter. To hunt and be hunted
is the nature of being a thief.
I will leave once
I've finished my job.
Your job?
I wish I had something to give you,
but I'm a prisoner.
Here. Take this.
What I seek is a treasure...
which an evil sorcerer
has locked inside a high tower.
Will you allow this humble thief
to please steal it away?
You mean me?
Like I save precious gems which
have been locked away in a vault...
I have come to take a girl
forced to be a bride against her will...
and set her free
in the green fields outside.
This all goes with being a thief.
You've come to set me free?
Thank you.
I appreciate what you're doing.
But you don't know the terrible
secrets of the Cagliostro family.
Please just leave me and go.
Oh, how can this be?
The girl believes in the
power of the evil sorcerer...
yet she doesn't believe
in the power of the thief.
Oh, if only she'd believe in him...
the thief would be able
to fly through the air!
He would be able drink
all the water in the lake!
For now,
this is the best I can do.
Mr. Thief!
Hey!
Treat the lady gently, okay?
Thank you so much for
returning the ring, my dear Lupin.
Well, I appreciate
this warm welcome, Count.
I'm afraid
you're going to disappear now.
But can you really
make me vanish so easily?
Stop it!
Don't hurt that man!
I'll be fine, Miss. Remember,
believe in the power of the thief.
Mr. Thief!
Yup, I'm right here.
I'll be back soon.
Well, now,
what game shall we play?
It would be simple
to just rip you apart.
However, I don't want
my bride's room to be stained...
by the blood of a common thief.
I'll make you regret
that you ever said that.
Enough of your insolence.
That hole leads to a hell
not one person has ever escaped from.
That pretty face has already
lured a man to his doom.
You can't deny the
Cagliostro blood inside of you.
You'll make
a most fitting wife for me.
Murderer!
You aren't human.
You're right.
My hands have blood on them
as do your own.
The family of the count has always served
in the shadow of the grand duke's.
Performing its plots and assassinations.
Supporting this country.
Let me go!
You're disgusting.
Don't pretend you don't know.
You, too, are a Cagliostro.
Within your body, like mine,
flows the ancient blood of the Goat.
Clarisse, for 400 years,
light has been separated from shadow...
but now the two houses of
Cagliostro will be reunited.
Look.
When the gold goat that
marks my house is joined...
with the silver goat
of your house...
the treasure hidden by our ancestors
will be restored.
I heard him!
- He's marrying her to get the treasure.
- It's him!
The counterfeiting count.
Everything he says or does is fake!
That girl happens to be
a sweet, wonderful person.
- Mr. Thief?
- Yup! I'm just fine.
Since the girl believed in me,
I was able to fly through the air.
Mr. Thief is coming
to steal you away.
- Wait for me, okay?
- Yes.
Damn it, it's the ring!
Give me that.
Okay, Count, listen up!
I've got the real ring.
If you lay one finger on that girl,
your precious ring will end up like this!
It's a fake!
Why, you—
You really do
treat people like crap!
- Did he fall?
- Probably.
Make sure.
Down there
isn't a place for the living.
If we leave him alone,
he'll surely die.
- He still has the ring.
- As you wish, My Lord.
Just wait.
I'll bring your dear thief
back to you in pieces!
Killing and killing for 400 years.
Rest in peace, all of you.
MARCH 14, 1904.
HERE GENNOSUKE KAWAKAMI.
SPY FOR THE JAPANESE ARMY,
MET HIS END. AVENGE ME.
Lupin!
Why, you—
Come along quietly!
Old Man, you're still alive.
Tell me. Where's the exit?
How did you get in here?
I fell in, same as you.
You look like you've been
walking around for a long time.
Shut up!
I won't take pity from a thief.
Well, we may as well relax.
There's no way out of here.
'Scuse me, pal.
Hey, Old Man, you got a light?
Lupin, what's with all these bodies?
I doubt this is a graveyard.
Take a look at that wall.
Th-This is—
Rest in peace.
I thought there was something
suspicious about this castle...
but what sort of secret is worth
this much trouble to hide?
Hey, Lupin.
Is that what you're after here?
That's what Fujiko's after.
I hope she doesn't end up
like these bodies in here.
Anyway, running around
in a panic won't help us.
Good night, Old Man.
It's cold!
Man, look how long it's been.
How do things look?
Still no movement.
Then I guess we just wait.
They're taking too long.
Mr. Jodo!
They've found it!
Heave-ho!
Curse you, Lupin!
These are coffins.
What is all this?
These are Japanese 10,000 yen bills.
Looks like this all is.
These are really well-made.
Hey, Old Man, look!
West German 1,000 mark bills.
Pounds. Dollars.
Francs. Rubles. Rupees.
Pesos. Crowns. Lira.
They've even got won!
It's the whole world in here.
They're making counterfeits.
Lupin, is this the castle's secret?
Exactly. This is the
source of the counterfeits...
that were supposedly better
than the originals: the Goat bills.
The counterfeit money
which inevitably moved...
in the shadow of the upheavals
of medieval Europe.
It caused the collapse
of the Bourbon dynasty...
became Napoleon's
source of funding...
and eventually triggered
the world bank panic of 1927.
Appearing
on the backstage of history...
as the star of the black hole:
the Goat bills.
Of all the people who came here
looking for their source...
not a single one of them
ever returned.
I've heard rumors about this...
but who'd ever believe an
independent nation was running it?
What're you gonna do,
Old Man?
After seeing this,
there's no going back.
I know!
It makes my cop's blood burn.
How about a truce
until we get out of here?
Very well, but I won't
help you steal anything.
And after we're out of here,
I swear I'll arrest you.
It's settled, then.
Let's shake on it.
- I won't be corrupted.
- Corrupted?
- Miss Fujiko.
- The time's come to say good bye.
Who are you?
To all appearances,
I'm the one woman...
who is employed here
in the castle as your servant.
But in reality, I'm a lady spy who's
looking for this castle's secret.
I was hoping to stay a little longer,
but now Lupin's come.
Everything's fallen apart,
so I'm leaving.
You know that man?
Only too well.
Sometimes we're allies,
at others we're enemies.
Occasionally, we're even lovers.
The guy's a natural born lady-killer.
Watch your step around him.
He walked out on you?
Oh, hardly.
I walked out on him.
There's smoke coming
from the trapdoor.
Afire?
It's coming from underground.
- Movement.
- He's started.
Fire! Fire!
Trouble! A fire's started in
the underground printing plant.
- What? Put it out at once!
- Yes, My Lord.
Close that blasted door!
The rest of you, go, too.
Damn you, Jodo.
Have you failed me again?
Hurry up, Old Man!
Our guests will be here soon.
Evidence. I need evidence!
Curse you, Lupin!
Look for them!
They may still be in here.
Have no fear! Forward!
It's Lupin. After him!
You put out the fire.
The chapel!
- Mr. Thief!
- Lupin. And Zenigata?
They're trying to steal
the autogyro!
- You fool!
-You can punish me later.
They're trying to take
Lady Clarisse. Hurry!
Hurry up!
Halt!
Why, you—
Never mess with Tokyo Metro!
Old Man, get on!
So long!
Old Man, we have to
make a little detour.
I will not cooperate
in a kidnapping for ransom.
This isn't business.
They're coming this way.
Bulletproof glass!
We can't open it.
Please just leave me!
- Old Man, take over, would you?
- What? Lupin, wait!
I can't fly this thing!
- Clarisse?
- Mr. Thief!
Your ride's here.
Fujiko, throw me a rope!
Quit bossing me around!
Miss Fujiko!
Hurry!
- Mr. Thief!
- Okay, you're safe now.
Old Man! This way!
What do you think
I'm trying to do, you idiot?
Okay, that's it!
Lupin!
Don't move,
you meddling woman!
Fujiko, I'll take my time
interrogating you later.
-Jodo, finish Lupin off.
- Yes, sir.
No! Don't shoot!
If you kill him,
you'll kill me too.
Fire.
I admire your devotion, Clarisse.
Get the ring back
and come here.
Become my wife
and I will let Lupin live.
Or you can both die here together.
The choice is yours.
Mr. Thief, give me the ring.
No, Clarisse. Don't do it.
Under his collar.
Lupin always hides things there.
Darn it, Fujiko!
I have the ring.
Let this man and Fujiko go,
or I'll throw it into the lake.
You have my word.
Now put the ring on and come here.
- Shall I shoot?
- Wait until we have the ring.
Lupin!
Shoot!
Don't let them escape!
Liar!
You said you'd let them go.
Let them go after they've seen
the underground plant?
At last, it's mine.
Lupin, you owe me for today.
See you.
We didn't even get to join in,
and we're already pulling out!
Oh, it's no use.
Jump for it!
Once again,
I cut a worthless object.
Lupin! Don't you dare die
before I get to arrest you!
Whatever we do,
it'll mean trouble.
It's some sort of plot.
Give the order for us to go in!
Look how clear all this evidence is.
I saw it myself.
The latest printing equipment,
all over the room like—
We understand that!
This is a high-level
political problem...
and Interpol's jurisdiction is
limited to international crime.
Chief, the crime is clear!
You don't understand.
The one committing it is an independent
member of the United Nations.
Even Interpol can't conduct
a forcible criminal investigation.
Besides that,
the situation isn't in our favor at all.
Have you seen the pictures on the
front pages of the world's newspapers?
"Count bravely defends his bride!
Lupin's attempt to kidnap
Princess Clarisse fails!"
Along with reports of a henchman
disguised as Zenigata.
That was really me!
Wasn't that a bit rash
for an officer in your position?
The truth has to be told!
The problem is whether
world opinion will believe you.
There's no way we can win.
The count has many friends among
the Western governments, does he not?
The truth may cause trouble
for a lot of nations.
Yes, considering the evidence
that these mass-produced...
counterfeit dollars were
ordered by a certain country!
And these counterfeit rubles
weren't ordered by the CIA?
Gentlemen, please!
You will not bring your countries'
quarrels into these chambers!
The only way to deal with this...
is for each country to
come up with its own solution!
Inspector,
we're ready to move out.
We can leave for Cagliostro
at any time.
We won't be moving out.
As soon as they choose my replacement,
we'll be off the Lupin case.
All of you,
get ready to go home.
It's me.
- Food.
- Thanks.
- How is he?
- His fever seems to have dropped.
Thanks to the treatment
you gave him.
If you want to thank anyone,
thank the dog.
That old dog doesn't like anyone,
but he won't leave that man's side.
If not for that,
I never would have hidden you here.
Hello, Karl.
He's awake.
Lupin, how do you feel?
Jigen. Goemon.
It's been a while.
A while?
What's he talking about?
I think his wounds have
temporarily confused his memory.
Karl, why aren't you
with your owner today?
How do you know
that dog's name?
The only other person besides me
who knows it's Karl is Princess Clarisse.
Clarisse?
So your owner's name is Clarisse.
Clarisse...
Lupin?
Jigen! How many days?
How many days has it been?
Uh, three.
What? That means
the wedding's tomorrow.
I have to—
Don't push yourself.
You'll reopen your wounds.
Food. Bring me food.
Food?
Some porridge, maybe?
I've lost a lot of blood.
Anything'll do. Bring me a feast.
Well, that's easy
for you to say, but—
I'll see what I can do.
You damn fool!
Don't eat so fast.
Your body can't take that much.
Shut up! Gimme 12 hours
and I'll be as fit as a jet plane!
See? I told you so.
Need a wash basin?
What?
He says now he'll sleep.
I see.
He did it for Princess Clarisse.
But now that
Lupin's hurt this badly—
You seem to be connected with
Miss Clarisse from the past, old man.
I tended the palace gardens.
Princess Clarisse
loved plants as a child.
When her family died and
she was sent off to the convent...
she gave me this dog.
He must have smelled the
princess's scent on Lupin's body.
But, then, how could he have
known the dog's name?
I dunno. Lupin can be charmed
by women really easily, but—
- It wasn't like that.
- What, you're awake?
It happened 10 years ago.
I was a young hotshot kid
who was just starting out on his own.
I acted like an idiot.
To top it all off,
I decided to go after the Goat bills.
Somehow, I made it to the shore,
but I could move no further.
Karl? What's wrong, Karl?
I thought my number
had finally come up.
Water.
As her trembling hands
gave me the water...
I noticed a ring on her finger,
sparkling in the light.
I'm ashamed to say this...
but until I saw the ring again,
I'd forgotten completely about it.
That was Fujiko's bike.
It's a clipping from today's paper.
"An archbishop is coming from
the Vatican tomorrow morning...
to perform the wedding."
I'm off the case!
Fujiko?
What? Lupin's gonna hit
the wedding? Really?
If you're after Lupin, your superiors
won't mind your going in there, right?
That's right!
That's how we'll play it.
We're in a hurry. Move!
Forget it.
Everything past here is all jammed up.
There was a landslide
seven kilometers up the road.
Isn't there some other road?
We're going to be late.
Would you by any chance
be the archbishop?
Ah, yes, you are.
Would you please bless this lamb?
Say, you're a local, right?
There any other roads to Cagliostro?
If you don't mind a country road,
there's one that way.
We're saved!
Can you show us the way?
C'mon, hop in.
Yes.
Anything for the archbishop.
C'mon, push! One more hill
and we're in Cagliostro.
We've gotta get there
by nightfall.
Is it really such a good idea
to have TV cameras in here?
His Excellency wishes
to show the world...
that this is a proper
and legal marriage.
The archbishop has arrived.
Do you suppose
Lupin will come?
My Shadows are guarding the bride.
All you need worry about
is guarding the front gate.
The time has come
for light and shadow to be united.
Come, Clarisse.
Bring forward the proof...
that these are truly noble members
of the ancient bloodline of Cagliostro.
In accordance to the old custom...
you shall exchange rings
and recite your vows.
Clarisse d' Cagliostro, daughter
of the Grand Duke of Cagliostro...
do you have no objection
to this marriage?
Silence will be taken as agreement.
God's blessing upon you.
I object!
This wedding is soiled
by the count's desires.
- A curse!
- Don't panic.
The meddlers have simply
made their appearance.
In the name of the dead
who lie beneath this castle...
I have come to take your bride.
- We can't have the wedding now.
- Step back.
This will make fine entertainment.
Clarisse, I've come for you.
Ghosts!
This is terrible, ladies and gentlemen.
It's Lupin! Lupin has appeared.
Stop the broadcast.
- What are you doing?
- Move out!
Clarisse! Clarisse!
Poor girl.
They've drugged you, haven't they?
The damned count.
He didn't want you able to speak.
- Mr. Thief!
- No, dear. Stay back.
You were a fool, Lupin.
Finish the others!
Clarisse.
Don't cry, Clarisse.
I'm coming for you now.
Money?
Do you like my present, Count?
Excellency!
They're the counterfeit bills you made.
Take it as payment for the rings.
Damn him! Find him!
He's somewhere in here.
Told you I'd get 'em.
You— Lupin?
Mr. Thief!
How dare you make a fool of me!
Cool off, O pedophiliac count!
Watch out before you get burned.
Lupin!
Sorry for the delay,
ladies and gentlemen.
We'll resume our broadcast now.
The wedding ceremony is in an uproar!
- Well, if you'll excuse me.
- Die!
After them!
Don't let them escape!
Lupin's escaped.
The count is following him in a rage.
And here come the police!
Lupin's under the altar.
All together! Charge!
Zenigata's men are opening
a path to the altar.
And here come the royal guards
with Captain Gustav in the lead.
Rear guard, deploy!
Stand your ground!
Justice is on our side.
This is a really fierce fight, folks!
What could be under the altar?
It's a stairway!
There's a hole leading underground.
Could Lupin be in that hole?
Let's take a camera in and find out.
Curse you, Lupin!
-Lupin!
- What's that idiot doing?
He's disobeying orders.
Recall him!
This is a satellite broadcast.
It's too late.
What can this be?
Why, it looks just
like the National Mint!
And what do I see over there?
Good grief! Japanese money!
It must be counterfeit.
- Lord, what a bad actor.
- What a terrible discovery!
Look. Counterfeit money
from all over the world.
I came in after Lupin and
found this terrible crime.
What should I do?
First of all,
let's get you out of the castle.
Go to it, Jigen. Goemon.
Leave this to us.
we'll hold 'em off here.
Please be careful.
And you, Sir Jigen.
Please be sure
to come back from this alive.
I'll never forget your kindness.
You'd better go.
Clarisse, hurry.
Coming!
SirJigen, huh?
She's lovely.
Let's do some damage.
This sword you face tonight
is like no other.
Curse you, Lupin.
You haven't won yet.
We'll take care of the castle,
My Lord.
- Do your wounds hurt?
- Nah, they were just scratches.
Now, let's get across this.
Two goats facing each other.
When you put them together,
there's an inscription in Capran.
Light and shadow—
It's too worn. I can't read it.
"When light and
shadow are joined...
face the Goat on high
who faces the sun...
and tells time
and place me in its eyes."
They're old words that have been
passed down through my family.
Are they any help?
Indeed, they are.
The mystery is solved.
The count!
C'mon, this way.
They slipped into the clock tower
machinery room. Moor the boat.
There they are.
He's here.
Forget this.
Turn off the lasers. Fools!
Do they think they can leave here?
- Scared?
Good girl. Let's go!
Don't let 'em go!
Don't look!
We can't go this way.
You men use the stairs.
Stay here.
I'm going to block the entrance.
- Be careful!
- I'll be right back.
There he is!
Mr. Thief! Behind you!
Hiya, Count!
You little rat. I'll skewer you.
Time for the finale, Count.
One more time!
Hey, Caggy!
Come and get me.
Mr. Thief!
I'll finish you off first.
Clarisse, run!
I'll be right there!
And just how far
can you run, Clarisse?
Well, now what?
Can't you run any further?
The Cagliostro bloodline ends here.
Die, Clarisse.
Wait, Count!
I'll make a deal.
Too late.
Watch as I kill the girl.
Listen to me!
I'll tell you
the secret of the rings.
The treasure will be yours
to do with as you please.
But let the girl go.
Set her free.
Look. You see the goat crest
on the clock face?
That's the goat which
faces the sun and tells time.
There's a hole
in each eye for the rings.
I'll give you the rings.
However, if you kill the girl,
I'll throw them in the lake...
and then I'll kill you.
That's far enough, thank you.
Send Clarisse inside.
All right. I see.
Lupin. I still had one ace
up my sleeve to play.
Come on.
They're real, all right.
I have the rings.
And now I'll pay you
for solving the mystery.
Let me go!
Clarisse!
The clock tower!
Excellency...
What's happening?
Cagliostro is finished.
Kill me.
I don't take lives without reason.
- Mr. Thief?
- Can you stand? Look.
The hidden treasure.
A Roman city,
hidden at the bottom of the lake.
When the Romans were
driven from here...
they flooded the city
with the floodgate.
Your ancestors secretly inherited it.
This is a treasure for all mankind.
Too big for my pocket anyway.
Interpol finally got off its fat butt.
Are you going to leave now?
Well, there are some very
scary men coming, you see.
Take me with you.
I know I can't be a thief now,
but I can learn!
I—
Please, I want to go with you.
Clarisse.
Don't be ridiculous.
You want to go back
into the darkness again?
You've finally made it out
into the sunlight, haven't you?
Listen, your whole life
is starting now.
You shouldn't want to turn into
a terrible person like me.
Oh, yeah! if you ever need help,
just let me know.
I'll come running from
anywhere on Earth to save you.
Karl!
Oh, Karl!
- Princess Clarisse!
- It's you!
- Mr. Thief!
- Until next time.
Hiya, Princess!
Mr. Thief!
Stay well, Clarisse. Adieu!
Thank you!
Good bye, all of you!
Adieu! Adieu!
Blast it!
I was one step behind him.
Lupin managed to steal
something again.
No, he didn't steal anything.
All he did was fight for me.
No, he stole
something quite precious.
Your heart.
Yes.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Follow Lupin! Follow him
to the ends of the Earth!
They all seem like such nice people.
I feel as though
I know that man from long ago.
Lupin, someday—
I know we'll meet again someday.
She's a nice kid.
You could stay if you want.
Oh? Fujiko!
Lupin!
Take a look at what I scored.
Hey!
The counterfeit printing plates!
- Can we be friends?
- See you!
Hey, wait! Wait for me!
It's the Old Man again.
Lupin!
You won't escape this time.