TOHO
TOHO COMPANY LTD.
A TOKYO MOVIE SHINSHA PRODUCTION
Son of a bitch!
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Billions of bucks with unmarked serials!
We're rich bastards! Ya-hee!
Hey, don't drown me in it!
I've got a lot of
spending to do before I die!
If you don't kill us
with your driving first!
What's wrong, Lupin?
It's fake.
Huh?
This stuff is counterfeit.
Top quality too.
You're kidding!
They're bogus?
Nah, you're just pulling my chain!
These look real to me!
They're Goat bills.
No way!
You mean the legendary forgeries?
We've ripped off funny money
from the national casino.
Jigen! I've picked out our next job.
Let's have a pre-victory celebration!
Hee hee! So much for
an early retirement!
Ehh, what the hell!
Who wants to sit around getting fat
on fine wine and gourmet food
with beautiful women in some
lush tropical setting anyway!
Lupin the Third
The Castle of Cagliostro
Producer
Tetsuo Katayama
Executive Producer
Yutaka Fujioka
Original Story
Monkey Punch
(Serialized in Weekly Manga Action • Published by Futabasha)
Screenplay
Hayao
Miyazaki
Haruya
Yamazaki
Searching out happiness
Music
Yuji Ohno
Theme Song
The Treasure of
the Flame
(Columbia
Records)
Lyrics
Jun
Hashimoto
Music
Yuji
Ohno
Voice
BOBBY
Music Selection
Seiji Suzuki
Is how I want to make my way
Director of Animation
Yasuo Ohtsuka
Art
Shichiro
Kobayashi
Photography
Hirokata
Takahashi
Recording
Satoshi
Kato
Editing
Yoshihisa
Tsurubuchi
Even thorny paths and freezing cold nights
Key Animation
Masako Shinohara
Kazuhide
Tomonaga
Hideo
Kawachi
Nobuo
Tomizawa
Tsukasa
Tannai
Shojuro
Yamauchi
Kouji
Maruyama
Johji
Manabe
Atsuko
Tanaka
Nobumasa
Shinkawa
I want to traverse, the two of us together
In-Between Animation
Yasunao
Aoki
Miwako
Ohsato
Masami
Ozaki
Masanori
Ono
Kyoko
Kawanaka
Ryoko
Kashiwada
Yumiko
Kumamoto
Yayoi
Kobayashi
Junko
Kojima
Hideyo
Sano
Yoko
Sakurai
Junko
Shimozaki
Yoshiko
Shimazu
Harumi
Shibata
Yoshihiro
Shida
Yukio
Suzuki
Atsuko
Tanabe
Miwako
Takagi
Junko
Tsutsumi
Yoko
Tsukada
Yoshinobu
Michihata
Hitoshi
Nanba
Shunsuke
Harada
Masako
Hayashi
Sachiko
Hamada
Masayo
Hamahata
Saburo
Hashimoto
Kumiko
Hirama
Toshiyuki
Hiruma
Kazuko
Fujimura
Kaoru
Honda
Rieko
Mochizuki
Yoko
Yoshimura
AJIADO
OH
Pro
The bleak heart of the traveler
Backgrounds
Kobayashi Production
Masashi
Aoki
Hiroshi
Ohno
Toshiharu
Mizutani
Miyuki
Kudo
Tsutomu
Ishigaki
Satoshi
Matsuoka
Hiromasa
Ogura
Jinzaburo
Kaiho
Yumiko
Hayashi
Yuko
Fujie
Telecom
Nizo Yamamoto
Who will be there to embrace it?
Photography
Takahashi Production
Masao
Miyauchi
Nobuhisa
Takahashi
Tadashi
Hosono
Keizo
Saito
Katsumi
Ohta
Akio
Hirayama
Yoshinori
Nakamura
Takuo
Suzuki
Who will make those dreams come true?
Finishing
Studio Korumi
Kunitoshi
Okajima
Shaft
Noriko Kato
Easy
World
Naoya
Hayashi
Studio
Taj
Noriko
Shiotani
Studio
Killy
Norichika
Iwakiri
Assistant Director
Shigetsugu
Yoshida
Voicing
Hideyashi
Iizuka
Effects
Toyo
Onkyo
(Shizuo
Kurahashi)
Negative Cutting
Kazuko
Takahashi
Title Logo
Takayasu
Fujii
A flame, it burns passionately
In-Between Checks
Keiko
Hara
Akiko
Shimada
Color Design
Hiroko
Kondo
Finishing Checks
Masayo
Yamamoto
Chisato
Sunagawa
Recording
Tohoku
Shinsha
Development
Tokyo
Laboratory
This love of mine
Production Manager
Hisao Saito
Production Coordinators
Rikio
Yoshida
Kazuhiko
Yanai
Mikihiro
Iwata
Produced in
Cooperation with
Telecom Animation Film
I want for you to understand, and you alone
Cast
Lupin the Third
David
Hayter
Fujiko Mine
Dorothy
Elias-Fahn
Daisuke Jigen
Goemon Ishikawa
Inspector Zenigata
John
Snyder
Michael
Gregory
Kevin
Seymour
Wrap me up in the bond we share
Clarisse
Count Cagliostro
Groundskeeper
Jodot
Bridget
Hoffman
Kirk
Thornton
Barry
Stigler
Milton
James
William H. Bassett
Lauren Benjamin
Beau Billingslea
Kevin Brief
Pamela Brull
Christopher Carroll
Tony Clay
Michael Deak
Keith Diamond
Dyanne DiRosario
Andrew Ebert
David Ellenstein
Eddie Frierson
Gloria Gines
Steve McGowan
Matthew K. Miller
Kenji Nakamura
Jeff Nimoy
Joe Romersa
Kevin Seymour
Adam Sholder
Paul St. Peter
Carol Stanzione
Dave Wittenberg
Tom Wyner
Director
Hayao Miyazaki
Passports, please.
That's my dad.
Thank you, enjoy your stay.
Thanks, I'm sure we will.
Dad?! Hmph, I don't look that old!
Well, I regard you as a father figure.
So this is the Duchy of Cagliostro.
I never heard of the place!
The smallest member of the United Nations
with a population of 3500.
What makes you think this burg
is where the Goat bills originate?
This place is infamous with the crime world.
It's the black hole of counterfeiting.
Huh? Black hole?
Yeah. Snoops who get too nosy
around here are never seen again.
Oooh, stop, I'm scared!
Fear wears me out.
Wake me if I start smoldering!
Hey!
Hm? What, am I burning?
Christ, Lupin, your spare's
balder than the flat!
Peaceful, isn't it?
What the—?
Get in!
Woah, everybody's in a big hurry!
Who we chasing?
The girl!
That figures.
Their tires!
Oh shit!
Damn!
They didn't buy that off the lot!
Gee!
Finally, some excitement around here!
Going up!
Watch it! Tree!
There they are!
This calls for something
more heavy duty!
Yes!
Hey! Hey, hello!
What?
She's unconsious!
Her car's coming apart.
Here, take the wheel.
Watch it!
You're... safe...
Oh, no no no no!
Stop, stop, hold on!
Hold on! Wait!
Hey, cut it out!
Stop, or we're gonna fall!
Look down, look down!
There, now you just
stay like that, okay?
Are you alright? Sir?
It's okay. There.
I have to go.
There she is!
Head her off!
Lupin, you alive?
Thought you were a goner!
Where'd my bride go?
She left ya' at the altar!
Damn!
Who the hell were
those goons... and the dame?
Hey, it's a ring!
I swear I've seen this some—
Are you gonna tell me
what's goin' on or not?
I caught that weird look in your
eye when you saw the ring.
Ow! Slow down, will ya?
We rushed here to look
at an old ruined castle?
It's the very same crest
that was on her ring. Hmm.
Lupin?
This place hasn't
been abandoned long.
Fire, huh?
Who are you?
Just a couple of passers-by.
Tourists, eh?
Yeah, you could say that.
I was under the impression that this was
the grand duke's palace. I must be wrong.
No mistakin' that! This is it, which means
you're tresspassing on private property!
You call this a palace?
It's just a burnt-out shell.
There was a fire here seven years back.
The duke and his wife
died in the flames.
Since then, the place has been
left to decay in the elements.
The grand duke was sort of...
uhh... like your king, wasn't he?
Does that mean
you don't have a ruler now?
There's a regent, and folks say
there's no cause to worry.
Now you two leave the way you come.
Old coot.
Where ya' goin'?
Why you've grown up, haven't you?
What's up?
Don't play dumb with me.
Talk!
No no no no no no!
You're not gonna keep
secrets from me! Come on, talk!
Nyooooo!
Tell me!
Okay, I'll talk, I'll talk!
Now that's what I call upscale living!
The castle of Count Cagliostro, the regent.
Now look over there.
Down more.
To the right, past the aqueduct.
Hmph, well I'll be damned!
That's the boat we saw earlier!
They docked in the old floodgate.
The place is still the same.
Are you telling me
you've broken in there before?
I tried to more than 10 years ago,
to uncover the secret of the Goat bills.
I was just a young punk back then.
Yeah? So what happened?
I got a royal butt kicking!
And I... um... ran off with
my tail between my legs.
I didn't think they still flew autogyros.
The count does.
Let's go find a room for the night.
Huh?
You were very careless, Jodot.
I beg your forgiveness, My Lord.
It occured while she was
being fitted for her wedding gown.
She slipped away when
the guards left her to change.
She's in the north tower now?
Yes, My Lord.
The lady has been heavily sedated.
Foreigners?
Yes.
Two men, My Lord.
They assisted the lady
in eluding her pursuers.
Find them and have
the interlopers dealt with.
It's gone!
I need that ring!
Summon Jodot!
The inscription's in Capran,
a dead language.
So, can you read it?
Of course.
"When light and shadow are joined
once again, it shall be restored."
AD 1517.
The date's in Roman numerals.
That thing's over 400 years old.
Sorry for the wait, gents.
Ooh, delicious!
Something sure has your
attention, what is that?
Oh, it's just an old ring I found.
Maybe it's worth something.
Oh, it's beautiful!
That's the royal crest of Lady Clarisse.
Clarisse?
There's an old photo
of her over the bar.
See?
That was taken when she was a child.
She just returned
from the convent yesterday.
I'll bet she's gorgeous now.
A convent?
Don't you know? I thought both of you were here like everyone else who
came to watch the wedding of
Lady Clarisse and the count.
I see. Well that explains all
the sightseers in this place.
I don't envy Clarisse though.
The count's got a
reputation as a playboy.
Playboy? Just like me.
Now, how about a smooch, huh?
Ahh, you!
What a wild time! We had a blast!
That guy was one of the count's men.
I know.
Hey, you hog!
That dame's not enough,
they want that ring too!
No, you don't!
You've known the whole time that girl was
the grand duke's daughter, haven't ya'?
Huh, thought I'd mentioned it.
"When light and shadow are joined
once again, it shall be restored," huh?
Do you think it is a treasure?
Hey look! The whole gang's here!
Bullets don't work.
They're trained killers!
Dirty bastards!
Look out, let's go!
Oh yeah, that was fun.
That was a full-scale attack
they've launched.
I think we hit a nerve.
And I thought this would be dull.
These bills are inferior.
The quality is becoming
worse in the new batches.
It is a problem, sir.
But it can't be avoided if
we continue mass-producing them.
Redo them. We can't
miss that delivery date.
Yes, sir.
Who's there?
My Lord, I come bearing you bad news.
I have failed you.
The rats escaped the trap.
Jodot, what is that stuck to your back?
What the—? Why that...
Lupin is on the scene
Lupin?
Lupin's calling card.
Read it.
But My Lord, the message is...
Do it.
Ahem.
"To the lecherous and greedy count.
I shall purloin your bride.
That day will come soon."
Signed, Lupin the Third.
Very convienent.
Just wait for the man.
Lupin will come here to us.
That's it over there.
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Why, you got here quick.
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
What's the job?
Goemon's here.
Yeah, so is someone else.
Who?
Take a look.
Huh?
Japanese cops, here?
It's Zenigata.
What?
Alright, everybody out! Rank formation!
And now the players are all in place.
Ow, hot hot hot hot!
Forgive me for barging in like this.
You see, I am Zenigata of Interpol, sir.
We've received a report that Lupin
sent one of his notorious calling cards to you.
Ah, you are no doubt referring to the
grandson of that petty thief, Arsene Lupin.
Is Interpol in the habit of interrupting
peoples' meals for such trivial matters?
Lupin is very treacherous, Your Excellency.
He'll rob you right under your nose.
Your wedding is just five days off.
Until then, please let me keep
a round-the-clock watch on your castle.
We have law enforcement too.
Although we prefer the
refined term of "royal guard."
My Lord, you rang?
Gustav, I expect you to give your full cooperation to our guest Inspector Zenigata.
Jawohl.
Your Excellency, Lupin is a master thief.
Why is he after your bride?
You tell me, you're the one
who's the great detective aren't you?
Goodbye Count.
You think it wise to have that
fellow inside the castle, My Lord?
Don't worry. I have influential
friends even at Interpol.
Our guests will be leaving soon.
Yep, you can always
rely on good ol' Zenigata.
Devoted archetypal Japanese worker.
What is that?
Do not proceed any further, please.
Why?
Observe.
If you don't want to
be killed, don't wander around.
Please tell that to your men too.
Sir. I'm picking up
anti-personnel radar.
Hmph. This is fishy.
There's a lot of extra security
here for your average Count.
A woman?
Relax! It's not what you're thinking.
Lupin just rescued some broad
then everything snowballed.
And what's the importance
of the ring in all this?
We'll find out after we nab the girl
from that lecherous fart, Cagliostro.
At any rate, my Magnum
couldn't dent their hardware.
Let's see how they do against
your sword and an anti-tank gun.
Hey, Lupin. You find a way in yet?
Nope.
Can't swing a dead cat
without hitting lasers or radar.
That sucks. Wish we had a tank.
That's why he sent for Zenigata.
What? Did you?
I did. Goemon, good call!
Pit your foes against one another, huh?
Alright, here's Cagliostro's Castle.
And here's where we are.
This old Roman aqueduct is still in use.
And it's the only way to get in.
The castle's water is supplied by the lake,
and it's brought in via the aqueduct.
So, no lasers in the water because no one's
crazy enough to come in that way.
I like it. Goemon. Keep watch here.
Woah! Bleh!
I forgot to mention the hole.
I forgot to mention the piranhas and crocodiles, Jigen.
Shut up!
Hmm, the first hurdle.
Let's go.
Lupin!
Well! This must be the
clock machinery room.
Hope that poor SOB made it.
What's that windmill for?
Gustav told me it's used
to bring water up into the castle.
Hmm... And where does it come out?
Uh, there's a fountain
on the battlement.
Come on!
Yes, sir!
Inspector!
Orders just came from Paris HQ,
we're to pull out at once.
What?! That's ridiculous! We can't!
Let me talk to 'em!
But we got solid evidence!
There was a written threat from Lupin!
Hm? He said what?
Well too bad if the count got his royal knickers
in a twist! I'm a cop, not a court jester!
Hey hello?! Are you there?
Argh...
It seems I'll have to have a
little chat with His Highness.
Attaboy, lead the way.
I want to see the count at once.
Did you hear me? Right now!
Halt.
Only authorized personnel
and guests are allowed past here.
You mean officers of Interpol
aren't authorized?
You were ordered to vacate the
premises. I must ask you to leave.
How would you know about that order?
We don't need you Orientals
to help us catch a burglar. Now go.
Rest assured, I'll be back.
We're pulling out for now.
Sir!
Tell me, was I just up here?
What?
That was Lupin disguised as me
trying to sneak in here you rube!
Didn't you see through that,
you overgrown strudel-head!
Why, that— Follow me!
Don't let that scoundrel get away!
Hold it right there!
You cannot run, Lupin!
Lupin?
Stop, God dammit! That's Lupin!
I'm not him, I'm me!
Save the Inspector and
our men out there! Go go go!
Wow, culture clash.
He's Lupin! Look!
Damn it!
Lupin!
It appears we've caught someone.
The fool. He should have left
when given the chance.
What happened to the guards?
Gustav!
What the hell is he doing,
leaving his post?
Stay here while I look for him.
Yes, sir!
Sorry, old boy.
Get your men back to
their stations this minute!
You idiot! Lupin tricked you
and now he's in the castle!
Scheisse!
Let go. Let go of me! I can't hold on!
Mein Gott! Help! Help!
So Lupin got inside after all.
I have no excuses, My Lord.
Inform Zenigata's men that
he went back to HQ ahead of them.
People vanish while
traveling all the time.
Yes, My Lord.
Don't move.
Good evening, Fujiko.
Lupin!
As usual, you look your
loveliest when absorbed in work.
I cannot believe that
you made it in here.
That's all you have to
say after a year? I'm crushed.
I searched the world for you.
Uh-huh. You can stop the sweet talk,
I know you came for Clarisse.
Oh, well yeah, that too.
If I tell you where she is, will you
promise to not interfere with my job?
Yes, yes! For you, anything!
Alright.
At the top of the north tower.
But I'm afraid that it's
impossible to get into the place.
Lupin?
Damn, when they lock someone
up they don't kid around.
Come here. Wait, wait!
Who's there?
I'm just a simple thief in the night, my lady.
I've nothing to steal!
Well hello there, Miss Bride.
Y-You're the man who rescued me!
You forgot this.
You came just for this?
But you'll be killed if
the count finds you here.
Just another occupational hazard.
It comes with the job.
I'll leave when my work is finished.
But what work?
Because I'm a prisoner,
all I have are a few pieces of furniture.
It's not much to offer.
Wait! You can take this.
My ring.
What I came seeking is a precious jewel
that an evil sorcerer has locked away
in a dark forbidding tower.
With your consent, this humble thief
will liberate the lovely gem.
Meaning me?
Like a beautiful treasure
that's hidden away in a shadowy vault,
an innocent maiden is
forced to marry against her will.
But an outlaw whisks her to freedom!
You see, heroism goes along with my job.
Then you've come to get me out of here?
I truly appreciate this.
But you don't know about the
terrible secrets of the Cagliostro family.
I'll never be able to escape the Count.
Please, just go.
How can there be a happy
ending to this romantic tale?
The fair damsel believes in the
power of the wicked sorcerer,
yet she has no faith
in the powers of the thief.
Oh, if only she'd believe in him,
then he'd be able
to fly through the air!
Or drink every last drop of
water in the lake in one gulp!
One gulp!
This will have to do for now.
I'm sorry!
Hey! Treat the lady gently,
you lousy gorillas!
I must offer you my thanks
for returning the ring, Lupin.
And I wanna thank you, Count,
for this warm reception.
I regret that we have
to dispose of you.
I warn you, I'm not an
easy guy to get rid of.
Count! Please let him go,
you have what you want now!
Don't forget, fair damsel,
you've got to have faith in the thief!
Mr. Thief!
Hey, don't worry about me. Alright?
I'll be back real soon.
Well, now, what game shall we play, hmm?
They'll rip you to shreds
if I give the word,
but I don't want my fiancee's boudoir
stained with the blood of a petty criminal.
I'll make you regret that,
you pompous drip.
I've grown weary of you, Lupin.
Ta-ta!
If the fall doesn't kill him, that pit
is a foul hell from which there is no escape.
That pretty face has already
tempted a man to his doom.
No question you're a Cagliostro.
You'll make a fitting wife.
Monster! Cold-blooded murderer!
You're so right.
I do indeed have blood on my hands,
but you do as well.
My family has served in the
shadow of the grand duke for centuries.
Carrying out its assassinations and plots
to support this country.
You're disgusting! Don't touch me!
Don't feign ignorance with me, Clarisse.
You're as much a Cagliostro as I am.
In both our veins flows the
ancient blood of the Ram.
We share a common
heritage and its legacy.
My lovely, you know our
bloodline has been divided.
For 400 years the light
and shadow have been kept apart.
It's time to reunite the
houses of Cagliostro.
Look.
When the golden ram
of my house is joined
with your house's silver ram,
then it will be revealed!
The hidden treasure of our ancient ancestors!
I heard that, you dirty so-and-so!
Clarisse, he's just marrying you to get the treasure.
It's him!
The counterfeiting count.
Everything he says or does is phony!
Bloodline be damned!
That girl's a wonderful person. Nothing like you, you nasty old goat, pardon the pun.
Is that really you Lupin?
Yup! The one and only.
Because you believed in the thief,
he was able to fly through the air.
I'll be winging my way to you
soon and steal you from here.
Okay?
Okay.
Damn him, it's the ring!
Give me that.
Okay, Count, listen up!
So help me, if you lay one slimy finger on Clarisse,
your precious little ring is gonna end up like this!
It's fake!
How rude!
You sure do know how
to make a guest feel unwelcome!
He fell?
Probably.
Make sure.
That rank abyss is not
a place for the living, sir.
Let him rot, in a while he'll be dead.
Lupin still posesses the ring.
I'll handle it, My Lord.
Just wait. I'll bring your dear thief
back to you flayed and quartered!
Must be previous uninvited visitors.
It does have a certain... rustic charm.
Some fresh paint, curtains,
a few plants, maybe... track lighting.
Centuries of political murder, and for what?
Rest in peace, you poor bastards.
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Here Gennosuke Kawakami,
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
spy for the Japanese army,
met his end. Avenge me.
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Lupin!
I've got you now, you little weasel.
It's nice to see you too, Old Man.
Be quiet, I'm taking you in.
Just show me the way out.
But I fell in, same as you.
It looks like you've been
wandering around here for a while.
Shut up!
I won't take pity from a punk.
We might as well get cozy.
There seems to be no way out of here.
'Scuse me there, my good buddy.
Say, Old Man, you got a light?
Lupin, what the hell gives with the cadaver
dump? Doesn't seem like a catacomb.
Take a peek at the wall there.
Good God...
May your soul be at rest, old soldier.
I had a gut feeling something
was suspicious about this place,
but what kind of secret is worth
so much trouble to hide?
That's why you're here, isn't it?
That's what Fujiko's trying to find out.
I hope she won't meet a fate
like these boys.
At any rate, worrying won't
do a lick of good right now.
Let's get some shut-eye.
Good night, Old Man.
Christ, it's cold out here.
I'm freezing my freaking ass off.
Damn, he's been in there
a long time. How does it look?
I've seen nothing.
Then I guess we'll have to keep waiting.
What's keeping them?
Mr. Jodot, look!
Ah, they've found the ring!
Heave...
I can't swim!
Hey, wait!
Don't leave me here! Come back!
Curse you, you'll pay for this!
These are coffins.
Well, this brings a whole-new
meaning to home business.
What the hell is all this stuff?
Woah.
These are 10,000 yen bills.
And so is the whole heap!
Exceptional quality.
Hey, Old Man!
Check it out!
West German Deutschmarks also!
Pound notes. Dollars.
Francs. Rubles. Rupees.
Pesos. Lira. Shekels.
Wow, even Chinese won!
The whole world's represented here!
A major counterfeiting ring.
Lupin, do you think this is what they're hiding?
Bingo.
The birthplace of Goat bills, legendary fakes
you can't tell apart from the real thing.
The notorious imitation currency that
silently brought about the
upheavals of Medieval Europe.
It caused the collapse
of the Bourbon dynasty,
provided Napoleon with funding,
and eventually triggered
the great bank panic of 1927.
Goat bills were responsible for
some of history's most influential and
devastating events of the last 400 years.
And those who came
here looking for the source...
never left.
I've always heard tell about them,
but who'd suspect a
tiny country be behind it all?
Now that you've seen this,
I'll bet real dough you won't walk away from it.
That's right! A good
cop can't ignore this.
Well then what do you say to a truce
until we get out of this place?
Okay, but I don't wanna
catch you filching, bub.
And I warn ya', I'm cuffing ya' the
minute we get outta here.
That's fair enough.
Old Man, why don't we shake on it?
That's pushing it.
Hmm?
Miss Fujiko.
I just wanted to stop in
and say goodbye, my dear.
What is this, who are you?
Just another employee
of the castle
hired to be your
servant, or so it would seem.
But in reality, I'm a spy hunting
for the secret of this place.
I was planning to stay a little longer,
but Lupin showed up.
He's got everyone jumping,
so I gotta leave.
You mean you know the thief?
Oh yes, only too well.
We've been allies, and enemies too.
On occasion, we've even been lovers.
He's a natural born lady-killer.
Watch your step.
Did he leave you?
Are you kidding?
I left.
That's the trapdoor.
There's a fire in the building.
Where?
It's coming from underground.
Movement.
That's our boy!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Come on!
Sir! The fire appears to have
started down in the printing plant.
Put it out immediately, damn it!
Yes, My Lord.
Shut that blasted door!
Go on, idiots, help them!
Jodot, have you
disappointed me once again?
Hey, Old Man! Shake a leg!
Our company oughta be here soon.
Evidence. I need evidence!
That does it! Go!
Huh?!
Lupin and that cop did this!
Find those bastards!
They're probably still in here!
Go on! Get in there!
Yes, sir!
It's Lupin and the cop! After them!
Put out the fire.
Ja.
We're in the chapel!
This way!
Look, it's them!
It's my thief!
Lupin and Zenigata?
The autogyro's up there!
Stop, you—!
You imbecile!
You can rake me over the coals later,
they're after Lady Clarisse! Hurry, sir!
Get a move on!
Halt!
You wanna tangle
with the Tokyo Metro Police?!
Come on!
Old Man, we're leaving!
Sayonara!
I'm afraid we've got
to make a small detour!
Kidnapping a cop's illegal!
No, we're on a rescue!
They're coming here!
Stand back.
Grenade-proof, that figures!
Save yourselves!
We can't break the window out!
Old Man, take over.
What? Hey Lupin!
Wait! I can't fly this thing!
Someone call for a cab?
Oh, Mr. Thief!
Your chariot awaits, m'lady.
Come on, throw me a line!
Quit bossing me around!
Fujiko!
Hurry!
My hero!
There we are, you're safe now.
This way, Old Man, down over here!
I'm trying, you idiot!
That's it, a little closer!
Lupin!
Don't move, you meddling bitch!
Fujiko, I think I'll have to interrogate
you later in my chambers.
Jodot, finish off Lupin now.
Yes, sir.
No, please I'm begging you!
You'll have to kill me
before you kill him!
Fire.
I admire your devotion, Clarisse.
Get the ring for me
and I'll forgive you, dear.
Become my wife without a fight
and I will even let your thief live.
Or you can both die right now together.
Which will it be, Clarisse?
Lupin, where's the ring?
No, Clarisse. Don't do it.
He's a liar.
His collar. He always
hides stuff under there.
Damn it, Fujiko!
Alright, I have the ring.
If you want it, let Fujiko and this man go,
or I'll throw it into the lake!
I swear on my life. Now please
put on the ring and come here.
Shall I shoot?
Wait until we have the ring.
Incoming!
Shoot! Don't let them escape!
No!
Lupin was right! You are a liar!
I would never let anyone leave alive
who saw those printing presses!
Finally, it's mine.
Hey, you owe me for today, honey.
Bye!
Man! We're pulling out
even before we get to join in!
Hang on, we're going down!
Jump for it!
This is unworthy of my blade.
Lupin! Don't even think
about dying before I arrest you!
We have a sticky wicket here.
Sacre bleu! It is a plot of some kind!
Let me bust this guy!
Look at the evidence, there's no
better proof! I saw it myself!
There were printing presses everywhere!
We understand that, Inspector!
We have a high-level political dilemma...
Interpol's exercise of authority
would not be recommended in this matter at all.
What do you mean?
We've got Cagliostro dead to rights!
It is not that simple.
Even Interpol cannot force
a criminal investigation
on a United Nations independent member!
The situation does not weigh in our favor.
Have you seen the front page
headlines of the leading global newspapers?
"Courageous Count defends fiancee!
Thief's attempt to kidnap Princess fails!"
Along with reports of a henchman
disguised as you.
Henchman my eye, that was me!
That seems like rash behavior
for a man of your standing!
Do you guys care about the truth or not!
That's irrelevant!
The world believes what it wants to.
It believes the count!
I have heard rumor that the Count has
many friends in Western government.
The truth could be
very embarassing for some nations.
Especially for a certain country that placed
a huge order for U.S. counterfeit dollars!
And I suppose these fake rubles
were not solicited by the CIA!
Gentlemen, please!
This is neither the time nor
place to end your nations' quarrels!
The only way to deal with this is for each country
to handle its own problems, discreetly!
Inspector, we're ready to mobilize.
Just give the word, and
we'll leave for the castle at any moment.
No one's going.
The sooner they find a
replacement for me, the better,
then we can get off this damn case.
All of you just get ready to go home.
It's me.
Some food.
Great. Thank you.
How's your friend doing?
Better. His fever broke.
Thanks to the treatment you gave him.
You know, it's the hound
you oughta be grateful to.
That old animal doesn't like anyone,
but when you brought your friend here
the dog refused to leave his side.
If not for that,
I'd have never hidden you boys.
Karl, old boy.
Hey look, he's awake.
Welcome back pal, how you feeling?
Jigen. Goemon.
It's sure been a long time.
Long time? What? Why'd he say that?
Seems his wounds have
temporarily addled his memory.
Good boy.
Why aren't you out romping with your owner today, Karl?
How does a complete stranger
like you know this dog's name?
The only other person besides myself
who knows it is Karl's mistress, the Lady Clarisse.
Pretty name.
So, a woman called Clarisse
owns ya' huh, fella?
Clarisse...
Lupin?
How many days have I been out?
Jigen, tell me, how long?!
Uh, well, uhh, three.
The wedding... he marries her tomorrow!
I have—
Hey, you can't push it.
You're gonna reopen your injuries.
Bring me food. I gotta eat something.
Want some mush? Porridge?
I've lost blood, Jigen.
I don't want to eat baby food, I want a feast!
Well, that won't be easy...
I'll see what I can do.
You damn fool! Stop stuffing yourself!
Your stomach can't handle it!
Clam up! Gimme 12 hours and I'll be fine!
See? What'd I tell ya'?
You're turning green, you want a bucket?
Huh? You what?
Lupin says he's full.
I see. So he did it for the Princess.
There's not much he can
do now that he's hurt.
You seem to have a deep connection
with the Lady Clarisse from the past.
I've always tended the palace gardens.
As a girl, the Princess
loved flowers and plants.
After her parents were killed in the fire,
she was sent off to a convent.
She gave Karl to me before she left.
So when the dog got a whiff of Lupin
he probably picked up Clarisse's scent.
Possibly, but that doesn't explain
how he knew the dog's name.
Hey, when he tried to rescue the girl,
maybe she mentioned it.
That's not how I know.
You're awake already, huh?
It was just 10 short years ago.
I was a kid stepping out on my own,
fearless and eager to take on the world.
Lupin
I had more enthusiasm than brains.
Stupidly, I decided to find the
wellspring of the Goat bills.
Somehow, I staggered ashore,
but I collapsed, unable to move another inch.
Karl? What's the matter,
did you find something?
When she ran off, I thought
my goose was cooked for sure.
Here, mister.
Water.
Her little hands trembled as
she gave me the glass of water.
That's when I happened
to notice her ring.
I'm almost embarassed to say...
I'd forgotten all about it
until I saw the ring again.
Hear that? It's Fujiko's bike.
It's a clipping from today's paper.
"Tommorow an archbishop is arriving
from the Vatican to perform the marriage."
Go away!
Talk, I'm a busy man!
Fujiko?
How do you know he's gonna
hit the wedding? You sure?
Your superiors wouldn't fault you
for going back there to catch a thief, right?
That's right! Excellent!
Come on! Move it!
We have to get through here! Move it!
Hey, you blind? Did you
happen to notice the traffic jam?
Yeah, there's a landslide
blocking the road up ahead.
There must be some other way we can take.
We can't be late for the wedding!
Excuse me. Would you by any
chance be the archbishop?
Ah, yes, I can see you are.
Please, would you mind blessing this lamb, Your Pontiff?
You live here. Do you know any
other way to Castle Cagliostro?
Sure. Nearby there's an old country road.
Fantastic!
Will you show us where it is?
Hop in, please!
Of course. Anything for the archbishop.
Put some muscle into it, will ya'!
We gotta make the castle by nightfall!
Just one more hill, men!
It does not seem like a good idea
to bring a TV crew in here.
His Excellency wants the world
to witness his marriage
to a proper, decent young woman.
The archbishop has finally arrived.
You suppose Lupin will come?
I have my Shadows closely
watching over the bride.
You just worry about
watching the front gate.
Ja.
The time is at hand
for light and shadow to reunite.
Clarisse, come.
Bring forth the proof
that will validate
these two as truly noble members
of the ancient bloodline of Cagliostro.
In accordance with the old custom,
you shall exchange these rings
and recite your vows.
Clarisse d' Cagliostro, daughter
of the Grand Duke of Cagliostro,
if you or anyone present
objects to this marriage,
you must speak now.
Otherwise, silence will be accepted as consent to this union.
I then confer God's blessing upon you.
I object!
This wedding is soiled
by the count's evil desires.
It is an omen!
Don't panic.
These are earthly meddlers
we are dealing with.
In the name of the dead
who lie beneath this castle,
I have come to take your bride-to-be.
Mamma mia, a ghost!
Stand back.
Enjoy the fun.
Clarisse, you must come with me.
What a terrible turn of events!
That scoundrel Lupin just turned up!
Stop the broadcast.
What are you doing?
Please wait one moment
Let's go!
Clarisse! Clarisse!
Poor girl. They drugged you, didn't they?
The evil count didn't want
you to able to speak.
Stay back, caramila. Please, control yourself.
No!
He was a fool!
Let his friends die with him.
Don't cry, Clarisse.
Your thief can't die that easily.
I'm coming for you, Clarisse.
How do you like my wedding gift, Count?
Excellency, look!
These are the counterfeit bills you made.
Take them as my payment for the rings.
Find him! He's got to be in here.
Well, look what I've got!
What is this?
Lupin!
You're alive!
Why, you!
How dare you make a fool of me!
Goat boy, chill out before
you burn yourself.
Check this out!
Oh my God!
Eat this!
You're not getting
away this time, Lupin!
After experiencing
some technical difficulty,
we now resume full coverage of
the royal wedding ceremony.
Well, gotta run!
Argh! Die!
Go on! After them!
Lupin's escaping with the princess,
and the count is chasing him in a rage.
Ah, now the police are joining in!
Lupin's under the altar.
Alright men! Charge!
The cops are storming their
way to the front of the chapel!
Oh, and here come the
count's royal guardsmen,
led by Captain Gustav!
Deploy the rear guard!
Stand your ground!
The place looks like a warzone!
Most of the fighting seems to
be centered around that altar.
No wonder, there's a secret
underground stairway!
Hey, could that be where Lupin is hiding?
Well, let's take a camera and find out!
Lupin!
Your crime days are over!
What is that idiot doing?
He disobeyed orders. Recall him!
There's no time.
This is a live satellite feed.
Oh ho, what have we here?
Those look like printing presses.
And what do I see over there?
Oh my, these are yen!
Could they be counterfeit?
Lord, he's a bad actor.
What a terrible discovery!
There's fake money
of almost every nation!
I came looking for Lupin but
uncovered a criminal plot!
Oh what to do?
Go, go, go!
We're gonna get you
out of here first thing.
Well gentlemen, are you ready?
Always. We'll hold 'em off here.
Let's go!
Wait!
Promise me you'll be careful.
And you, Sir Jigen.
Be sure both of you come back alive.
I'll never forget your chivalry.
You'd better get going.
Clarisse, come on, hurry!
Right!
See ya'!
She called me sir!
She's lovely.
Let's do some damage.
Tonight you face a
sword that is like no other.
Damn that accursed Lupin,
he hasn't beaten me yet!
We'll secure the castle, My Lord.
Good.
Your wounds hurt?
I never felt better.
Now, let's get through here.
A crest of two rams...
each one facing the other.
Put 'em together,
and a message appears.
It's in Capran. Light and shadow...
It's too worn. I can't read it.
"When light and shadow are joined,
face the sun-washed ram on high,
the hourkeeper, and place this within its eyes."
They're old words that have been
passed down through my family.
Are they of any help to you?
My dear, the mystery is solved.
It's the count! This way.
They're headed for the tower
gear room. Moor the boat!
Duck. Heh.
Look, there they are.
So, we're playing rough!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Run!
Turn the lasers off now.
The fools can't get out, they're cornered.
Get down!
You afraid?
Not really.
Brave girl. Come on!
Don't let 'em go!
Don't look!
Not that way!
Take the stairway you half-wits!
Stay here.
I'm going to block the entrance.
Be careful!
Be right back.
There he is!
Behind you Lupin!
Alley-oop!
Hiya, Count old pal!
Bastard. I'll skewer you.
Take your best shot,
it's your last chance!
One more!
Hey! Come and get me Caggy,
or are you scared?
Lupin!
I'll finish you off first,
my darling fiancee.
Go on Clarisse, run!
I'll be there as fast as I can!
Where you running off to, Clarisse?
Oh dear. It appears that
you can't go any further.
And your thief isn't here
to save you this time.
What a pity.
Let the Cagliostro bloodline end here.
Farewell, Clarisse.
Now wait a minute, Count!
Let's haggle.
It is too late. Stand there and
watch as I run the girl through.
Just listen to me!
I'll give you the secret of the rings.
Then take the damn treasure
and do what you want with it.
In exchange, let the girl go.
Set her free.
Look. See the ram crest up there?
That's the sun-washed ram on high,
the hourkeeper.
There's a hole in each of its
eyes where the rings go.
I'll give you the rings now.
But if you hurt the girl, I'll throw them
into the lake, and then I swear I'll kill you.
That's far enough, thank you.
Now, send Clarisse inside.
Mmm, no. I don't think so.
No!
You fool. I still had one ace up my sleeve.
Come.
The rings are back in my possession now.
And for solving the mystery,
your reward Lupin...
Let go!
Hold on Clarisse!
Let me go!
The clock tower, look!
The Count...
What in the hell's that?
Count Cagliostro's reign is over.
Please, do it.
I don't kill without cause.
My thief?
Hi. Feel like standing?
Feast your eyes.
The mysterious hidden treasure.
An ancient Roman city lay at the
bottom of the lake all these ages.
I'm assuming the Romans built the floodgate
and then flooded the city
when they were driven from here.
Your ancestors unknowingly inherited it.
This is a treasure all right...
it's one to be shared with mankind.
It's too big for my pocket anyway.
Interpol finally got off its fat ass.
Does this mean you're going to leave now?
Well, you see there are
some very scary men after me.
Take me with you.
I know I can't be a thief yet,
but I can learn!
Oh please, I want to—
I want to go with you, my thief!
I'll follow you anywhere!
Clarisse.
It's no life for a young lady.
Do you want to go back
into the darkness?
Why, you've only just
found your way into the sunlight!
Hey, your whole life is ahead of you.
It's beginning right now.
Besides, you don't want to
be a ne'er-do-well like me.
But if you're ever in trouble,
I'll come running.
Just let me know and I'll rush to your rescue
from the far reaches of the Earth.
It's Karl!
Oh, Karl!
Lady Clarisse!
Christopher!
Ah, Karl!
Wait!
'Til we meet again!
Hiya, Princess!
My thief, wait!
Stay well, lovely princess! Adieu!
Thank you so much everyone!
All of you take care now!
Adieu! Adieu!
Blast! Just one step behind!
The thief managed to steal again.
No, he didn't take anything, I swear.
He saved my life putting his own at risk.
I'm right, that devil stole something
precious and priceless.
Your heart, my lady.
Yes.
Well, duty calls.
After Lupin! I won't rest until he's caught!
Searching out happiness
Is how I want to make my way
Even thorny paths and freezing cold nights
Good folk like that you
sure don't meet everyday.
I want to traverse, the two of us together
For some reason I get a feeling
that I knew Lupin a long time ago.
My thief, we will meet
again one day, I know it.
The bleak heart of the traveler
Y'know, she's a pretty nice kid.
Who will be there to embrace it?
You could stay if you wanted.
Who will make those dreams come true?
What the—? Fujiko!
Hey sweetie, I really scored! Take a peek.
Huh? The Goat bill printing plates!
Oh yeah, that's my girl! Woohoo!
See you babe!
Uh, wait-wait-wait-wait-wait!
Fujiko, wait for me!
A flame, it burns passionately
It's the Old Man again.
This love of mine
Stop! You won't get away, Lupin!
I want for you to understand, and you alone
Wrap me up in the bond we share
Fin