TOHO
TOHO COMPANY LTD.
A TOKYO MOVIE SHINSHA PRODUCTION
After 'em! Move! Move! Move!
- Hurry up!
- What the-
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Keep up
the good
work
Five billion bucks and all untraceable.
How about a money shower?
Here.
Hot! Very hot!
Just burry me, why don't you?
What's wrong, Lupin?
Let's dump it.
What?
Oh, they're very convincing, but they're all counterfeit.
They are? They can't be.
Why would a government-run casino
have counterfeit money?
They're Gothic bills.
Gothics? I thought that was just a fairy tale.
Nope, but you wouldn't expect to
see them in a state casino.
Jigen, that should be our next job.
Now it's time to spread the wealth.
Let's party!
Get this funny money out of here.
Lupin the Third
The Castle of Cagliostro
Producer
Tetsuo Katayama
Executive Producer
Yutaka Fujioka
Original Story
Monkey Punch
(Serialized in Weekly Manga Action • Published by Futabasha)
Screenplay
Hayao
Miyazaki
Haruya
Yamazaki
Music
Yuji Ohno
Theme Song
The Treasure of
the Flame
(Columbia
Records)
Lyrics
Jun
Hashimoto
Music
Yuji
Ohno
Voice
BOBBY
Music Selection
Seiji Suzuki
Is how I want to make my way
Director of Animation
Yasuo Ohtsuka
Art
Shichiro
Kobayashi
Photography
Hirokata
Takahashi
Recording
Satoshi
Kato
Editing
Yoshihisa
Tsurubuchi
Even thorny paths and freezing cold nights
Key Animation
Masako Shinohara
Kazuhide
Tomonaga
Hideo
Kawachi
Nobuo
Tomizawa
Tsukasa
Tannai
Shojuro
Yamauchi
Kouji
Maruyama
Johji
Manabe
Atsuko
Tanaka
Nobumasa
Shinkawa
I want to traverse, the two of us together
In-Between Animation
Yasunao
Aoki
Miwako
Ohsato
Masami
Ozaki
Masanori
Ono
Kyoko
Kawanaka
Ryoko
Kashiwada
Yumiko
Kumamoto
Yayoi
Kobayashi
Junko
Kojima
Hideyo
Sano
Yoko
Sakurai
Junko
Shimozaki
Yoshiko
Shimazu
Harumi
Shibata
Yoshihiro
Shida
Yukio
Suzuki
Atsuko
Tanabe
Miwako
Takagi
Junko
Tsutsumi
Yoko
Tsukada
Yoshinobu
Michihata
Hitoshi
Nanba
Shunsuke
Harada
Masako
Hayashi
Sachiko
Hamada
Masayo
Hamahata
Saburo
Hashimoto
Kumiko
Hirama
Toshiyuki
Hiruma
Kazuko
Fujimura
Kaoru
Honda
Rieko
Mochizuki
Yoko
Yoshimura
AJIADO
OH
Pro
The bleak heart of the traveler
Backgrounds
Kobayashi Production
Masashi
Aoki
Hiroshi
Ohno
Toshiharu
Mizutani
Miyuki
Kudo
Tsutomu
Ishigaki
Satoshi
Matsuoka
Hiromasa
Ogura
Jinzaburo
Kaiho
Yumiko
Hayashi
Yuko
Fujie
Telecom
Nizo Yamamoto
Who will be there to embrace it?
Photography
Takahashi Production
Masao
Miyauchi
Nobuhisa
Takahashi
Tadashi
Hosono
Keizo
Saito
Katsumi
Ohta
Akio
Hirayama
Yoshinori
Nakamura
Takuo
Suzuki
Who will make those dreams come true?
Finishing
Studio Korumi
Kunitoshi
Okajima
Shaft
Noriko Kato
Easy
World
Naoya
Hayashi
Studio
Taj
Noriko
Shiotani
Studio
Killy
Norichika
Iwakiri
Assistant Director
Shigetsugu
Yoshida
Voicing
Hideyashi
Iizuka
Effects
Toyo
Onkyo
(Shizuo
Kurahashi)
Negative Cutting
Kazuko
Takahashi
Title Logo
Takayasu
Fujii
A flame, it burns passionately
In-Between Checks
Keiko
Hara
Akiko
Shimada
Color Design
Hiroko
Kondo
Finishing Checks
Masayo
Yamamoto
Chisato
Sunagawa
Recording
Tohoku
Shinsha
Development
Tokyo
Laboratory
This love of mine
Production Manager
Hisao Saito
Production Coordinators
Rikio
Yoshida
Kazuhiko
Yanai
Mikihiro
Iwata
Produced in
Cooperation with
Telecom Animation Film
I want for you to understand, and you alone
Cast
Lupin the Third
Tony
Oliver
Fujiko Mine
Michelle
Ruff
Daisuke Jigen
Goemon Ishikawa
Inspector Zenigata
Richard
Epcar
Lex
Lang
Doug
Erholtz
Wrap me up in the bond we share
Clarisse
Count Cagliostro
Groundskeeper
Jodot
Cherami
Leigh
Jamieson
Price
Paul St.
Peter
Steve
Kramer
Kevin Brief
Kyle Hebert
Kayli Mills
Jason C. Miller
Bill Rogers
Ellyn Stern
Director
Hayao Miyazaki
I've never heard of principality of Cagliostro.
They're the smallest country in the United Nations.
Their population's only 3,500.
Ah, and you're sure this is where the
Gothic bills are coming from?
They have a nickname for this place in the underworld.
It's the Black Hole of Counterfeiting.
Why the Black Hole?
They say anyone who comes around here
snooping is never seen again.
Ah, that's quite a scary story.
Scares me right to sleep.
Hey.
Hmm?
And the spares totally bald, of course.
That's really not helpful, Lupin.
Beautiful day.
What the?
Get in!
Who're we helping?
The girl.
Naturally.
Shoot the tires.
Got it.
Those aren't normal tires.
Yikes.
Now things are getting interesting.
Get him.
Hang on.
This time I'm giving 'em the good stuff.
Yes.
Uh-oh.
She's passed out.
Her car's falling apart.
Take the wheel, Jigen.
Huh?
Wait a sec.
Hang on.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
No!
- Let me go!
- Hey, knock it off. Stop it.
We're going to fall.
Look down there and you'll see.
Look down.
Much better.
Now please hold still.
Hello, sir.
Sir.
Sir. Sir.
Please forgive me.
There she is.
Yo, Lupin.
You look rough.
Where's the bride?
Shoot.
All of that for some girl?
Who were they?
It's a ring.
Hang on.
Where have I...
What's gotten into you?
You take a look at that ring and now
you're acting all weird.
Woah, take it easy, will ya?
Hey, Lupin.
What are we doing at this old castle, huh?
It's just like the crest that was on that ring, Lupin.
This place wasn't deserted that long ago.
A fire?
Who's there?
Just passing through.
Are ya tourists?
You could say that.
This is supposed to be the palace of His
Highness the Prince, isn't it?
It's still the Prince's palace, and it's
not open to tourists or outsiders.
If it's still the Prince's palace, why
the heck is it all hollowed out?
There was a big fire seven years ago.
Ever since the passing of the Prince and his wife,
it's been left to fall apart, as you can see.
That's odd.
Wasn't the Prince kind of like a king?
You guys don't have a ruler any longer?
There's a region, so apparently it's not a problem.
So don't you linger, you hear?
All right.
Hey, Lupin.
You went and got all grown up.
What's wrong?
Quit playing dumb, Lupin.
Stop you're choking me!
Tell me what's going on, Lupin.
No!
How about now?
I'll talk, I'll talk.
That's the castle of the regent Count Cagliostro.
Look over there.
Lower.
On the other side of the aqueduct.
Hey, it's that boat from earlier.
So the bride is in that castle.
There's a sluice gate where it's docked,
just like it was before.
Lupin, you've broken into that castle before?
I went in there over 10 years ago to learn
the secret of the Gothic bills.
I was one naive little punk.
And what happened?
I got a royal butt kicking, so I skedaddled
and hightailed it out of there.
Who the heck flies an autogyro these days?
That's the Count.
Huh?
Come on, let's go find an inn or something.
Hey.
Uh...
That was careless of you, Jodot.
My apologies, sir.
Her ladyship was being fitted for her wedding gown,
and the men were not present at
the time, your Eminence.
She's in the North Tower now?
Yes, sir.
The drugs have put her into a sound sleep.
Foreigners?
Yes, sir.
I'm told it was two men, strangers.
While she tried to escape, they came to her aid.
Find them, and dispose of them as you see fit.
Oops.
The ring is gone.
Get me Jodot.
Hmm.
It's written in the old Gothic alphabet.
Gothic, you say?
"With light and shadow as one once more,
it shall surely be restored."
"1517."
The year is in Roman numerals.
So this thing's over 400 years old?
Sorry for the wait
Ooh, looks yummy.
You seem awfully preoccupied.
What are you looking at there?
This? It's just an old ring I found.
Maybe it's worth something.
Wow, it's pretty.
It has the crest of Lady Clarisse on it.
Huh? Clarisse?
See, that's her in that photo up there.
That's from when she was little, though.
She came back from the convent yesterday.
I'm sure she's a fine young lady.
The convent?
Oh, you don't know?
I thought you gentlemen were here for the big event.
Lady Clarisse is going to marry the Count this week.
So that's it.
I was wondering why all of these sightseers were here.
I don't envy Lady Clarisse.
The Count has a bad reputation for being a playboy.
Playboy? Like me?
How about tonight, huh?
Oh, you!
Rawr!
She's a Capricorn, he's a Libra.
I'm sure that guy was one of the Count's spies.
Clearly.
Hey, Leave some.
The Count wants both the girl and the ring.
Hey, give it.
Why didn't you tell me that girl we
saw today was the Princess?
Thought I mentioned it.
With light and shadow as one once more,
it shall surely be restored, huh?
Do you think it is a treasure?
Hmm?
Hey, who invited these guys?
They're bulletproof.
There's too many of them.
Hurry up.
Take that.
Creep-o!
Yeesh, that was something.
Well, it certainly wasn't the welcoming committee.
Down the rabbit hole we go.
Think they're trying to tell us something?
These didn't turn out well.
Lately the quality's been very disappointing.
My apologies, sir.
But our quality control can't keep up with mass production.
Redo all of these and don't miss our delivery date.
Who's there?
Forgive me excellency, I have failed you.
The rats have escaped.
Hmm?
Jodot, what is that paper on your back?
Uh, this is, what?
Lupin is on the scene
When did he do this?
Lupin.
It's a warning from Lupin.
Read it.
Yes, sir, but--
Go ahead.
To the count of lust and greed,
I'll be taking your bride.
Expect me soon, signed Lupin the Third.
It's good news, Jodot.
Huh?
Let us wait then for Lupin to come to us.
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
You got here quick, didn't you?
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
Udon Noodles
with
Deep Fried Tofu
There's a job.
Goemon's here.
And so are the others.
Huh?
Go take a peek.
Hmm.
Huh?
Japanese police cars.
Yeah, it's Zenigata.
Huh?
All personnel, disembark.
Pull in!
Now our cast of characters is complete.
Hot, hot, hot...
Pardon me for interrupting your meal, Excellency.
I'm Zenigata of the International
Criminal Police Organization.
I'm here because you received a notice from Lupin.
Ah, that petty thief who claims
to be the grandson Arsene Lupin?
Does Interpol always disturb people's breakfast
over such trivialities?
Excellency, don't underestimate Lupin.
If he says he'll come, he'll be here.
Your ceremony's in five days.
I must insist that you allow us
to inspect your castle.
We have police in this country too,
though we refer to them more elegantly
as the Royal Guard.
You rang, my lord.
Gustav, I want you to cooperate
with this Japanese officer.
That will be all.
Sir.
Pardon me, sir.
Could you tell me why you think Lupin
would be after your bride?
Well, it's your job to investigate
these matters, Inspector.
If you'll excuse me.
Do you think it wise to have
that Inspector roaming the castle, sir?
No matter.
I have friends even inside Interpol.
Don't fear, he'll be leaving soon enough.
There's Zenigata, truly a child of pre-war Japan.
One determined bulldog.
What's that over there?
No, do not take another step.
What?
Observe.
If you prefer to stay alive, don't wander around.
Be sure to pass that on to your men.
Sir, we're picking up anti-personnel radar.
Hmm, something's fishy.
It's too small a country for defenses like this.
A woman?
Don't go, it's not what you're thinking.
There's a woman involved, yes,
but there's more to the story, see?
Is there anything special about this ring?
We'll know that once we get the girl back
from that creepy old man, the Count.
Anyhow, my magnum couldn't dent the monsters,
but with your blade and this anti-tank rifle,
Hey Lupin, did you find a way in yet?
Nope, this place is a fortress,
a network of lasers and radar.
No kidding, we're gonna need a tank.
So is that why you called Zenigata?
What, is that true?
Yeah, you got it, you're as sharp as ever.
You are going to fight fire with fire.
This is the castle of Cagliostro.
We're here and this Roman aqueduct is still in use
and it's our only way in.
They use the aqueduct to draw water
from the lake into the castle.
Well, that's good news since there won't be
any laser cannons underwater, an easy in.
Goemon, you're the lookout.
Watch out for the hole.
Told ya.
Here's the first hurdle.
Let's go.
Hey! Lupin!
Wow, that's the Clock Tower's machinery room.
I really hope Lupin made it through there.
Hmm. What's that windmill do?
Gustav told us it brings water
up into the castle, sir.
Hmm. Where's that water come out?
It comes out in a fountain up in the battery.
- Come with me now!
- Yes, sir!
Inspector!
New orders from Paris.
We're to withdraw and return at once.
What? That's totally ridiculous!
I'm gonna verify this myself.
What? But, but Lupin left one of his warning notes.
Hmm? The Count called.
I don't care if he made a stink. We're
police officers, not his lackies.
We gotta job to do-- Hello? Are you there?
I'm taking this up with the Count.
Oh yeah, show me the way, Pops.
I'm here to talk to the Count.
Didn't you hear me? Let me pass.
No admittance.
Inspector, only the trustworthy are
allowed past this point.
You telling me the ICPO can't be trusted?
I believe you've been ordered to withdraw.
Please take your men and leave here.
How in the world did you know about that?
We can deal with Lupin without the help
of you foreigners. Now leave.
Okay, I understand. We'll pull out for now.
Yes, sir.
Hmm.
Were you just talking to me?
You idiot, that was Lupin.
He just disguised himself to get in.
What good are those muscles if you
can't even spot a fake?
Follow me.
Don't let Lupin get away.
Hold it right there.
We have you, Lupin.
Lupin?
Stop! I'm not Lupin! Wait!
They're attacking the inspector.. Everybody
put down those guards.
Toodle, see you, Pops.
Lupin's right there.
Lupin!
It appears that we caught someone.
Idiot should have left when he still had the chance.
Where are the guards?
Gustav. What is he doing leaving his post?
- You stay here.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, Pops.
Gustav, call off this insanity immediately.
Are you blind and dumb? Lupin played
you like a fiddle.
What?
Let go! Let go of me!
So Lupin snuck in, apparently.
My shame is beyond words, sir.
Tell the police officers that their inspector
went back ahead of them.
People vanish all the time while traveling.
Absolutely.
Don't move.
Good evening, Fujicakes.
Lupin.
Seeing a woman engrossed in her
work is a beautiful sight.
You've made it this far in here already?
It's been almost a year, and that's all you can say.
You know I searched everywhere.
Lupin, what you're really searching
for is the bride, am I right?
Ah, can't fool you.
I'll tell you where she is if you promise
you won't get in the way of my job.
Of course, of course. You know I won't.
Yeah, right. She's at the top of the North Tower,
but I don't think there's any way
you'll ever get in there.
Lupin?
Yikes. What a lousy place to be locked up in.
Come on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Catch it.
Who are you?
I am a thief.
Did you say thief?
Good evening, Miss Bride.
You helped me. I remember you.
You forgot this.
You came to give me this back when you know the
Count would kill you if he found you here.
Aiming for a prize you're being aimed
at, it's all part of the job.
And once the job's done, I'll leave.
The job?
If I had anything of value here I
could offer you, I would.
But I'm a prisoner. Oh. Take this.
This time I seek a priceless treasure sealed in the
top of a tall tower by an evil sorcerer.
Uh...
Would you please allow this thief
to steal you away from here?
Steal me?
To rescue jewels and riches that
are trapped inside a safe.
Yes, to stop a forced marriage and release the girl
to run in the grassy fields of freedom.
All of these jobs are perfect for a thief.
You've come all this way to free me?
Thank you. I'm grateful.
But I don't think you noticed how terrible
the House of Cagliostro truly is.
Please, just leave.
Oh, I can't believe this.
This lovely sweet girl believes in
the powers of the wicked evil
sorcerer, yet somehow refuses to believe
in the powers of the thief.
If the girl would only believe, the thief
could take to the skies above.
He could drink up all the water in the
lake if only she'd believe.
But for now, this'll have to do.
Sir Thief!
Hey, show the lady the respect she deserves.
Thank you for coming all this way
to deliver the ring, Lupin.
I am so deeply honored by this welcome party, Count.
That's touching, but you're going away now.
Oh, really? You think it'll be that
easy to get rid of me?
Hey, please! Leave him alone! Don't hurt him!
It'll be okay, Missy. You've just
got to believe in the thief.
Monsieur!
Yes, the Monsieur is right here. Don't worry.
He'll be back real soon, okay?
So, what's the game gonna be?
Tearing you apart would be too easy,
but I'd rather not sully
the bride's room with the blood of an
inconsequential sneak-thief.
Call me names if you want, but you're
going to regret it.
It was nice of you to drop in.
That hole leads to a foul Hell of a place
that no one has ever escaped from.
So innocent, and yet you've attracted
a man to your side.
That's the Cagliostro blood at work.
You deserve to be my wife.
Murderer! You're an inhuman monster!
How true. My hands are covered in blood,
but yours are no different.
For generations, my family has served
in the shadow of yours,
overseeing schemes and assassinations
to support this country.
Let go of me! You disgust me!
You can't tell me you didn't know.
You are of Cagliostro blood as well.
The same ancient blood of the Goths that flows
through my veins flows through yours.
Oh, Clarisse, it's been over 400 years now.
The two houses of light and shadow
have been kept apart.
With light and shadow as one once more,
it shall surely be restored.
This is the golden goat of my family.
Your ring, bearing the silver goat,
will become one with mine
to restore the hidden treasure of our ancestors.
Oh, I totally heard that. A marriage
for treasure, is it?
It's him.
Count on a counterfeiting Count for all
his words and deeds to be a sham.
The girl is a very kind hearted, wonderful young lady.
Monsieur! Are you all right?
Yes, alive and well.
Thanks to the girl's belief in him,
he can even take to the skies.
Sir Thief will come and steal you away for sure.
Just you wait.
Yes.
Blast him, it's the ring.
Give me.
Hey, Count, you listen here.
I got the real ring. You even lay
a finger on that girl.
And here's what I'll do to your precious ring.
It's a fake.
Dump me down a sewer, will you? Well poo to you.
He fell?
Probably.
Make sure
No man could possibly exist down there for long.
If we leave him, he'll die for certain, Excellency.
That little weasel still has the ring.
I'll check immediately, sir.
You'll see. I'll have that petty little thief
of yours, flayed and quartered.
Over 400 years of killing, killing and more killing.
Rest in peace.
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
1904, Japanese Army scout Inosuke Kawakami died here.
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Japanese Army Scout
Gennosuke
Kawakami
perished here
Avenge
Avenge me.
Hmm?
Ah! Lupin! You! You're under arrest!
Hey, Pops, how are you still alive?
I'll be asking the questions. How'd you get in here?
Oh, I dropped in just like you.
Looks like you've been walking for quite a while now.
Shut up! I don't want pity for a thief.
I think we should take it easy. There's
no way out, after all.
May I borrow this seat, pal?
Hey, Pops. Got a light?
Hey, Lupin, what's the deal with the skeletons?
It doesn't seem like a gravesite.
Take a look at the wall there.
Huh?
This... this message...
May you rest in peace.
I figured this was no ordinary castle.
What could be worth going this far to keep a secret?
Is that why you're here?
No, it's why Fujicakes is here. Hope she
fares better than us right now.
Anyway, grumbling about it won't get us anywhere.
Good night, Pops.
Man, would you look at the time. See anything yet?
No, nothing yet.
Nothing to do but wait.
What's keeping them?
Master Jodot, look!
Hmm. Ah, well done.
Heave! Heave!
Toodles!
Don't leave us here!
Huh? This is a coffin.
Huh?
What kind of place is this?
Hey.
These are 10,000 yen bills.
And so's this whole heap.
Ooh. Exceptional quality.
Check it out, pops.
Huh? These marked bills are from Germany.
Pounds. Dollars. Franks. Rubles.
Rupies. Pesos. Crowns. Lira.
Whoa.
Even Chinese Yuan.
They got the whole world covered.
Ah, printing counterfeits.
Lupin, this is the castle's secret!
That's right.
The home of the Gothic bills.
Better than the real thing, some would even say.
Fake money's been a shadowy player in every European
upheaval since the Middle Ages.
It brought down the Bourbon dynasty
by helping fund Napoleon.
And in 1927, it was the trigger behind
the Great Depression.
The hidden player on the dark side of history?
Gothic bills.
And anyone who tried to find its source never escaped.
I had heard the rumors before, but I'd never imagined
it was the work of a sovereign nation.
What are you gonna do, pops?
Now that you've seen it, you can't just unsee it.
I know that.
No good cop could ignore this.
How about a truce, just until we get out of here?
Okay. But I won't aid in a better criminal.
Once we've escaped, you're under
arrest for good this time.
Fantastic.
Hey, pops, why don't we shake on it?
That's collusion.
Hmm?
Ms. Fujiko.
I've come to say goodbye to you while I still can.
What are you doing?
I was hired to be milady's handmaiden, the
only other woman in the castle.
But the truth is, I'm a spy hunting
for the secret of this castle.
I planned to stick around longer, but Lupin showed up.
He'll mess up everything, so I need to go.
You know that gentlemen?
Mm-hmm. Better than I wish I did.
Sometimes friends, sometimes adversaries.
I suppose we've even been lovers, too.
He's an infamous womanizer. Be careful.
Did he leave you?
Are you kidding? I left.
- Smoke's coming from the trap door.
- Fire.
It's coming from the basement!
- Movement.
- Finally, some action.
Sir! The fire started down in the printing plant!
Then get down there and put it out!
Yes, sir!
And shut that door! You all go, too!
Jodot, you have failed once again.
Shake a leg, Pops! We're gonna have
company here real soon!
Evidence! I need evidence!
Curse that Lupin!
Find him! I'm sure he's still in here.
What are you waiting for? Get in there!
Hurry! Lupin's getting away!
Put out the fire!
It's the chapel.
It's Monsieur.
What are they doing?
Lupin! And Zenigata?
They're after the autogyro.
You idiot!
You can reprimand me later, sir! He's
after Lady Clarisse! Hurry!
Hurry it up!
I'm from Interpol!
Pops, get on!
Come on, Pops!
Sayonara!
Hey, Pops! I'm gonna make a quick pit stop!
Are you gonna kidnap her?
Yes, but it's non-profit.
He's coming this way!
It's bulletproof glass!
We can't open it! Please just go without me!
Up there!
Here, you take the wheel!
What? Hey, Lupin! I've never done this before!
Here we are.
Clarisse?
Monsieur!
Your chariot awaits, milady. Fujiko, some rope.
Don't boss me around!
Behind you!
There you are! You're safe now.
Pops! Put it down over here!
You think I'm not trying, you maniac!
All right, that's good!
Easy!
Lupin!
Don't you move, you meddling rat!
Fujiko, I will look forward to
interrogating you later.
Jodot, go ahead and finish off Lupin.
Right!
No, please don't shoot him! If you kill
him, then I shall die as well!
Fire!
I admire your attitude, Clarisse.
Take back the ring from him and come here.
If you marry me, I will agree to spare Lupin's life.
Or you can both die here and now. The choice is yours.
The ring, Monsieur, let me have it.
Don't do it, Clarisse. You just can't.
In his collar, he always hides things under there.
Darn you, Fujiko!
Here is the ring. Now spare this man and miss Fujiko's
life, or I swear to you, I will throw it in the lake!
You have my word. Put on the ring and come to me.
Shall I shoot?
Wait till I have the ring.
Shoot them down!
You horrible liar! You gave your word!
They've seen the printing presses. I'd
never let them leave here alive.
It's in my hands at last.
Lupin, let's just say you owe me one, okay?
Later!
Now we gotta go without getting in on the fun?
We're going down!
Jump for it!
Again I have cut a worthless object.
Lupin, come back here so I can arrest you!
Right, this could be a very big problem.
If anyone finds out.
These fake bills, I've never seen anything like them.
Let us take action! We have this
indisputable evidence!
I saw it myself! Counterfeit printing
presses lined up!
We understand that, Inspector.
This is a very sensitive political problem.
Our jurisdiction at Interpol is limited
only to international crimes.
What do you mean? This is clearly criminal activity!
You just don't get it.
They're sovereign state and a member of the UN. Interpol
can't conduct a forced investigation.
In addition, the situation is not in our favor.
Did you see the picture that's on the front
page of every newspaper in the world?
The Count who bravely protected his bride against
Lupin who tried to abduct Princess Clarisse?
And he apparently had an accomplice disguised as you.
That was all me, I was there!
That's a problem. It makes it seem as though
you were colluding with Lupin.
Did you forget? I told you what happened!
The issue is, who is the public gonna believe?
They won't believe you.
The Count supposedly has a lot of political
friends in the west.
That alone could be a big problem for some countries.
Especially for a certain country that placed
a huge order for fake American bills.
And I suppose these fake rubles weren't
ordered by your CIA.
Gentlemen, stop! This is not the place
for international disputes.
Gentlemen, please! Each country will decide
how to deal with the Gothic bills.
Inspector, we're prepared to mobilize. Ready to
depart for the Principality of Cagliostro.
We're not going, sir.
As soon as they find a suitable replacement for
us, we'll be taken off the Lupin case.
Prepare to return to Japan.
It's me.
Here's some food.
Great. Thanks, pal.
How's your friend doing?
His fever seems to have gone down. Thanks
to you operating on him.
It's that dog you should really give thanks to.
That old dog is friendly to no one, but he
won't budge from that man's side.
If not for that, I probably wouldn't
have offered you folks shelter.
Hey, Karl.
He's finally awake.
Lupin, how are you feeling?
Jigen. Goemon. Long time, no see.
Long time? What are you talking about?
His wounds have temporarily impaired his memory.
Karl? How come you're not with
your mistress today, huh?
How in the world could you possibly
know that dog's name is Karl?
I thought the only ones still around here who knew
it were myself and the lady Clarisse.
Clarisse?
So, Karl, the name of your mistress
is Clarisse, is that right?
Clarisse.
Lupin?
Jigen, tell me what day it is. How
many days has it been?
It's been three.
Three days? The wedding is tomorrow.
I can't...
You shouldn't push it, Lupin. You'll
reopen your wounds.
I need some food. Bring me some food.
Food meaning what? Oatmeal?
I'm low on blood. Doesn't matter.
Just keep it coming, okay?
- That won't be so easy.
- Don't worry. I'll get it for you.
Hey, Dummy, quit stuffing your face or
you'll throw it all back up.
Butt out, will ya? I'll be good as new in half a day.
I told ya, you need a bucket, huh?
Huh? What's that?
He's gotta get some rest.
I had no idea all of this was for Lady Clarisse.
But with Lupin in rough shape like this,
it would seem that you have had much
history with Lady Clarisse.
I used to be the palace groundskeeper.
As a child, Lady Clarisse loved plants.
When the prince and his wife passed away
and she was to enter the convent,
she entrusted this dog to me.
So when the dog got a whiff of Lupin, he must
have noticed the princess's scent.
But that still doesn't explain how
Lupin knew Karl's name.
Hey, he's a lady's man. Maybe he
charmed it out of her.
It's nothing like that.
Already awake, huh?
It happened ten years ago. I was young and inexperienced,
eager to set out and make a name for myself.
Lupin
I did some crazy things. Real showy.
To top it all off, I went after the gothic bills.
I managed to pull myself up onto the shore somehow,
but then I couldn't move another inch.
Karl? What's wrong, boy?
I really thought I had come to the end of the road.
Water?
Her little hands trembled as she
helped me drink the water,
and the ring was on her finger.
I'm ashamed to admit it.
I'd forgotten all about it until I saw the ring again.
Fujiko's bike.
It's a clipping from today's paper.
Tomorrow an archbishop is arriving from the
Vatican for the wedding ceremony.
I officially resign.
Fujiko?
What? Lupin's gonna hit the wedding? You sure?
Yes, I am. And if you're in pursuit of
Lupin, you can mobilize, right?
You're right. It's perfect.
Hey, could you get out of the way? We're in a hurry.
There's nowhere to go. This jam
goes on for miles, man.
Yeah, they said there's a landslide up the road.
But isn't that any other way to get to there?
We'll be late for the wedding.
By-golly, aren't you the fine Lord Archbishop?
Ah, just as I reckoned it.
Would you be so kind as to bless
this little baby goat?
Amen.
You're a local. Is there any other way to
get to Cagliostro Castle from here?
Sure is, if-n-you don't mind country roads.
Of course not. Would you show me the
way there? Hop in, please.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. Anything to help out the archbishop.
Keep it up, men! We have to get there by nightfall!
One more hill and we'll reach the border!
Do you think this is a good idea?
Televising the wedding?
His Excellency wishes to show the world his wedding
to Lady Clarisse is a legitimate one.
Ah! His Grace, the archbishop, has arrived.
Do you think Lupin will show up?
My shadows will be closely watching over the bride.
All your men have to do is guard the gate.
Yes, sir.
With light and shadow as one once more
it shall surely be restored.
Come.
The House of Cagliostro is an ancient and noble family.
Bring here the proof that you are the rightful heirs.
In accordance with the old customs, the exchange
of rings constitute your marriage vows.
Daughter of the Prince of the Principality of Cagliostro,
Clarisse de Cagliostro, do your consent to this marriage.
If you do not object, respond with silence.
May the Lord above bless you and keep you.
I object.
These marriage rites are profoundly tainted by greed.
This is a curse.
Don't panic.
An uninvited rat's making his entrance.
I have come to speak on behalf of the
dead in the dungeon below.
I want the bride.
We can't go on like this.
Just step back.
Enjoy the show.
Clarisse, I've come for you.
Something incredible has happened.
Lupin the Third has appeared.
Stop the broadcast.
What are you doing?
Please wait one moment
Let's go.
Clarisse, Clarisse, poor thing.
You've been drugged, haven't you?
The rotten count drugged you so you couldn't speak.
Oh, Monsieur!
You must not get closer, my dear.
That was foolish.
Take care of the other two as well.
Clarisse, don't cry, Clarisse.
I'm coming to get you.
I wonder if this gift will be to your liking, Count.
- Excellency.
- The counterfeit bills you printed.
Consider them my payment for the rings.
Find him.
He's here somewhere.
Now I've got the rings.
It's you, Lupin.
Monsieur!
How dare you play me for a fool!
You cradle robber, don't play with fire.
Or you'll get... burned!
Take this!
Lupin!
Ladies and gentlemen, we will now
resume our broadcast.
The wedding hall is in utter chaos.
Well, gotta go.
Die!
Don't let him get away, come on!
Lupin's gotten away and the Count is hot on his heels.
The police have stormed the castle.
Lupin's hiding under the altar.
Make a hole, men! Charge!
Zenigata's men are making a path to the altar.
Oh, here's the royal guardsmen.
They're led by Captain Gustav.
Secure the rear men.
Give no quarter!
A fierce battle's in progress.
What secret could that altar be hiding?
Look, it's a staircase leading underground.
Could Lupin be hiding down in that hole?
Let's take a camera and see, okay?
Come on, let's go!
- Lupin!
- What's that imbecile doing?
He's ignoring orders, call him off!
Too late, it's airing live worldwide now.
Whoa, what's all this?
This looks like a national mint!
Mmm, what's that over there?
Oh, wow, Japanese bills.
They must be counterfeit!
Talk about hamming it up.
What a find!
Look at this, counterfeits from everywhere.
I found this dreadful stuff while
I was chasing after Lupin.
What do I do?
First things first, let's get out of here.
Jigen, Goemon, you good?
Leave it to us.
- We'll hold them off.
- C'mon.
Gentlemen, I beg of you to be careful.
and you Noble Jigen?
Please make sure that you both return safely.
I will never forget your chivalry.
You should go quickly.
Hurry up, Clarisse.
Coming!
- Noble Jigen.
- Beautiful.
Let's start this party.
Finally, my Zantetsuken has cut something meaningful.
Curse that Lupin, this isn't over yet!
I'll attend to the castle, Your Grace.
Do you still hurt?
Nah, I'm over that.
Now, let's get over this.
Two goats facing each other.
There are gothic letters carved on the
seam, binding light and shadow.
Oh, they're too worn down to read.
Binding light and shadow, tolling the hours is the
goat on high, and whose sun-facing eyes I belong.
I remember they are ancient words that were
passed down through my family.
Are they of help to you?
Yes, the riddle is solved at last.
I's the Count. This way.
They are going to the machinery room. Moor the boat.
Good.
Up there.
Ooh, they're coming in hot.
Let's go.
Shut down all the lasers. Does that
fool think they can escape?
- You scared?
- No.
That's wonderful. Come on.
Got him!
Uh-oh.
Can't go that way.
You men go over there. Take the stairs.
Yes, sir.
Okay, stay here. I'm gonna block the entrance.
Be careful.
Be back in a jiffy.
There he is!
Huh?
Run!
Monsieur! Behind you!
You missed me.
You rat! I shall skewer you.
Take your best shot. It's your last chance, Count.
And...
One more.
Hey! I dare you to come get me, Countypants.
Monsieur!
I'll start by taking care of you first.
Clarisse, get out of here! I'm coming!
Where do you think you're going, Clarisse?
Come on, my dear. What's wrong?
Nowhere to run.
And so ends the Cagliostro bloodline.
Now die, Clarisse.
Wait a minute, Count. Let's make a deal.
It's too late. Just stand there and
watch as this woman dies.
Just listen to me.
I'll tell you the secret of the rings.
You can take the treasure and do
whatever you want with it.
Just leave the girl alone. Set her free.
Look, the Capricorn on the clock face.
That's the goat which faces the
sun and tolls the hours.
It's got two holes in its eyes
that the rings fit into.
I'll let you have the rings.
But if you kill Clarisse, I will
throw them in the lake
and then I will kill you.
Okay, that's far enough. Let Clarisse go inside.
All right. I understand.
Lupin, you have to hold your winning
card to the final hand.
Come on.
They're the genuine articles this
time and now they're mine.
Here's your payment for solving the riddle, Lupin.
Oh, no!
Clarisse!
Let go!
Ah! The clock tower!
Ah! Your Grace!
What in the world?
Count Cagliostro's reign is over.
Please.
No, I will not take your life.
- Monsieur.
- Hey, can you stand? Feast your eyes.
The real hidden treasure.
I had no idea there was a Roman city beneath the lake.
When the Romans were driven from this land, they
built that floodgate and submerged it.
And your ancestors quietly inherited it.
Good.
It's amazing. A treasure that belongs
to all of mankind.
Besides, there's no way it'll fit in my pocket.
Interpol finally sprang into action.
Will you be leaving now?
Hmm? Yeah. A lot of scary men just showed up, so...
Please, take me with you. I don't have the
skills of a thief, but I can learn.
Oh, please, I want to...
Please, I want to go with you.
Oh, Clarisse.
Now, don't give me that silly talk.
You don't want to go back into the darkness again,
when it took you so long to find your
way to the sunlight, right?
You belong right here. Your whole
life is just beginning.
The life of a thief is no life for you.
But if you're ever in trouble, call me anytime,
and I will come running, even if it's from the
far reaches of the Earth, I promise.
Karl, it's you!
Karl!
Lady Clarisse.
Hi, Gramps.
Toodles Clarisse!
Monsieur!
So long, Princess.
Wait, Monsieur!
Bye, Clarisse. You take care.
Goodbye now.
Thank you so much, everyone. So long.
So long!
Goodbye. Goodbye!
Darn. Just missed him again.
He got away with another treasure.
No, he didn't steal anything, Inspector.
He saved my life and fought for my honor.
No, Miss. He ran off with a tremendous
prize in his hands.
Your heart, milady.
Yes.
Well then. Good day, Miss.
After Lupin, to the ends of the Earth!
Searching out happiness
Is how I want to make my way
Even thorny paths and freezing cold nights
What an intriguing bunch of fellows they were.
I want to traverse, the two of us together
I feel as though I have known that gentleman
from a very long time ago.
Lupin, I know we'll meet again someday.
The bleak heart of the traveler
She was a nice girl, wasn't she?
You know, Lupin, you could stay here if you wanted.
Who will be there to embrace it?
Who will make those dreams come true?
Oh, hey, Fujicakes.
Hey, Lupin. Take a look at what I scored.
Hmm? The master printing plate's
for the counterfeit bills.
That's great. Let me have one.
See ya.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
A flame, it burns passionately
Hey, just hold on a sec. We could trade.
Here comes Pops. He never gives up.
This love of mine
You won't get away this time.
Lupin!
I want for you to understand, and you alone
Wrap me up in the bond we share
Fin