Here's an audio commentary.
I'm Sato. I worked on the set
and the script. I'll be your host today.
We have two guests today. Let me
introduce them one by one.
The first person is... please go ahead.
Hi, I'm Kouichi Yamadera,
voice of Spike.
Good to be here. Thanks.
Yes, our second guest...
Let's see... I'm... Jet.
That sure took you a while!
You had to think hard to remember?!
- How is that possible?!
- Unbelievable! You're confusing us!
All right. I'm Unsho Ishizuka,
voice of Jet.
At least he remembered his own name.
- At least!
- He couldn't remember the name "Jet".
He was just hemming and hawing.
I wasn't sure if I should say his
full name. You know... like... Black Jet?
- Or Jet Black?
- Oh, yeah.
That's pretty bad...
Then, let's try Spike's full name.
You guys are mean...
We'll give you a little test.
- His last name's Spiegel, isn't it?
- Right.
Hey, it's already started.
That was the first line of the series.
So what's this thing called? Commen...
- Audio commentary.
- I've been looking forward to this.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You haven't done it before?
- No.
This is really my first time.
- It's cool you can watch it and hear us.
- Yeah. I love that.
But you have to wonder how many
people will actually switch the tracks.
Yeah... really.
So, this is the first episode and
the first time these characters speak.
Yes. It begins with the Chinese dish,
"Julienned beef and bell peppers."
Do you remember?
I just remember the julienned beef
and bell pepper Chinese dish.
But I wasn't sure
what the setting was.
Now I'm watching it,
I understand better.
Back then we were still
kind of fumbling our way.
Those characters weren't
finalized yet.
- That's right.
- It was only the first episode.
The picture was still messy, too.
Oops, can I say that?
Basically, the picture wasn't
this clear back then.
But Jet was scary-looking
like this from the get-go.
Yeah, he was kinda cute.
- That's what I was aiming for.
- Wait a minute.
You're going a little too far...
I was aiming for cutesy idol-ish style.
You mean like Akira Ishida?
Right. I was trying to imitate him.
Let's hear it.
Why don't you do Jet in his voice?
Here's Akira Ishida's version of Jet.
Take it away.
Julienned beef...
At least you gave it a try.
I also wasn't sure how to
characterize Spike.
As I recall, wasn't he the first
main character you ever dubbed?
- In a TV series? Yes.
- Oh, really?
Yes. It's true.
And I didn't do much after that, either.
You're just saying that.
It's probably because you're too great
to be asked to do serialized shows.
Scenes like these were mind-boggling.
I couldn't grasp the concept just by
listening to the explanation.
I was clueless. Even when they described
my character, I didn't quite get it.
But, in substance, it's more of a
human drama than a SF story.
Right. This episode in particular...
featured the friendship between
these two guys.
But it's a brilliant as SF with a nice
balance of CG and anime and all that.
It's almost amateur-like. I don't know
if I can call it that.
It was unprecedented for
a TV series.
What about this whistling?
Didn't you do it yourself?
- Yeah, I did.
- It's coming back to you, huh?
Yeah, I remember it well, too.
I said I'd do it myself. They told me
they needed sort of a listless song.
So I just did it on the fly.
- Oh, it was ad-libbed?
- It sure was.
Really? Ad-libbed?
I was intimidated because Yoko Kanno,
the genius, was doing the music, ya' know.
That goes to show you how clueless
I was back then.
He came up with a very listless song.
I thought he was a genius.
Well, I'm flattered.
Now I need to praise you, Unsho-san.
No, you don't have to. I'm serious.
That's really how I felt.
What they requested was
kind of complicated.
Right.
It had to sound kinda listless,
but it had to sound cool in a way, too.
If I remember correctly,
that's what they asked for.
I don't remember anything but
something trivial like that.
At that point, Unsho-san and I were
the only regular characters.
- That's right.
- Oh, yeah.
It was just two of us and
some incidental guests.
Later on, those old guys joined us.
Yeah, you're right. They were there.
They appeared very frequently. They
were there till the end of the movie.
Yeah, those three old guys...
They were main incidentals.
Here they are.
I don't know what it was, but they
somehow managed to show up.
I always wondered
how they moved around.
- They showed up everywhere.
- They sure did.
Do you remember their names?
What? Taro, Jiro... Saburo...
Wasn't it?
- Carlos... Antonio, Carlos and Jobin.
- That's right.
Actually that's the name of
a bossa nova composer.
Oh, really. I didn't know.
I've just found out.
You mean one person?
It's one person by the name of
Antonio Carlos Jobin.
At this point their names weren't
in the script yet. Right?
That's correct.
It was like Old Man 1, Old Man 2...
But maybe Nabeshin-san already had
that name in mind.
And these two... they were the guests
in the first episode.
She's got big boobs.
I was stunned.
You're too much... stunned by
big boobs in an anime?!
At any rate it was awesome.
This setup was awesome, too.
I don't know if I can say this because
it wasn't aired on a certain TV station...
That's true.
This was completely cut, and it didn't
really get going until the next episode.
Yeah, at first, it almost looked like
Ein the dog was the main character.
I thought this was the best plot ever.
When I watched Episode 1, it looked
too mature for the early evening slot.
Yeah, because the first episode was
advertised on a late night show.
Ah! Boobs!
Boobs and Carlos Jobin, huh?
So, it was advertised on TV?
Yes, it was talked about
during a live TV talk show.
Right. There was a segment dedicated
to the show airing later that day.
This particular scene would have
never been shown in that segment.
This is a little too hairy.
That was an eye drop, right?
Yeah, an eye drop caused that.
Usually an eye drop reduces red-eye,
but this one caused it.
These images were mind-boggling.
Look at this.
Only people who've experienced it
would know what it's like.
Oh, come on. That's not true.
- Hey, that's sort of a scary thought.
- Really. That's dangerous.
Unsho-san's getting dangerous.
You know... you're being zeroed in on!
What do you mean? What did I do?
Someone tipped you off.
Anyway, the show was full of
elements like that... like tip-offs.
At the end I was tipped off.
I just have to wonder...
While making Episode 1, did the staff
want to make it sensational?
At first the staff didn't know
what the director was shooting for.
We sort of figured it out
as we created the first 5 to 6 episodes.
- This is very different from others.
- I've never seen anything like this.
Particularly... when you think about
the fact that this is a TV series.
You're right.
I wonder how the budget was managed.
Impossible!
This is impossible for a TV series.
- Yeah, it was reckless.
- But Unsho-san was impressive.
It wasn't me alone.
- It was a certain group of people.
- No, it's not that...
A certain group of people...
We'll just leave it at that.
This guy... he was mysterious.
I didn't know what he was.
- A Prophet.
- Yeah. He appeared a couple of times.
Right. He was in a movie, too.
He shows up in important scenes.
- Right. Bull.
- He's called Bull.
He's Ms. Nobumoto's creation.
She likes to add characters like that.
Yes. You see someone like him
in every episode.
- Unsho-san really likes Ms. Nobumoto.
- Right.
It's the other way round. She likes me.
Yeah, right.
It's been rumored lately that
my figure has changed a little.
Well, this conversation's going to be
made public, so let's be careful.
You know, it could come back
to bite you.
It they cut this part out, there'll be
a blank spot.
I just said that my figure changed.
I never mentioned how it changed.
I guess this guy is saying
something important. I wasn't listening.
This is when he's mentioning Julia.
The beginning of the first episode
is suggestive but chaotic as well.
You never got any explanation
when you first started out?
- No.
- There was none.
I think it was more like,
"OK. Let's get started."
After that first scene, Jet and Spike
show up as partners out of the blue.
So, that was crazy and funny.
They're not that close as partners.
The most unlikely guys paired up
and that was kinda interesting.
One is a former cop and the other is
former Mafia.
- Oh, yeah, I used to be a cop.
- That's right.
- So things are coming back to you.
- Yeah, finally.
I thought I used to be a truck driver.
Well, that would be
Tomie Kataoka's character.
- Oh, yeah.
- There was something like that.
Here's a different scene.
He's using this like a bike.
It's so cool. All the machines in here
are just awesome.
He's always hungry, too.
Yeah, that's true.
At first I thought there would be
more funny scenes.
- This whistling...
- It was also ad-libbed.
The difference between serious and
funny scenes are extreme in the show.
Right. Also no particular effort is
made to make the audience laugh.
- That's true.
- Unsho-san said very few gags.
Gags... I hardly said any.
- In real life you like gags, right?
- Not really.
- I'm a serious type.
- You, on the other hand, like puns.
Oh, no. At least not like Mr. Hirokawa.
I'm not too crazy about puns.
Here's a scene in a restroom.
How long has it been?
- Six or seven?
- Long, long time ago, right?
I don't wanna say something
to be frowned upon, but...
I was gonna make him say
something like "because it smells bad..."
But I was told not to.
Maybe "It stinks" or something.
- No. That wouldn't work.
- It's not funny when you try too hard.
- The first half has ended?!
- Yep. It's over.
It's so dense.
Besides, it's so "stylish." Look.
Right here!
Oh, no. How pathetic!
- Why?
- Right here!
- A woman meets a man.
- You almost think it's a gag.
When I spit it out,
I use a little trick.
I say the first part of "Excuse me"
with my mouth full.
Oh, I see.
I wasn't sure if I could do a gag like
Lupin or City Hunter would.
I ad-lib something
off-camera after this.
Right here. Right here!
Now I think about it, Spike shouldn't
have said anything like that.
You'd only think that after 26 episodes.
When we were recording Episode 1,
we had no clue.
Using a wallet as an excuse, huh?
In all 26 episodes that was the only
time I ad-libbed a stupid gag like that.
- Oh, really.
- Yes.
Wasn't the director frowning?
I think the director just couldn't
say no back then.
He couldn't tell me to stop.
Mr. Kobayashi was probably thinking
"Whatever..."
He probably thought the show was
like that to begin with.
Do you establish your character
by exploring little by little?
In my case... I'm not sure
if I could say that...
At the audition I asked them
how they wanted me to act.
They asked me to be myself.
"Myself?" I asked, and they said
they wanted me the way I was.
So, I just did it the way
I naturally would.
Then, they said, "Fine."
I never changed anything!
So, there was absolutely
no performance notes, Unsho-san?
Oh, it's not that. It's just
that's all I can do and nothing else.
It's no different than talking about
golf with people at the studio.
So you can use the same tone of voice
when performing, too?
Exactly.
I had to work harder than that.
I see. It was different in Spike's case.
But, in the end,
I wasn't really thinking.
Basically... he had to sound calm,
aloof and natural.
I was always told not to try too hard.
Yeah. That's right.
Did you still try too hard?
As a voice actor I couldn't help it.
I worked with Mr. Watanabe on
another show before this.
You didn't remember that though...
It was like, "Have we met before?"
"I directed the previous show."
"Ah, you're the director?"
"How do you do? Happy to meet you."
"Well, we already met on the show
before this."
"What? What did you do?"
- "I was the director."
- It wasn't like he was just observing!
So I was thinking... was he there?
- No matter.
- He WAS the director!
But I'm glad I met him.
I worked on anime a little before.
But this was the first time I was asked
to talk naturally.
It was really comfortable for me.
I would say it was even more natural
than dubbing foreign movies.
Yes. Yes. Yes. I agree.
It was like doing a live action movie
and they just took the voices.
It was really easy for me.
I don't know if I should be
saying it was easy.
Today we wouldn't be able to create
main characters who smoke so much.
- Yeah. Things have certainly changed.
- Good point.
You're absolutely right.
Also each prop was very elaborate.
The lighter we saw earlier was cool.
There they are.
- They sound young.
- Do you think you sound young?
You think so?
Yeah.
Were you already playing
Professor Oak back then?
Back then...
I might have been...
It was about the same time.
Were you doing "Good Morning Studios?"
- Let's see...
- You advertised this show in it?
- Oh, yeah.
- I must have been already doing it then.
"Good Morning Studios" has been
on the air for 8 years.
- I might have started it midway...
- How old is this first episode?
- Six or...
- You were going full swing back then.
No... after we got started...
I remember saying I couldn't continue
after the fall because...
- I'll be in the early morning show.
- Oh, yeah...
I think it was after we had recorded
two or three episodes.
It was smack in the
middle of transition.
- It pretty much overlaps then.
- It must've been seven years ago.
Yeah, that sounds right.
I'm positive it was
around the same time.
- Yeah, a few episodes were done first.
- Right. Then you went on air.
You went on the morning show
after some episodes had been recorded.
You tried to advertise the show
but you were still unclear about it.
So you probably gave up
and tried to quit.
Then, we were always talking about
going out for drinks in Shibuya.
I think we recorded in May or June.
Then we recorded a few each month.
We did it sporadically.
The production schedule was relaxed.
Right. We recorded over a long time.
There was no on-air schedule at first.
- They didn't know when it was gonna air.
- That's correct.
And as soon as the schedule was set,
the first episode was cut.
- That's right!
- It didn't see the light of the day.
- When did Aoi start to appear?
- In Episode 9.
Then, when he auditioned,
he was a 9th or 10th grader?!
We were talking about that earlier.
- When he auditioned, he was 15 or so.
- But now he's 23.
He's old enough to get married.
He's old enough to be a father.
Wait a minute! Don't go too far.
Unsho-san has five grandchildren, right?
Hey, no way.
I have no children or grandchildren.
You might have one somewhere.
- There might be a posthumous child.
- Well, grandpa is working hard!
Come on. That's not it.
Maybe we should talk more about
the show, don't you think?
Something about the story?
No, it's all right.
Right here he looks like a real
mean character with that sombrero.
The action scene right after this was
breathtakingly cool.
It was almost like Kung Fu.
It reminds you of good ol' Bruce Lee.
The moves were amazing, though.
I couldn't see it while recording.
Right. You just saw the line art.
Which episode did we see when
it was finished? We all applauded.
- Yeah, we watched this together.
- Was it this episode?
- We watched this when it was done.
- Oh, was it the first episode?
I'm sure we watched Episode 1 together
when it was completed.
I was like, "I'm in such a great show?"
- It was so much fun.
- Yes. Yes.
- The music was awesome, too.
- Right. Music added so much to it.
Yeah, I was really impressed.
Even after so many years we can
still enjoy it.
I'm positive this will last a lifetime.
Honestly...
- The camera work is amazing...
- The fact I was part of it...
almost miraculous to me,
because this happened to be
my debut.
Right. I was very surprised
to hear that.
I thought you had done a lot more
work before this.
My workload increased after this.
We owe our careers to everyone involved.
Is that so?
- That's kinda goofy.
- What are you saying?!
What we said was, this was maybe
Mr. Sato's debut work, but thanks to...
all the other creative staff, it became
a huge hit and we all benefited from it!
I can't believe you spaced out
on us!
Later on, I worked on other projects
with people I met on this show.
I see.
For example, we did "Wolf's Rain"
together, remember?
Oh... yeah...
That's right. It was also written
by Ms. Nobumoto.
She wrote it with me in mind.
I don't know why she though I'd be
perfect as an alcoholic character.
It was quite a character.
We also worked together
on "Stand Alone Complex".
That's right.
"Stand Alone Complex"...
Then, once again, we worked together
in "Samurai Champloo"...
Mr. Watanabe directed that, too.
- I see.
- This was the beginning of everything.
What a history...
Anyway, the show was full of
battles and fights and...
everything was condensed
in one episode.
It's just flawless.
It might not have been suitable
for the young morning show audience.
Right. It might have been too much
for children.
Every segment is so cool and awesome.
I've never seen anything this cool.
In a way, a lot of non-anime fans
became hooked because of this show.
That kept the show alive
for a long time.
That's true for the people I know.
The designer who designed the clothes
I'm wearing today got hooked...
and... so did some musicians.
- Yeah, many of them...
- Really.
The other day I was invited to go see
Mr. Children's live concert...
James and Mr. Nakagawa are both
huge fans of Cowboy Bebop.
When I talked to them after the concert,
they said they had already placed
an order for the box.
You know... this box...
the special edition of DVDs.
- That's amazing.
- Some people don't even know about it!
Unsho-san, do you even know
why we're recording this today?
This will be the bonus material
for the DVDs in the special box.
What did you think this was for?
I thought maybe they were
re-mastering the DVD or something.
- You know, something like that.
- At least you knew about the DVDs.
Sort of. I guess I was half right,
but completely out of touch...
A special box version will be released.
Ah, this is close to the ending.
This was such a cool scene.
Spike was desperately trying to...
She said "Adios!" How cool is that?
I see.
It's just too cool.
She blew up and scattered like a flower.
Look at this! It's too much!
After this show aired...
I realized a lot of people
from our industry watched it, too.
I was asked to narrate some clips
for a news show and I asked why.
They decided after watching
Cowboy Bebop.
WHAT?!!!
- I was asked to do it just like Bebop.
- For a news show?! It's serious stuff!
Someone decided on the narrator
because he watched this show?!
So I did a series of Iraq War segments
in the same style as Jet.
- Just like that?
- Right.
I was really surprised.
Maybe some kickback is due...
You know... part of your guarantee...
Oh, this was a cool shot, too.
It means the news show staff was
also watching Cowboy Bebop.
Sure. Many news guys in their 30's
are watching it. They're fans.
On other occasions I've been asked
to do things like Jet.
Ah... it ended.
Well, we kind of babbled away.
What? It's over?
I wanted to talk more!
I'd like to ask both of you,
though it's been so long...
to briefly share your thoughts on
the show, Cowboy Bebop.
- Why don't we start with Unsho-san?
- What? Me?
I watched it after a long absence,
but I really think it's a great show.
The music was fantastic.
I say this all the time, but...
the music and animation are
perfectly matched.
So when you hear the opening music
that goes "Tah-dah-dah-dah-dah..."
you almost feel the tingles
running down your spine.
It really gets you prepared
for the show to start.
Then, when you hear the ending song,
you're like, "Ah! What a great story!"
- Even now... at the age of 53.
- Wow, that old?
Yeah, I feel really old.
Even at such an age, I really like it.
I think it's really a great show.
I'd like to get the special box version
and enjoy it thoroughly.
What about you, Spike?
Let's see... in my case...
I was interviewed a lot and participated
in many panel discussions for the show.
It means the show received
so much attention.
I always said this at every occasion.
I would show this first episode of
Cowboy Bebop to my friends.
And whoever doesn't think it was
a great show is no longer my buddy.
I'd say, "I don't like you anymore.
Bye!" That's all there is to it.
I've renewed my vows. If you
don't like this, I can't be your friend.
Of course everyone has his own taste.
- That sorta summarizes it. Bye for now.
- Cowboy Bebop forever!