♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
♪ I got a feeling that it's
gonna be a wonderful day ♪
♪ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ♪
♪ And he's shining a salute
to the American race ♪
♪ Oh, boy
it's swell to say ♪
♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
The Channel 3 Noon Report,
with anchor partners
Greg Corbin and Terry Bates.
News that's independent,
proud and unashamed.
-Good news
to report today, Greg.
-Sure is, Terry.
The threat level
has just been lowered
from yellow to blue,
prompting
across-the-board reductions
in security measures.
This is the first time
the threat level
has been blue,
same color as
my handsome coanchor's eyes.
-Stop.
-Come on now.
We've talked about this.
-Learn to take a compliment.
-Thank you.
See, now how hard
is that, huh? All right,
let's check the freeways.
Hey, they just lowered
the terror level.
I saw it on the news.
Sweet.
Wanna play backgammon?
Do I?
Well done, fellas.
Our country is
a full color value safer.
Hey, everyone.
The boss just said
we could take a half day.
All right!
I got stuff to do.
-Wanna get baked and ride
the escalators at the mall?
-Do I!
Roger, take something out
or close the refrigerator.
Nothing looks good to me.
You know what looks good to me?
Francine bent over that sink.
Klaus, calm down.
Well, you're home early.
Well, that's my reward
for making the world
a safer place.
That and this magnificent
government paycheck.
That's my Stan the Man.
-Here's your allowance, champ.
-Wow, a whole five bucks.
-Yeah, I'm gonna need change.
-I can't buy
a Game Station with this.
You know, when I was a boy,
five dollars was--
Tell you what.
I'll give you $10
not to tell me this story.
Oh, what's this?
Smells like crap.
That should be empty.
I had my soup for lunch.
Honey, why is there
a biohazard symbol
on your thermos?
Let me see that.
This is not soup.
This is the scene
in Langley Falls, Virginia,
where the Smith family's been
quarantined in their two-story
Georgian Colonial home.
Actually, Terry, it's an
updated Cape Cod. The shutters
are a dead giveaway.
You're right, Greg.
Thanks for correcting me.
That's how I learn.
The Smiths have been exposed
to a biological agent
which will eventually liquefy
their internal organs.
We have a computer-generated
image of what that might
look like.
-But I must warn you--
this is not for the squeamish.
-I'm not gonna look.
Oh, no,
this is a nightmare.
Don't worry, honey.
You know how the media
sensationalizes everything.
Hey, friend,
what's the real deal?
-The good news is
you're not going to die--
-See there?
-What a relief!
-Thank God!
-Wunderbar!
-for 24 hours.
Which is just enough time
for you to learn
not to interrupt someone
when they're talking.
Don't worry, Tony.
We'll find a place
to build that homeless shelter.
Thanks for all
your hard work, Hayley.
-And thanks for walking me home.
-Oh, my God!
-Hayley!
-They let me come say good-bye.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
Hey, how come
she gets to live?
Because I was out
helping the homeless,
-while you were here
being a loser.
-Oh, yeah?
Who's the loser now, loser?
-Mom! Steve just infected me.
-Nobody likes a snitch, Hayley.
I don't believe this.
We're all gonna die!
Yeah, tough break.
Can you hold this for me?
-What the hell are you doing?
-Measuring for drapes.
As soon as you're dead,
I'm gonna completely
redo this place.
I'm thinking something vibrant,
like a seafoam green.
Oh, 'cause I'm gonna need
a lot of happy to get over
all this sad.
Ooh, dimmer switches.
Dimmer switches everywhere.
What makes you think
you're gonna survive?
My species is immune
to all human ailments.
-So explain that cold sore.
-Mind your own business!
Oh, stop bickering.
Time is precious.
We have to make the most
of our last 24 hours together.
Your mother's right.
We should all sit together
as a family
and watch the entire
first season of 24 on DVD.
Well, that was bold television,
and we still have
a minute to spare.
I can't believe
I'm gonna die a virgin.
Aw, sweetie,
there was a 70%, 80% chance
of that happening anyway.
-Daddy?
-No tears, damn it!
A Smith dies with dignity.
Kids, I've been tough on you,
but only because I love you
so very, very--
-Right, I should probably wait.
-This is it!
Look!
I was just snoozing.
You're alive.
We all are.
That clock's always fast.
Let's give it
a few more minutes.
Good news. Apparently
that batch of virus
was inert, so that means--
-We're going to be okay.
-Yes.
Although apparently
your manners died years ago.
You're welcome.
- Hey, what's wrong, honey?
- We're alive.
I know, and that's good.
But, well, when I thought
we were gonna die,
it made me realize
how little I've done
with my life.
And now I guess
I'm feeling... unfulfilled.
Unfulfilled?
But I've given you everything
you could ever want.
You clean, you cook,
and once a week
we lie together
as husband and wife
in sexual congress.
What's going on?
Hi. Barb Hanson,
Exposition Realty.
Let me bring you up to speed.
Your virus scare prompted
these folks to put
their house on the market.
-Any questions?
-No, that was very concise.
Give me a call
if you ever need
a real estate agent.
-I'm also a hand model.
-Sweet Sean Hannity,
your hands are lovely!
-Uh, come on, Francine.
-Oh, boy,
she seemed so confident.
And the way she wears
that smart cranberry blazer
with her company's logo.
-Her life must be so exciting.
-You could do what she does.
-You think?
-Absolutely.
We will absolutely get you
a real estate costume.
Oh, you'll look adorable.
And I'll dress up
as a sea captain,
-and we can take pictures.
-I mean a real job.
No, no, it'll be great.
I'll be Admiral Finch
from the 58th Flotilla.
And you'll be
Lady Constantina,
my real estate agent.
And we'll promenade
around the neighborhood,
delighting young and old alike,
-with our saucy banter.
-I can't be a real estate agent
just because you say so.
It takes years
to get a license.
You leave that
to me, milady.
-Barb Hanson?
-Yes?
Go!
Wait. Go!
What? What's going on?
Congratulations,
you're in real estate.
Adorable.
Wait a minute.
This is Barb's stuff.
-What happened to her?
-She'll be fine.
Hi. Barb Hanson,
Exposition Realty.
Mind if I borrow
one of your napkins?
Thanks.
-You let your wife get a job?
-No, no, no.
It's more like a hobby.
You know, something
to keep her busy until
Stan the Man gets home.
-I used to work in real estate.
-What are you, gay?
I was when I worked
in real estate.
Once I stopped selling houses,
my sodomy cleared up like that.
You know what's so wrong
about gayness?
If there are two men,
who has the vagina?
No kidding.
You need a vagina.
Yeah, vaginas are great.
Wish I had one.
I did it!
-I sold my first house.
-Hey, who's my big girl?
-And such a nice family.
-Oh, they're just the movers.
The new owners
are Greg and Terry.
What were you thinking?
We don't want their kind
in this neighborhood.
-You're overreacting.
-Overreacting? Overreacting?
Do you know
what those two are?
Reporters.
That's right, Francine.
Members of the liberal media.
Stan, not all journalists
are bad. You like
Brit Hume, don't you?
You know damn well
I like Brit Hume.
Just give Greg
and Terry a chance.
All right, but if I--
What? What the hell?
Dimmer switch.
Huh? Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Too fabulous?
I hate this place.
Oh, I haven't even told you
the best part.
Look at
my commission check.
Incredible. That is more
than Stan the Man
makes in a month.
And that's just
for one house.
Ooh, you have been
emasculated
by the superior earning power
of your little Hausfrau.
Ah, oh, God, stud!
Stud! Hit the stud!
Well, you're
in a pickle here.
I agree.
In a relationship,
money is power.
Look, this is just
a bump in the road.
Francine's like a puppy.
Sure, she's having fun
chewing her new bone
and selling a few houses,
but soon she'll get bored
and go right back to ironing
my shirts and scooting
her ass on the carpet.
Open your eyes, Stan.
Your very manhood
is at stake.
-Oh, that's crazy.
-Is it?
When my wife started working,
I didn't think twice,
but she kept earning
more and more money.
And then one day-- Bam!
And I didn't even
get to say good-bye.
-Hmm.
-Your very manhood is at stake.
Your very manhood
is at stake. Your ver--
Okay, that's it.
We're not gonna
carpool anymore.
Here's to Mom. She's finally
cast off the shackles
of domestic servitude
and realized her potential
as a smart, independent woman.
Hayley, how would you like
a punch in the face?
Oh, I have a little surprise.
I bought you all presents.
A donation
for my homeless shelter.
Fifty bucks
towards my Game Station.
A tie?
When do I ever wear a tie?
Thank you very much,
Mrs. Smith.
You paid?
You said you were going
to the bathroom.
-I did both.
-Well, you can just
do it all, can't you?
Gang, we still need
a hundred bucks
for that Game Station.
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
Toshi, you have
a video camera, right?
Wow, that's a lot of words
for "Of course."
I get it.
We can sell Toshi's camera
and get the money.
Whoa, Barry. Why do you always
have to make everything
so complicated?
The plan
is quite simple really.
Toshi will borrow a camcorder
from his parents.
Meanwhile, Snot and I
will find some lovely ladies
willing to go wild,
in exchange for a little
financial aid.
We'll have ourselves
a little photo shoot.
After that, we make
thousands of duplicates,
direct market the tapes
on late-night cable television.
And then we retire
and live out our days
playing video games.
I got to admit.
I wasn't sure
about you fellas,
but sometimes you just
wanna be around other men,
you know?
-It's nice to meet you too.
-Yeah, thanks for,
uh, dropping in.
I envy you guys.
Just a couple of unmarried studs
enjoying life to the max.
-Actually, Greg
was married once.
-I was confused.
Is that why you're here, Stan?
Are you confused?
Things are strained
between me and the missus.
The whole balance of power
in our relationship has shifted,
and, well, I don't like it.
Oh, I don't blame you.
A healthy relationship
should be a partnership.
Well, it's never really equal.
Someone always ends up on top.
Yeah, but you know,
sometimes it's okay
to switch.
-Really?
-Mm, down the line.
I think I hear
what you guys are saying.
I'm the man,
and I have to reclaim
the power in my marriage.
Hey, thanks, fellas.
-Take a picture, why don't you?
-I'm just being polite.
It'd be rude not to look.
Forgive me, Francine.
I'm only doing this
to save our marriage.
What am I thinking?
This is the woman I love.
That's better.
Oh, damn it!
I'm such a softy.
There's gotta be a better way
to put her out of business.
-Uh, excuse me,
are you Francine's boss?
-Yes.
Go! Go! Go!
-You're all under arrest.
-For what?
-Possession
of cocaine doughnuts.
-Those are powdered sugar.
Put it in a rap song,
jailbird. This office
is permanently closed.
-What are you saying?
-I'm saying you're fired.
Oh, for God's sake,
somebody pay Mr. Trump.
So you're sure
we can use this house
for our video shoot?
I overheard my mom say
it's been on the market so long,
everybody's forgotten about it.
Eavesdropper.
You should respect
her privacy.
You guys got beer, right?
'Cause we're not going wild
and exposing our breasts
without beer.
Gotcha covered.
What?
We are going neither wild
nor totally wild
at a homeless shelter.
But we are taking
your beer.
Hayley, you ruined everything.
What are you doing here?
I'm giving these poor,
forgotten people
a new lease on life.
Um, Hayley,
I think Phil is dead.
Now we'll never
get a Game Station.
Au contraire,
my dear Snot.
Hey, honey,
I just heard the news.
Too bad about your office
being closed down.
Well, looks like I'm making
more money than you again.
I'd advise you to write
an offer soon, Randy.
Mortgage rates aren't going
to stay this low forever.
-That's real estate chatter.
-Silence, you fool.
She's closing a duplex
at four percent over list.
Francine, what the hell
is going on?
You were fired.
That's passive past tense,
Trump. You don't own that.
Stan, I'm on the phone.
Sorry, Randy.
I'm working out of
my home office these days.
-Here you go, boss.
-Boss?
I'm Miss Smith's assistant.
Can I get you something
while you wait?
-Uh, a bottled water.
-It's not cold.
Is that all right?
Uh, forget it.
Fran Smith and Associate.
Hold her calls.
Francine, I want you
to stop this nonsense.
Nonsense?
This job is my career.
No, my job is a career.
This is just some silly
housewife's hobby.
Oh, yeah?
Well, this silly housewife
loves her hobby.
She's good at it.
In fact, she kicks ass.
So her big
career man husband
-is just gonna have to
deal with it.
-I could have assassinated you.
-What?
-Nothing.
It was my house first.
You can't stand in the way
of progress, butt-face.
Hey, hey,
what's going on here?
Steve's making
the homeless men in my shelter
beat each other senseless.
It's called "Bum Fights."
I'm gonna make a fortune
selling tickets.
It's exploitation.
You're making money
off their pain and misery.
All right, Hayley,
I'll handle this.
Let me get this straight, Son.
You're pitting desperate,
downtrodden men
against one another
in a violent confrontation
for profit?
-Yes, sir.
-I'm in.
What the hell
is going on here?
Ask Dad. He stole
my whole Bum Fights idea.
He won't even give me
a piece of the action.
Okay, I want this
to be a class act.
I'll introduce you both,
you'll shake hands,
and then I'll throw
raw meat on the floor,
and whoever beats the crap
out of the other one
gets to eat.
Dad, you were supposed
to shut this down. You're
degrading these poor men.
That's ridiculous.
I'm giving them jobs
and self-esteem.
More importantly,
I'm giving them costumes
and a backstory.
This is
The Garbage Collector.
He's got his own catchphrase,
"I'm taking out the trash
and sorting it."
And this guy, this guy,
he grew up in the bayou,
living with alligators,
wrestling with alligators.
I call him The Aviator.
Fight night's already sold-out.
I set up a ring.
Fans can make bets.
I even put out
some nice mixed nuts.
No!
Those are for people.
I can't believe
you muscled out your own son.
You stink, Dad.
Oh, come on,
what's more important?
Your hopes and dreams
or me making more
than your mother?
-This is pure exploitation.
I'm gonna tell Mom.
-Go ahead.
Then your homeless pals
will be right back
on the street,
where the nights are cold
and the fights are meatless.
This isn't over.
Yeah, it's been
that kind of week,
girlfriend,
but, uh, hey,
T.G.I. hump day, huh?
Roger, who are you
talking to?
Tammy, down at Mencer Escrow.
We're phone buddies.
Did you copy
those title reports?
Tams, I gotta go.
Yeah, the boss is being
a real "Catch 'U' Next Tuesday."
Stan the Man is back.
Here you go.
Just my little way
of saying you can keep
your little job.
-A diamond ring!
-I also got you a mink stole.
Oh, my God!
But, Stan,
can we afford this?
Well, you can't,
but I can.
-But how did you get--
-Shh. Smile for LeRoy Neiman.
-He's painting us right now.
-That's LeRoy Neiman?
I know, I thought
he was black too.
I've gotta
hand it to you, Dad.
You really pulled it off.
Or did you?
You unionized
the homeless?
Yep. This is
the Fighting Bums Local 302.
Yeah!
Here are our demands.
"Longer red lights
at freeway off-ramps.
Free doggy day care.
Human dignity"?
I can't meet these demands.
Then you better
start refunding
everyone's money,
'cause there won't be
any bum fights tonight.
-No! You can't take my money.
-Don't sweat it, Dad.
I found a bum
who's willing to scab.
Now all you gotta do
is dress up like a bum
and fight him.
Son, you're a lifesaver.
All right, where's the bum
who's stupid enough
to step into a ring with me?
Who the hell is that?
-He doesn't have a name.
-What do you mean?
He killed his own name.
Ptooey!
My God, Steve!
You couldn't get me
The Aviator
or The Tickler
or Pillow Hands McGraw?
No way! Not me!
I ain't no scab!
Dad, this is suicide.
You're a weapons expert.
When was the last time
you fought hand-to-hand?
I'll be fine, Hayley.
You never forget how to fight.
It's like beating up a bicycle.
Don't let it eat my heart.
This is a wonderful
starter home.
I've been saving it
for a couple just like you.
Pretty soon we're gonna
be more than a couple.
Oh, congratulations.
I just thought you were fat.
-We're adopting.
-Let me show you the backyard.
It's the perfect place
for a baby to play.
Oh, my God!
Stop it!
Stan, what are you doing?
Leave my husband alone.
-Look, that bum's wife has to
jump in and save him.
-What a wuss.
Oh?
It's a knockout.
My dad wins!
I lost a pile of dough
on that one-thumb psycho.
Me too.
Let's exit quickly.
I did it.
I'm Stan the Man.
-Not really.
-We paid this guy
to take a dive.
-Then bet everything on you.
-This whole thing was a setup?
More of a performance piece.
Hi. Ted Fiedler, method actor.
I'm also a hand model.
No!
-Stan, why did you do this?
-Oh, money.
You make more of it than me.
I'm a failure as a man.
You big dope.
Don't you get it?
We're a team.
I know, and you're the owner.
I get it.
No, Stan, we're equals.
We share everything,
good and bad.
You don't have to feel
threatened by my job.
So, you mean,
when you succeed,
I succeed.
Exactly.
Hey, I was gonna
hitch a ride home,
but I bit my thumb off.
-So use your other one.
-Right. Thanks.
Hey, teach a man
to fish, huh?
I made you fresh coffee.
-Have a good day
at work, partner.
-Shh!
Interest rates
went up this morning
by a whopping 20 points,
sending mortgage rates
soaring.
Uh, smart play
locking us in on
that low fixed rate, Terry.
-Thank you.
-Said the man who is finally
learning his own self-worth.
This senseless rate hike
by Federal Reserve Chairman
Alan Greenspan
has jeopardized
the fragile U.S. economy
and put every real estate agent
in the country out of work.
That's a shame.
I'm sorry, hon.
Can I keep this mouse pad?
I'm keeping this mouse pad.
Oh, well, at least
I had some fun,
and you learned there's no need
to be threatened by my success.
Absolutely.
Go, Team Smith.
It's Stan the Man.
Release Greenspan's schnauzer.
Fannie Mae!
That's all for
the morning report.
We'll see you at noon.
And I'll
see you tonight.
-Greg!
-Oh, relax. Everybody knows.
Bye-bye.
See you soon.