♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
♪ I got a feeling that it's
gonna be a wonderful day ♪
♪ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ♪
♪ And he's shining a salute
to the American race ♪
♪ Oh, boy
it's swell to say ♪
♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
- Shut up, Steve!
I have a term paper due.
Ooh, yeah, right.
Community college.
Big girl. Big girl.
Hey, you think that diploma
will help you land
a better section when you're
waitressing at the Olive Garden?
Think you'll hit puberty
before you turn 14?
Why? You wanna do it
with me? You're sick.
Steve, you've only
got one sister. Be nice.
And, Hayley, Steve's
big-boy hair isn't gonna
come in any faster
with you taunting him.
Oh, Francine,
liebchen,
I love the way you rule
with an iron fist.
You know, perhaps when you are
finished there, you would stick
your naughty pinky finger
into mein bowl
und let me feel you.
-Klaus, I don't think--
-You're right.
When the kids are gone.
No, Roger, you cannot
borrow the car!
You think you'd be a little
more grateful to the guy who
saved your life at Area 51.
If my superiors at the C.I.A.
found out you were living here,
we'd have our memories erased.
Did you see Memento? It's
not as good the second time.
-The point is, you are not
allowed to leave the house.
-For God sakes, Stan.
I just wanna
pick up a pack of smokes.
Have you managed to contact
your home planet yet?
Oh, you know,
I was gonna do it yesterday,
but I got distracted.
VH1 was running this
"I Love the '80s" marathon.
Did you know Lou Ferrigno
was deaf?
I don't know.
Somehow it's hard
to take him as seriously.
Oh, hey, Francine,
did you get those Pecan Sandies
I asked for?
Oh, Roger, I'm sorry.
I was at the market yesterday,
and I forgot.
Pretty sure I asked
for Pecan Sandies.
-I'll pick some up
this afternoon.
-Francine, be careful today.
We're at terror alert orange,
which means something
might go down
somewhere in some way
at some point in time,
so look sharp!
You know, Dad,
it's great that you
and your C.I.A. buddies
have created a fun little system
to keep the masses paralyzed
in fear.
You like shavin'
your armpits, Hayley, huh?
'Cause if the terrorists
take over this country,
that's the first thing to go.
it's just toast, Dad.
This time it was toast,
Hayley-- This time.
It's okay.
This one'll be mine.
Hey, Steve, how's it goin' with
that gal on the lacrosse team
I picked out for ya?
Actually, Dad,
I have decided to go
for the brass ring.
Today I'm asking out
Lisa Silver, head cheerleader
and future Mrs. Steve Smith.
Yeah. I like the sound
of that: Steve Smith.
That's my boy.
You hear that, Francine?
Hey, Francine,
tell Steve how many girls
I dated in high school.
-I didn't meet you till college.
-No, but I've told you.
-Steve, I sure hope
she says yes.
-Don't worry.
She won't turn you down.
You're a Smith, and a Smith
always gets his girl.
Mmm. Mmm.
Resist him, Francine.
Resist him!
You und I are meant to be.
Happy hour!
Steve, isn't Lisa Silver
way out of your league?
Well, now, Hayley,
don't bury him
before he's dead.
I think you got a shot,
Steve, as long as you don't
wear that Shazam! shirt.
Oh, don't everybody
help at once.
My goodness, Roger.
When was the last time
you weighed yourself?
Oh, oh. Ow, ow, Francine.
You know, we can't all look
like those anorexic aliens
in the James Cameron movies.
I'm sorry, Roger,
but I'm putting you
on a diet.
-Starting today,
no more junk food.
-What? No.
No. Not my Franken Berries.
Oh, Francine, please.
Be reasonable.
Oh, God. I've got
a bear claw in my ass.
Okay. So that's
two million halogen lamps
and 500,000 coffee tables.
-Thanks a lot.
-Hey, Stan.
What was that all about?
Oh, we just signed a contract
with IKEA to furnish Iraq.
Basically, the whole country's
gonna look like
your first apartment.
I like this.
It fits with our hip,
twenty-something lifestyle.
Oh, for Allah's sake,
put some clothes on!
Now, how about a beer?
Hey, Jackson.
Check out what I bought online.
It's a pencil,
and the eraser
is stuck up bin Laden's pooper.
Ha! Best 40 bucks
I ever spent.
-Wow. You're
in a good mood today.
-You bet I am.
-My kid's
asking out a cheerleader.
-Steve?
That's right. I tell you.
He's just like his old man.
Hey, Marcus, check this out!
The eraser is stuck
up bin Laden's pooper!
He thought
it was funny too.
There she is. Gentlemen,
if you'll excuse me,
I have a fully
developed woman to conquer.
Lisa Silver?
Dude, you're a madman.
Thank you, Snot.
it is a beautiful day
for love, Toshi.
Thank you.
-Steven! Steven! Steven!
-You're cool with chicks.
You're cool with chicks.
Ow!
Hi, Lisa.
Did that hurt so good?
It's Steve, Steve Smith.
Remember me?
Ah, it'll come to ya.
Hey, you wanna go out
Friday night?
-It's okay, baby.
I can handle this.
-Yeah, baby.
How could she just
reject me like--
like I was a nobody?
-Hey. I love your dog.
-Thanks.
Hey, wanna come back
to my apartment
and pet my schnauzer?
-Okay.
-And then we can
play with this dog.
Wait a minute.
That's it! I just need
to get a dog,
and women will
be all over my jock.
In other news, the White House
was stunned today
when President Bush
received a phone call
from God himself.
Uh, hey, George.
It's God.
-Well, hey. How you doin'?
-Good. Good. Doin' good.
Hey, listen. Big favor.
Is there any way that
you could kind of, uh,
from now on
just sort of downplay
our relationship a little more
in your public addresses?
-What do you mean?
-Well, I mean, uh--
To give you an example--
All right. When you
make comments like,
"God wanted me to be president."
You know, that would be
an example of maybe something to
just kind of keep to yourself.
-Well, uh, sure.
I mean, if you want.
-Great. Great. Thanks.
- Ooh. That's Cheney.
- I gotta take it. Yes, sir?
And on Wall Street today,
the Dow was down again.
Ow! Dad, get off me!
I have to study
for my term paper!
-You know the procedure, Hayley.
-How come you never
search Steve?
Now, honey, I love you both,
but Steve is not
a left-wing liberal
who I tried to raise properly
but somehow--
-What's this?
-It's a pack of gum.
All right. It's gum.
Hey, champ.
When's your big date?
Um, she was out sick today.
Well, that's all right.
You'll get her tomorrow.
Hey, listen. Mom, Dad,
can I have a dog?
Absolutely not.
It's enough that
we've got an alien
and a goldfish
with the brain
of a German guy.
Oh, Francine,
I can see your schmutzklitzen.
Sorry, Steve. No dog.
-I'm more than happy to
get you an Etch a Sketch.
-Mom.
You know, Stan,
a dog's not such an awful idea.
It might teach Steve
the responsibility he'll need
for when he, one day,
joins the army.
-Are you seriously contemplating
a military career?
-Thinking about it.
Hey, did somebody
order a brand-new dog?
Oh, sweet, Dad!
You're the best!
What the hell is that?
It's a dog.
-Oh, my God.
-He can barely stand up.
-Well, of course. He's 19.
-Stan, honey, didn't the pound
have any younger dogs?
Francine, this dog
has character. He was around
for the Reagan administration.
-He knows how things
are supposed to be.
-Eh.
Oh, damn it. He's gonna pee!
No, no, no, no!
Nope. Just dust.
Hey, dumb-ass!
Your dog's half dead!
You hear that, boy? That girl
talked to me, and I didn't even
have to talk to her first.
Come on, Thor.
Let's go cruise the mall.
Francine,
you are one lucky lady.
You can do anything you want
to this body because
you married it.
-Mm-hmm.
-I hope you're not
taking all this for granted.
No potato chips.
No cupcakes.
Damn it, Francine!
I'm gonna hawk a loogie
in your Oil of Olay!
-Where's your machete?
-Honey, take it easy.
If I die,
you must protect the clan!
Osama, is that you?
Gee, Stan. What gives?
Holy Toledo.
You killed your son's dog.
And don't ask me
to bring him back with
that E.T. finger thing,
because that's
a giant load of crap.
God, please watch over the soul
of this dead dog
and carry him up to heaven,
because he sure as hell
can't walk.
-He's dead. Amen.
-That was beautiful, honey.
I used to have a dog
and legs and arms.
I was an Olympic skier
before the C.I.A. switched
mein brain with ein goldfish.
What were we supposed to do?
Just let East Germany win that
gold medal? Not on my watch.
Ohh.
You know, Steve's dog
would still be alive
if you right-wing lunatics
would agree to gun control.
You know what I have
to say to that?
Ah. I thought
I was gonna fart.
This sucks.
Now I'm never gonna get a girl.
-Wait a minute. Is that
why you wanted the dog?
-Yes, sir.
Well, son, you don't need
a dog when your old dad
is the greatest ladies' man
of all time-- Come on!
Now, Steve,
girls love a guy
who can protect them.
Now I'm gonna
pretend I'm a thief
and snatch her purse.
Then you'll chase me down,
tackle me and win her heart.
-Got it?
-Got it, Dad.
Oh, my God.
My mom almost caught me
throwing up last night--
-Hey! My purse!
-Don't worry, young lady!
Hey, you!
Come back here!
- Hey!
- Oh, no!
Okay. I got
a little carried away
back there.
-Hey, Jeff.
-Hey, babe. Some guy
at the restaurant
sent his meat loaf back because
there was a hair in it, but
it's cool, because it was mine!
-Picnic in the park?
-I can't. I have this paper due.
Bummer.
Well, you know what
Shakespeare said.
I mean, I don't,
but I'm sure you do.
See ya!
Chillin' with Jeff.
Sounds like fun.
-Yeah, but this is due tomorrow.
-Listen, Hayleykins.
Obviously I can't
leave the house, but if you
supply me with Twinkies,
Ho Hos, you know,
any of your basic
white-trash foodstuffs
that your freakin' mother
won't let me have,
I'll write your paper for you.
-What do you know
about Crime and Punishment?
-You mean, besides the fact
that the suffering of man
is both necessary and useful,
which is revealed to us
during Raskolnikov's redemption?
-Nothing.
-You got a deal.
Sorry about that.
Once every seven hours,
like clockwork.
Oh, my God.
Dad, why is Hilary Duff
in our house?
Hilary is here of her
own free will because she wants
to have dinner with Steve.
-Hilary, could you
pass the salt?
-Pass him the salt.
So, as I was saying,
student body elections
are next week,
and I have personally
been wedgied by both candidates.
Whoa. You hear that, Hilary?
Looks like you're a winner
with Steve.
Help me!
Dad, you can't go around
abducting people just because
you're C.I.A.
Hilary, look out for the mines!
What did I just say? You
heard me. What did I just say?
-You said,
"Look out for the mines."
-"Look out for the mines."
I don't understand. I didn't
have this problem getting
girls when I was his age.
A little observation, Stan.
Steve isn't like you.
You're a big, powerful guy.
Women are attracted to power,
and Steve just doesn't have any.
That's it.
If Steve needs power,
I'll rig the school election
and make him student body
president.
-Wow. Can you do that?
-Rigging elections
is my bread and butter, Roger.
All right, Steve.
Now the key to
fixing any election
is to cast doubt
on your opponent.
Vote Shelly Maxwell
for student body president.
Shelly for president.
Sure, you can vote
for Shelly Maxwell, if you don't
mind voting for a prostitute!
-What?
-Don't play coy,
You cardigan jezebel!
I have photographic evidence
of you having sexual relations
with the Jack in the Box man.
Ew!
-The Jack in the Box man?
He's not even human!
-That's sick!
-Dad, is that really
the Jack in the Box man?
-Yeah. He's in our basement.
-You know, I got an "A"
on that paper.
-My pleasure.
-Got anything else
in the pipeline?
-I've got a poli-sci paper.
-You know anything
about Henry Kissinger?
-All I know is he's Jewish,
but if you get me some churros,
I can probably stretch that
into about 12 pages.
Hey, Steve.
Congratulations.
Why, thank you, Lisa.
Say, I was thinking,
maybe you and I could--
-Go out? I'd love to.
-Yes!
Oh, my God! Score,
score, score, score, score!
-Women love a man with power.
-You were right, Dad.
Hey. Sorry to interrupt,
Stan.
I was gonna take a shower,
but we're all out of Prell.
-You mind pickin' some up?
-Yeah, yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, Steve,
kudos on the beeyatch.
-Man, your stream
is so powerful.
-Thanks.
I wish your locker
wasn't right next
to the boys' room.
Yeah, me too. Then again,
I am student body president.
Smith, what's the meaning
of this?
Principal Lewis,
I'm taking your office.
Pursuant to Pearl Bailey
High statute 39-F, quote,
"The student body president
may acquisition any room on
school premises for the purpose
of conducting school business."
You can read!
The system works!
I'll be back for my stuff.
You're amazing, Steve.
I'm gonna go tell everyone
we're going out.
This is it.
I have absolute power.
Doris, could you please
send in our high school mascot?
Welcome, buffalo.
As you must have heard,
I've been elected
student body president.
As such, I can
do anything I want,
- and I want...
to ride the buffalo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Yes! Yes!
I'm riding the buffalo!
Now send in the lunch lady.
The lady's steak is not
nearly Salisbury enough.
Take it back.
Steve,
you're the greatest boyfriend
I've ever had.
My dear, I'm just
getting started.
Bobby, get over here.
I want my Shazam! shirt
dry-cleaned and pressed
by third period.
Oh, and another thing.
All periods will now
be called "Steves."
Hey, I'm thinkin' of
cuttin' third Steve. You in?
-Yeah, as long as I'm back
by fourth Steve.
-So if it's a statement,
it should always
be followed by a Steve.
Mr. Philips, may I be excused?
I'm having my Steve.
Mmm. Oh, Hayley,
you are the best.
Mmm. Now what else
we got here? Chocodiles.
Haven't tried those.
Oh. Oh-ho-ho.
Oh, my God!
How good are these!
Oh. Mmm-mmm. Dangerous.
Mmm.
How's my paper comin', Roger?
You know, it's due
tomorrow morning.
-Got it under control, Hayley.
Do not worry.
-Okay.
By the way, Hayley--
Oh, my God.
These Chocodiles--
These Chocodiles,
Hayley-- Oh, my God.
These Chocodiles--
Oh, my God.
-Um, yeah. They're good.
Back to work.
-I'm on it.
Oh, no. Hayley!
Hayley! Hayley, wake up.
I fell asleep. I had
a sugar crash and I fell asleep.
-I didn't do the paper.
-What? It's due in two hours!
I know. I'm a douche bag,
but the important thing now is
to find a way to buy more time--
Holy frijole.
I got an idea.
Well, under the circumstances,
I think we can give you
another few days for your paper.
Thank you, Mr. Goodwin.
Hey, these chocolate lockers
were a great idea!
-Mine has nut clusters.
Thanks, Steve.
-No problem.
I am a river to my people,
and I hope you're all
enjoying the computer lab
now that I've
disabled the porn blocker.
Yeah. I never knew
Todd's mom had a Web site.
-Pretty sexy, huh, guys?
-Sure is, Todd.
Oh, hello, gorgeous.
-Ew. What are you doing?
-What? I'm kissing my woman.
Steve, I like the perks
of dating the school president,
but I'm not gonna kiss you.
I mean, I'm beautiful,
and you're repulsive.
-But-- But I thought
you liked me.
-Yeah. You were supposed to.
Attention:
There is a new school policy.
Anyone caught holding hands,
hugging or swapping saliva
will be expelled from school
permanently.
It's too risky right now.
I'll come back tonight.
This is Stan Smith.
Mr. Smith,
I'm afraid there's a problem
with your son.
Oh, God. He's gay.
This is it.
This is the gay call.
-I've been ready for this
for years.
-Uh, no.
It's just that
he's gone mad with power.
He evacuated the entire school
and barricaded himself
in my office.
I see. Henry, antidote!
Hey, how'd
the dead dog work out?
Did it buy us some time?
-Yeah. He gave me till Monday.
-Oh, great. Here's my list.
Sorry, Roger.
That was too close a call.
I'm gonna do my own work.
Wha-- But I--
Wh-Where am I gonna get my fix?
-Not my problem.
-You can't do it alone, Hayley.
You don't have the skills.
You're not smart enough.
Somebody'll clean that up.
-Steve, this is your father.
-Get out of here, Dad.
I'm not comin' out.
All right. I'm going in.
Francine, keep talking
to him.
-Be careful, honey.
-Hey, don't worry
about me, kiddo.
-Oh, oh. Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
-I'm fine, honey. It's okay.
-Oh, God. I just meant
to brush you lightly.
-I know, sweety. It's all right.
-I guess
I don't know my own strength.
-Go get Steve, honey.
-Right.
-Steve, it's Mommy.
Listen, honey.
You're not alone.
When I was your age,
I had a huge crush
on someone too--
Mr. Feeny,
my algebra teacher.
Such a cute man
with a neat little beard.
Of course, he didn't
take me seriously,
but that all changed
when his wife found me
in their closet,
cutting myself
and sniffing his t-shirts.
-Dad, what are you doing?
-Son, I'm stopping you
from making a huge mistake.
I lied and told the police
we were lovers.
-He either killed himself,
or he's in jail--
-Francine, for God's sake!
I got him!
Wanna talk about it, champ?
Dad, Lisa only liked me
because I was school president.
She thinks I'm repulsive,
and the worst part of it is,
she's right.
Steve, I promise you, and this
comes from years of experience:
women are never right.
I was crazy to think
any girl could ever like me.
Look at me.
I am repulsive.
No, you're not.
Look, son. Roger was right.
You're not like me.
You're not as good looking
or as strong or as smart
or as good sexually.
Oh, wait. He killed himself
in jail.
Damn it, Francine!
We're having a moment here!
Listen, son.
I'm gonna show you something
I've never shown anyone before.
-That's me when I was your age.
-Oh, my God! You were hideous!
Well, I certainly wasn't
the stallion I am today.
The point is, Steve, you'll
be just fine, because you're
chock-full of potential.
Wow. Thanks, Dad.
Aw, but I don't wanna
face Lisa Silver.
I got you covered.
Hello? I.N.S.?
Is this Nick?
Hey, Nick. It's Stan.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Hey, how'd that wiretap
on your wife work out?
Oh. Oh. Sorry about that.
But, hey, better
with your brother
than some stranger, right?
Yeah. Movin' on.
Movin' on. Right. Right.
Say, listen,
could you do me
a huge favor?
You know the Silver family
at 419 Elm? Yeah.
Let's deport them.
You're the best, Dad.
Mmm. Great stew,
Francine.
The peas are like
floating survivors
from a sunken beef ship.
Steve, you're awfully quiet.
Are you still upset
about what happened at school?
I'm fine with that.
I just wish I was smoother
with the ladies.
Oh, okay, Melissa.
So I'll meet you at the arcade
tomorrow after school.
Bye. Thanks for the help,
coach.
My pleasure.
But if you expect
to get any boob,
I'm gonna need
a butt-load of Twinkies.
Uh, "gesundheit"?
Have a great night.