♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
♪ I got a feeling that it's
gonna be a wonderful day ♪
♪ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ♪
♪ And he's shining a salute
to the American race ♪
♪ Oh, boy
it's swell to say ♪
♪ Good morning, U.S.A. ♪
CHORUS:
(bones crunching)
(all screaming)
I just made a killing
in the shock market.
Time!
Reset the test course.
(bell rings)
(chattering)
(groans)
Deputy Director Bullock,
I had no idea you were watching.
Glad I could be so impressive.
I'll take my victory muffin now.
Make it... bran.
I'm afraid your usual muffin's
been earmarked for someone else.
Hi. Agent Duper.
Big fan.
Agent Duper
not only bested your time,
he did so with
a far better catchphrase.
-What? Better
than "shock market"?
-Duper?
(imitating Desi Arnaz)
Lucy, you got some
'sploding to do.
-(grenade explodes)
-(man screams)
Oh, we're doing
accents now?
But at the last minute,
God told Abraham
not to sacrifice his son.
It was all just
a test of his faith.
My uncle's doing 25-to-life
for sacrificing his son.
Well, I hope he found God.
He sure didn't find him
in my cousin's stomach.
-Hayley!
-Mom!
This is my Bible class.
Please, dim your headlights.
Bible class, huh?
Hey, tell them the story
of how God was denied
his fruity cereal.
No, wait.
That was the Trix rabbit.
I get them confused,
because they're both fake.
-When did you become so jaded?
-She's a harlot!
-They should be stoned!
-Way ahead of you, kid.
I'm telling you.
That Agent Duper
is out for my job.
I always get the muffin.
Always! Damn it!
Did you use
my "shock market" line?
Yeah, and it died.
Thanks a lot, Larry David.
Beep, beep.
Done with your
foot cream, Stan.
I got most of it
back in the tube.
Oh, for crying out loud!
Can't you get your own?
Love to, but you won't
let me leave the house.
So, unless you're gonna open
a Circle K in the dining room,
looks like we're
ointment buddies.
Oh, and F.Y.I., your roll-on
really worked wonders
on my 'rhoids.
Great. Francine, this Duper
situation is out of control.
Hey, why don't you invite
your boss over for dinner
tomorrow night?
You know, for some good,
old-fashioned boot licking.
Dinner, huh?
Great idea.
Ah, cheap Chinese toothbrush!
They can make a chicken
taste like an orange,
but when it comes
to oral hygiene,
they really phone it in.
(fanfare plays)
-You bitch.
-Bitch.
-Bitch!
God, they sure knew
how to write female
characters back then.
Look alive, people!
Roger, what the hell?
If my boss sees you,
I'm finished.
-(doorbell rings)
-That's him.
Up in your attic! Move!
-Ah, now you're doing this?
-Yeah, I haven't
been feeling so great.
Once it dries,
it'll chip right off.
-Go!
-Can I just top off
my Chardonnay?
-I'll bring it up later.
-Something bright
and summery on the palate,
but with an explosive
finish--
All right, I'm going!
Deputy Director Bullock,
welcome, welcome!
We're so glad you could make it.
Where's your wife this evening?
Handcuffed to a radiator
in Fallujah.
She wanted to come,
but I do not negotiate
with terrorists.
Hey, do I smell meat loaf?
Hayley, why don't you
say grace?
-I'll pass.
-Come on.
You pray all the time
when Jeff comes over.
"Oh, God! Oh, God!"
Yes, yes, she's very devout.
Anyway, what are these
photos doing laminated
in our place mats?
Is this Agent Duper?
Yes, and he's eating
a falafel, recreationally.
-(coughs) Terrorist.
-Smith!
It appears you've
gone to great lengths
to discredit a fellow agent.
I like your style.
-(women on TV, slapping)
-Slut!
-God, who do you have to probe
around here to get a Chardonnay?
-(continues)
Um, uh--
Idaho!
-That's all 50.
-Idaho.
-Well done, Smith!
-(gasps)
Pardon me. I think I hear
my wife's pie burning.
That's my boss out there!
Have you lost your mind?
-No, but I lost my buzz,
thanks to you.
-BULLOCK: Smith?
-Into the bathroom!
-(yelling)
Smith, this might be
the Chardonnay talking,
but I think this bathroom
is the perfect place
to discuss your promotion.
-Into the tub!
-Without my flip-flops?
-Ah, no! Good God,
control yourself!
-(yelling)
Stop it!
Oh, in my eye!
Smith, are you
under attack in there?
-No, everything's fine.
-Stand back!
(grunts)
Good God, Smith!
What the-- Oh!
(groaning)
Thanks a lot, Roger.
How do you expect me
to compete with Duper
after what
my boss saw in there?
It's not my fault
I don't feel well.
It's always something with you.
You've been nothing
but a burden.
-(gasps)
-Stan, please!
Yeah, Dad.
Don't stress him out.
It messes with his stomachs.
No! No! It's about time
he heard it!
We're the ones risking
our necks here.
Do you know what would happen
to us if the government found
out we were hiding an alien?
Oh, but he doesn't care. No,
he just lays around the house,
inhaling groceries
and pumping out pudding.
Shut up, Stan!
Just shut up!
Our lives would be
a hell of a lot easier
if you were just gone!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I-I-I-I--
(gasping, wheezing)
Roger, are you okay?
Oh, bravo, bravo.
Quite a performance.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Ethan Hawke.
-He doesn't look right, Dad.
-Up and at 'em, Ethan.
Time to make another awful
Richard Linklater movie.
Just ignore him.
He's being a drama queen.
-All right, everyone up to bed.
-It's 7:45.
We're going to bed!
Uh, "Good night, Klaus?"
Geez!
Huh. What commitment!
Wakey, wakey, Mr. Hawke.
Gattaca II finally
got its financing.
-Dad, I think he's dead.
-(gasps)
Well, then I guess he
wouldn't mind if I poke him
in the eye with a fork.
-(all screaming)
-Yeah, he's dead.
I can't believe
he's gone.
He's up in heaven now,
bumming smokes off Jesus.
-Poor Roger.
-We should have a really
nice memorial service.
Out of the question!
No, I'll have to dispose
of the body,
so the government can never
trace it back to us.
Well, at least do it
in a way that honors
his memory
and all that he
meant to us.
Darling, it's me.
A double cheeseburger,
small fries and a Mr. Pibb.
Not the largest.
The one right under that.
MAN (on speaker):
That would be the medium.
(tires screeching)
Can I get some ketchup?
Oh, no, it's already in there.
I see it. I see it.
(screams)
Oh, that sounded
kind of effeminate.
Holy crap!
Can't a guy fall
into a stress-induced
hibernation cycle
without being
chucked in the trash?
-Okay, calm down. Calm down.
Nothing to be scared of.
-(bird tweets)
(screams)
Ahh, get it off me!
Wait a minute.
I can use this to get home,
-disguised as a lady.
-(glass clinking)
A lady who keeps medical
waste in her pockets.
You call me, Dad?
Son, I know you're
having trouble dealing
with Roger's death,
so I thought
it might cheer you up
to help me burn
every shred of evidence
that he ever existed.
What? Why can't we
just hide that stuff?
It's too risky. No one can
ever know Roger was here.
Don't you have
any feelings?
Son, feelings
are what women have.
They come from their ovaries.
You're a monster!
I have no father!
I'm not
a monster.
So if I cash out
my pension right now,
how much will I get?
Oh, damn it!
That's a very steep penalty.
So, basically, you're
telling me I'm stuck here
for two more years.
Yeah, thanks
for nothing, Marty.
So-So what is it now?
Your mother died or something?
No, it was
a very dear, dear--
He was like a pet.
You'll have to forgive her.
She's very upset.
Could you say a prayer
for him on Sunday?
You know, so maybe
he'll hear it in heaven.
For a pet?
You're serious?
Look, according to the church,
there are no pets in heaven.
Eligible for heaven: You got
your men, women, children
and apes who use
sign language.
Not going to heaven: You got
your pets, your dinosaurs,
your smart types
and self-aware robots.
You ever seen Blade Runner?
No, of course you haven't.
All righty. Can I validate
your parking?
Wait a minute.
Roger was good.
What kind of god wouldn't
allow him into heaven?
This kind.
That's your idea
of God?
(chuckles)
Hey, kick your ass.
-(sobbing)
-Whatever.
How do I get home?
Where the hell is
a trail
of Reese's Pieces
when you need one?
-Hey, where you goin'?
-(screams) I'm not an alien.
Back on the bus,
Mrs. Nesbaum.
ROGER: Huh?
Look, there's been a mistake.
I need to get home.
The home? No, we're goin'
to D.C. to see the sights.
Haven't seen you
around the pill line.
The name's Gertie.
Now don't you fret about that.
Happens to me all the time.
What do you know?
It's happenin' right now.
Morning, Jackson. Wanna help me
analyze some Al-Qaeda chatter?
Actually, Stan, they put
Agent Duper on chatter.
They bumped you
down to Al-Qaeda banter.
MAN (on tape): So I'm trying
those whitening strips,
but they're not working.
MAN 2: Are you
wearing them every day?
-Well, every other day.
-Well, duh. That's why
they're not working.
STEVE'S VOICE:
Don't you have any feelings?
You're a monster!
I have no father!
(groans)
What seems to be
the problem?
Well, I got in an argument
with our dog.
He expelled a large amount
of xenoplasm, and then he died.
Am I a monster
for not feeling anything?
Well, that depends, Stan.
How close were you to this dog?
Well, we do go back a ways.
-(alarm sounding)
-MAN (on P.A.): The alien
has escaped to Level 4.
-Repeat: Level 4!
-(electronic humming)
I'll check this lab
where the theremin music
is coming from.
Don't hurt me.
I know it sounds cliché,
but I mean you no harm.
You're the alien?
Well, they said you'd be
bigger, and with claws.
Oh, I've got claws.
Look how fat you are.
See? Kitty can scratch.
MAN: It's in the lab!
Let's dust it!
Let's go, space chimp!
(groaning)
You saved my life.
How can I ever repay you?
You got TiVo?
Stan? Thought
I lost you there.
Now look,
this is a safe place.
How do you feel?
Oh, I guess I feel
kind of... sad?
-And do you know why?
-Because I... miss him?
No. Because
you're a lady!
-(laughing)
-"Oh, yeah. I'm sensitive."
-I am not a lady!
-Wait, Stan.
You forgot your purse.
Oh, I swear I'd lose
my own head if I--
Hey, I don't have a purse!
Heaven, pearly gates, angels--
it's all a lie.
When your parents die, they'll
be in a hole in the ground,
worms slowly chewing through
their foul, putrid organs.
Uh, don't worry, kids.
God is real,
Jesus loves you,
et cetera, et cetera.
Mom, what are you doing?
Well, I just can't believe
in a god
that wouldn't
let Roger into heaven.
Hey, Hayley, since Dad's
a heartless bastard and all,
I'm auditioning
new father figures.
Should I go with
outwardly affectionate
Tom Hanks
or consistently
underrated Jeff Bridges?
Why are you worried about Dad?
It's Mom that we've lost!
Steve, mein Kinderstrudel,
there's an emotionally
available father figure
floating in front of you.
-Really? You'd be my dad?
-It would be mein honor.
Now, here's your allowance.
Five bubbles.
Ach! What the hell.
Six bubbles.
Don't tell your mother.
Wow.
The Oval Office.
Just think of the history
that's been made
behind that desk.
Not to mention under it.
(laughing)
-Here, have yourself a nip.
-Wow! Getting hammered
in the Oval Office.
Hey, look! I'm Kitty Dukakis
in an alternate timeline.
People, this footage was
captured at 1400 hours today
by a White House
security camera.
Sorry I'm late. I was getting
a piping hot cup of coffee.
It's far too hot to drink,
but luckily my leathery
man mouth can take it.
Sit down, Smith. Our analysts
have confirmed this creature
is none other than the alien
that escaped from Area 51
four years ago.
-My eyes!
-He's alive!
Naturally, recapturing this
fugitive is our top priority.
Then we can track down
the bastards
that have been harboring it
and punish them brutally!
-(man screams)
-I mean really brutally.
Weird stuff. Butt stuff.
-(man screams)
-Somebody take Smith's coffee.
(horn honking)
-(patriotic ring tone)
-Smith. Talk.
Stan, you lantern-jawed
Sasquatch!
You throw any of your kids
in the garbage today?
Roger, I've been looking
for you. Where are you?
Oh, I'm getting by
just fine on my own.
And I got--
I got something to say--
-Call him a carpetbagger!
-You're a carpetbagger, Stan!
You know that?
What's that?
Look, I'm sure you're mad
I chucked you in the trash,
but I've thought about it,
and I'm willing to forgive me.
But the important thing is
the C.I.A. is looking for you.
Oh, yeah? Bring 'em on!
I got some stories to tell them
about who's been hiding me.
Hope you and your family
like prison, because that's
where you'll be rotting.
In prison! That's who!
Hey, I'm not
screwing around here. My butt
is literally on the line.
Well, that must be one
massive line, because
your butt is huge!
-(laughs)
-(line disconnects)
So, old buddy,
to protect our family,
we must kill a friend.
Don't worry. It's not you.
I could never be mad at you.
Huh? Coochie-coochie.
Ha, ha! Made you laugh!
Gun, we've got to track down
and kill Roger
before the C.I.A. finds him.
(sniffing)
Oh, gun!
Crack a window!
Boy, I really got up
in Stan's grille, huh?
He was all, "Come back!"
And I was all,
"Fat-ass carpetbagger!"
-(laughing)
-He had it comin'!
That family don't give
a Dixie toot about you.
From now on,
we're a family.
We are, aren't we?
Oh, my God!
A Dynasty exhibit.
They must've gotten
my letters.
Can we go? Can we go?
Can we go? Can we?
Sounds glorious.
Let's get movin', sis.
Oh, almost forgot.
(hawking)
That's for freein' the slaves,
you Negro-lovin' Yankee devil!
And suddenly
things turned ugly.
Roger?
(whistles)
Here, boy! Damn it.
Where could he be?
This ain't
your corner, bitch!
Well, I guess my G.P.S.
is out of whack, slut!
-Bitch!
-Slut!
This reminds me of something.
(gasps)
Dynasty!
C.I.A.
To the Smithsonian! Drive!
Wait. This is my car.
Even better!
Now, Son, here's a fun activity
my father taught me.
But I feel weird
washing Mom's underwear.
Nonsense!
We're bonding. Now bury me
in an avalanche of panties.
Ja. Ja. Her sweaty,
sweaty sports bra!
(cackling)
Mom, you're reading
the Bible again!
Oh, no.
There's an oil spill
in the garage.
I'm just gonna mop it up
with Exodus.
-(phone rings)
-Hello?
Hayley? Roger.
Got a sec?
Roger? Whoa!
Is this one of those
Twilight Zone phones
where I can talk to the dead
but only with horrible,
ironic consequences?
Oh, right. It's past noon.
You're already high.
Let me talk to the fish.
Oh, my God!
You're really alive?
Yes, and I've somehow acquired
a nasty, old, racist sidekick.
I'm at the Smithsonian.
You gotta come get me.
There you are. You send
me to get you a churro,
and then you disappear.
-Anyway, here's your
filthy wetback doughnut.
-Hurry.
(gasps)
We've tracked the alien here.
We need to take it alive,
so we can punish those
who've been hiding it.
Not if I get to him first.
Oh, my God!
Joan Collins's ball gown!
Linda Evans's tennis outfit!
Wow! John Forsythe's girdle!
Oh, the stories it could tell.
-STEVE: Roger?
-Steve! Hayley!
Oh, thank God you came.
Roger's alive?
It's a miracle!
I knew you couldn't resist
a federally funded
Dynasty exhibit.
Stan! Look,
about that phone call--
-(gunshot)
-(screams) What are you doing?
-Say your prayers, space chimp.
-Stan, no!
Leave her alone,
whitey!
-(gunshots continue)
-(both gasping)
BULLOCK:
Damn it! He's getting away!
DUPER:
Look, we're parachute ghosts!
(making ghostly sounds)
All this
for a "fat-ass" comment?
No, former Dad!
Nobody threatens my family.
Now get out of the way,
or I'll shoot you all.
Oh, God, it's my junior prom
all over again.
Leave her alone, you
two-dollar, pai-gow whore!
(Gertie screaming)
We know you're in there, alien!
Come out with your tentacles up!
-Dad, you can't
just give him up!
-That's the C.I.A. out there.
They won't stop until
they have Roger in custody.
-Just make it quick.
-No, Roger!
-Use my children as a shield!
-(both gasping)
It's no use. They've got me.
If they torture me, I'll crack.
I mean, I can't even
make it through the afternoon
without a freakin' mojito.
I'd never want to put
my family's safety at risk.
-Your family?
-Of course. Now, how
are we gonna do this?
I think right here
would be most dramatic.
Okay. Huh?
What's this? Some kind
of tear-like substance
coming from my eyes.
-He's crying.
-I'm not a lady!
Stan, having feelings
doesn't make you a lady.
It makes you human.
BULLOCK:
We've got to blow this door!
Prepare the door blower!
We really should find
a better name for that.
(sighs)
Well, it's clear
what I have to do.
-Smith!
-I've got the alien, sir.
Give me back my wig,
you scalp-happy red man!
Look how it mimics
our language.
(Gertie muttering)
Well done, Agent Smith.
I'm going back to the office
and striking the words
"tool" and "incompetent"
from your personal record.
Thanks. Perhaps
you could insert the words
"lady" and "not a."
You know,
I think we can.
It's good to have you
back, buddy.
So, Roger,
what was heaven like?
-Heaven? Wh-What
the hell are you--
-(kicking)
Oh, yeah, heaven.
Oh, oh, it was great.
Fluffy clouds, unicorns,
bubble-gum waterfalls,
all that crap.
Roger's our little miracle.
Isn't he, Mom?
He sure is. God certainly
works in mysterious ways.
Oh, wait.
This is last month.
Bye. Have a great time!